Chapter 100: Jia Yuan City

The Lan Province is the eighth largest of the thirteen provinces in the State of Yue. It is located in the southern region of the State of Yue. Despite its small size, it is said to be quite wealthy, second only to the Xin Province. With fertile land, countless rivers, lakes, and canals running through the region, as well as constant favorable weather, the province was extremely suited to growing grain and rice. Thus, it became the State’s largest producer of crops.

Located in the center of Lan Province was Jia Yuan City. Although it wasn’t the Lan Province’s capital, it was, without question, the largest city its province. The Great Lu Canal, which spanned from the north to the south of the province, passed through the center of the city. In addition, several roads and waterways also ran through the city. As a result, the city’s transportation was highly developed and could be considered the hub of water transportation, as well as the main road of trade and commerce in the region. Every year, an innumerous amount of merchants and travelers passed through, spurring an enormous amount of trade at this location. Therefore, the fact that Jia Yuan City became the largest city in the province was not strange in the least.

In Jia Yuan City, there was traffic of all sorts. Docks and boatmen were numerous, and could be found anywhere in the city. Boatmen, cart drivers, and unskilled laborers were as many as number of the hairs on an ox. There were several tens of thousands of people, including Sun Ergou,[1] who relied on the harbor to make a living.

Like his name suggested, Sun Ergou had long, slanted eyebrows and crooked eyes. In addition, he had the appearance of a ruffian, a cross between a rotten pear and a spoiled jujube. However, because he was skilled in flattery and reading body language, he had actually been able to secure the position of minor gang leader. Managing several tens of unskilled porters, he made a living off the harbor transporting the goods and luggage of passing merchants.

This was the reason why Sun Ergou’s many subordinates had hastily gathered at early dawn and respectfully addressed him with “Good morning Grandpa Er!” and “Grandpa Er has come!”[2]

……

Hearing these greetings, Sun Ergou could not help but be somewhat smug. After all, being addressed as “Grandpa” indicated that here, he was someone of status. Consequently, he exhibited an air of arrogance. He finally responded to his subordinates’ greetings after snorting from his nose, “Who is Grandpa Er? Shouldn’t it be Grandpa Ergou?”

“It should, but here, there’s only a two-legged dog imitating a man!”[3]

“Haha! Haha! …”

……

The burst of mocking and ridicule could not mask the words that entered Ergou’s ear.

After Sun Ergou had heard this, his face suddenly sunk, and his mood dropped in an instant.

He slowly turned his head and looked to the several tens of people at the other side of the dock. He brought his gaze down to a large, burly, dark-skinned man as a hint of hate flashed in his eyes.

Among all the people that Sun Ergou hated the most in the entire city of Jia Yuan, this large, dark-skinned man would absolutely make it into his top three. If someone were to tell him that he or she would use the wealth of Sun Ergou’s entire family to thoroughly make this large, dark-skinned man disappear from the world, Sun Ergou might hesitate, but if he or she changed it to only half of Sun Ergou’s wealth, he wouldn’t hesitate to agree in the least. Naturally, this was because he led a life of decadence; the so-called entirety of his family’s wealth wasn’t much to begin with.

No one had known what the dark-skinned man’s name was for quite a long time. The people at the harbor either addressed him as “Grandpa Black”, or his nickname, “Black Bear”. He was the leader of the small gang “Iron Fist Group” while Sun Ergou held a similar status in the “Fourth Level Gang”. As a result, these factions had arrived at this dock to supervise the porters of their respective sides.

A mountain cannot hold two tigers, let alone this minuscule dock. As a result, the two gangs have had tense relations since. After several conflicts over merchant customers, their relationships grew even more vile. Whenever the two gangs saw each other, they would sneer in contempt and shove each other aside, falling short of a full-on conflict.

If the subordinates acted in this manner, then what was there to say about the greatest beneficiaries of the business here, Sun Ergou and Black Bear? These two figures looked at each other with great dislike. However, as the young gang leaders, these two knew that the Iron Fist Group and the Fourth Level Gang were allied gangs. They had united to fend off the comparatively larger “Poison Dragon Gang”. As a result, although the two had wanted to drive the other away from this place and monopolize the dock, they could only restrain themselves for the time being. However, they accumulated resentment and fury against one another and vented their feelings through their subordinates’ verbal conflicts. Their exchange of insults had become a common occurrence that took place every morning.

As a matter of fact, Sun Ergou’s subordinates did not even wait to initiate a conflict. Many clever, eloquent subordinates struck back without a trace of politeness.

“Do you know what animal is the most stupid of them all?”

“Bears!”

“Which of bears are the most stupid?”

“Black bears without a doubt!”

“Ha…”

When Black Bear had originally heard his own subordinates ridicule the other party, his face wore a proud expression. However, his elated face darkened after hearing these words. Sun Ergou started to smile. Pleased, he patted the shoulders of several subordinates to further encourage them.

Black Bear’s subordinates were not to be outdone. Those on Sun Ergou’s side were not polite either. A great deal of filthy words spurted out from both sides. Everyone became each other’s old grandpa, and neither side feared the other. Naturally, the conflict at the dock was not pleasant to hear. Vulgar unpleasantries of all kinds were exchanged.

As the leaders of their respective gangs, Sun Ergou and Black Bear cooly looked at each other. Since they were people with status, they naturally could not join in the abusive, quarrelsome racket.

Just as these two sides’ mouths and tongues were about to dry, saliva suddenly splattered. One of Sun Ergou’s subordinates cried out in alarm, “A boat is drawing near!”

These words roused Black Bear’s near one hundred cursing subordinates, who all exhaled in surprise. They all stopped making noise and immediately turned their gazes toward the river bank. After all, shining white silver was far more attractive than the fleeting verbal delight.

However, when Black Bear’s group looked toward the boat in the dock, they were somewhat disappointed. It was only a small flat boat. At best, it would only have three to five merchant customers, which was not a large amount of business at all.

This was not surprising, given that this dock was rotten and small. In addition, its location was far from the city. Under these circumstances, it was only natural that no big boats would come here. However, during peak season for trade and commerce, other docks would have no space for large boats, so merchants would have no choice but to disembark here.

After this small boat stopped at the dock, two people climbed off board. One appeared to be a common youngster about seventeen to eighteen years old. The other was a large man at least two heads taller than an ordinary person.

The youngster wore a common azure garment, and a small yellow bird perched on his shoulder. Just as he stepped off board, he looked around. He had the appearance of a rural villager that had entered the city for the first time. The huge man wore a green gown and a mantle over his head. His facial appearances were unclear because he wore his clothes in a strange manner. The huge man followed close behind the youngster, refusing to fall even a step behind. Based on his appearance, it seemed that he was a servant.

The huge man and the youngster were actually Han Li and Crooked Soul; they had traveled on the road for three consecutive months before arriving at Doctor Mo’s homeland.

TL Note: This is the start of Book Two. You're in for a great ride.

[1]. TL: Sun Ergou. Sun being a surname (not the star in the sky) and Er’gou meaning Second Dog

[Back]

[2]. In Confucianism, status is often associated with age. That is why you often see in Chinese stories, “I, your father.” or “This grandpa [referring to self]”, as a way of acting arrogant.

[Back]

[3]. TL: A play on words from his name. ?? Ergou, Er ? Two, Gou ? Dog.

[Back]

Chapter 103: Subdue

Han Li had his back facing Black Bear, who was standing alongside the battling crowd. Although Black Bear tried his best to soften his footsteps, how could it possibly escape Han Li’s notice?

As the distance between Black Bear and Han Li shortened to just a few steps, Black Bear started to sprint, moving frenziedly like a demon. Han Li lightly shifted his body slightly and pivoted to directly face Black Bear, revealing a smile on his face.

Black Bear was shocked out of his wits, but he could no longer stop his momentum. Helplessly, he could only roar as he extended his black hairy hands, grabbing ruthlessly towards Han Li. He estimated that Han Li was just someone without much battle experience, and should have been shocked immobile by his savage, demon-like rush, thus rendering him vulnerable

Upon seeing the black, burly man recklessly raise his hand against him, Han Li’s expression suddenly sunk. His body flickered and disappeared right in front of Black Bear’s eyes.

Black Bear’s roar became stuck in his throat as he quickly halted his steps, planning to run away. Suddenly, he felt the point of a sword that shone brilliantly like snow coming into contact with his throat before it disappeared once more. Black Bear rapidly covered the bleeding wound with his hands and attempted to speak. However, only some unintelligible grunts was heard before his corpse fell onto the ground.

The color of Sun Ergou’s face turned waxy yellow. He had witnessed the youth moving like a specter as he appeared behind Black Bear’s back and easily sliced Black Bear’s throat with a flexible sword he had drawn from his waist. Afterward, the youth took out a white cloth and wiped the blood off his sword.

The young man raised his head and flashed a smile at Sun Ergou, almost as if he could sense Sun Ergou’s gaze.

As if he had seen a poisonous snake, Sun Ergou quickly retracted his gaze. His long-time enemy, Black Bear, had just died, but he felt not a hint of joy or excitement. On the contrary, he felt sad and mournful, like a person in distress.

He was completely awake now, and he knew full well that this young man was no fat sheep, but rather a King Yan from Hell who wanted his life. [1]

The only slight trace of hope that Sun Ergou had left was whether his subordinates were able to defeat Han Li’s giant bodyguard. If that were the case, then he would still have a chance at surviving, enabling him to negotiate with the young man and thus saving his insignificant little life.

But as soon as Sun Ergou saw the situation unfolding over there with the young man’s giant bodyguard, he became dumbstruck like a wooden chicken.

Lacking the strength to move even a single muscle, over twenty burly men were lying on the ground, bleeding profusely. The giant bodyguard glanced coldly in Sun Ergou’s direction.

Although a mantle was obscuring the giant’s features, Sun Ergou could still feel a bestial, bloody aura emanating from the large figure, causing his waxy yellow face to turn pale white.

Han Li observed the variation of expressions on Sun Ergou’s face, and from his movements, Han Li determined that this person did not know martial arts. Looking at Sun Ergou’s face of abject terror, Han Li disdained from dealing with Sun Ergou personally.

“Crooked Soul, kill him!” Han Li commanded.

“No! Please! I surrender, I’m willing to give up all my fortune to young master. I’m willing to work like a slave, and I know all the news floating around Jia Yuan City! I could be a good lapdog for young master…” Sun Ergou walked over, step by step, towards the large man, whom he viewed as a demon. Begging for mercy in a panic, he frightenedly limped across the ground.

“Ai!” Han Li originally wanted to ignore Sun Ergou’s words, but as soon as he heard that Sun Ergou knew all the news regarding Jia Yuan City, his heart was moved, he became filled with joy.

“Stay your hand for now.” He commanded to Crooked Soul, who was about to twist Sun Ergou’s neck. Han Li walked forward, stopping right in front of Sun Ergou.

“Are you very familiar with Jia Yuan City?” Han Li smiled as he asked, taking on the very appearance of kindness.

Just earlier, Sun Ergou had seen Han Li’s ruthless side, so how would he dare to be slow to reply? Immediately, his voice quavered as he shouted, “Very familiar, extremely familiar. I grew up here so I know everything that happens here as if it were on the back of my hand.”

Now it was as if he had grabbed onto a life-saving strand of grass; he couldn’t help but wish he could make himself sound more useful by a tenfold so that Han Li would feel that he was still of use.

Hearing Sun Ergou’s reply, Han Li touched his own nose in consideration before pulling a bottle out from his robes.

He took out a white, longan-sized [2] medicine from the bottle and handed it to Sun Ergou.

“Either you consume this or you die.” Han Li told him in straightforward manner.

The hand that Sun Ergou extended to take the medicine trembled violently. He hesitated while looking at the white pill in his hands before shifting his eyes to meet Han Li’s cold gaze. Coughing a few times, he had no choice but to ingest the pill.

“Good, I can trust you now.” Satisfied, Han Li nodded his head.

“The name of this pill is Rotten Heart Pill, and it was personally concocted by me. Every month, you need to consume the antidote, or else your inner organs will rot, causing you to die. I believe that you are an intelligent man, and you will serve me to the best of your abilities.” Han Li coldly and threateningly stated.

Sun Ergou was already prepared in his heart, but upon hearing the effects of the pill he had just consumed, he couldn’t help but to wail pitifully, appearing extremely depressed.

“Relax. As long as you help me settle what I need to do in the Jia Yuan City, I will neutralize the poison and return your freedom back to you. Based on your martial skills, I can’t really put you to good use anywhere else.” Han Li used both the stick and carrot, giving Sun Ergou the assurance that as long as he completed his task well, there was still some hope that he would be freed.

“Truly, young master?!” Sun Ergou’s expression slightly trembled upon hearing this news.

“Take these taels of silver with you and clean up this place. I don’t wish for this matter to spread, do you understand?” Han Li commanded as he tossed a bag of silver over to him.

After catching the bag, Sun Ergou weighed it in his hand. It was heavy, as if there were about 200 taels of silver inside.

An expression of joy appeared on his face. He realised that if he could work for such a man with riches and authority, it might not necessarily be a bad thing.

“Young master, please leave this to me. I will handle this well, without creating any trouble for you!” He laughed as he patted his chest proudly.

“Okay, I shall leave first to find an inn. Tomorrow morning, come look for me. Since you yourself claim to be the local head in Jia Yuan City, you should be able to find out which inn I will stay in.” Han Li commanded again, without a trace of politeness in his voice.

“Yes! Yes! Tomorrow morning, I will be there, waiting for young master’s commands!” At this stage, Sun Ergou could only be described as “eager” to become Han Li’s lackey.

Han Li smiled as he gestured to Crooked Soul, who picked up the baggage, and left the alley. After walking a distance, Han Li turned back and glanced at Sun Ergou, only to find him him obediently standing there at the same spot. Sun Ergou was using his eyes to respectfully send Han Li off, showing an expression of fear and loyalty.

“Interesting!” Han Li suddenly felt that this person was extremely interesting and intelligent. Perhaps he could really put him to good use in a sticky situation.

[1]. King Yan: the god of death and a ruler of one of Hell’s eighteen levels.

[Back]

[2]. A longan is a fruit belonging to the same family as the lychee

[Back]

Chapter 104: Information

“The gang I founded, the Fearsome Flood Dragon Association, possesses 64,000 common gang members. Core gang members include more than seven thousand people. It is also one of the three great overlords of the Lan Province. Its main branch is set up in Jia Yuan City, and its side branches are….

“Throughout my life, I married five women and witnessed the birth of two daughters. My apprentices….”

“First Wife Jin, she had a gentle disposition. She was the sole daughter of the Golden Lion Escort Company’s Head Escort Chief, Jin Can. She has already passed away, leaving behind her daughter, Mo Yuzhu.

[1]

“Second Wife Li was educated and well-balanced. She was the daughter of some rich household. Unfortunately, she did not have any children.

“Third Wife Liu has a bold disposition, but she is rather ambitious. She is the younger sister of Quling[2] City’s Lord and Wind Sect’s Sect Leader, Liu Feng. She bore no children. Pay great attention to her.

“Fourth Wife Yan is my younger female cousin from my mother’s side. She has a calm disposition, excels in scheming, and has great ingenuity. She raised one daughter, Mo Caihuan. Before I departed, I bestowed most of my authority over Fearsome Flood Dragon Association to her. You can trust her.

“Fifth Wife Wang is taciturn. She was infatuated with me and was previously First Wife Jin’s personal maid. She did not bear children, and she secretly grasped hidden strength. You can trust her unconditionally.

“Adopted Daughter Mo Feng Wu is the daughter of my confidant and subordinate. After her parents died, I received her as an adopted daughter. Before I left, she had just turned seven and was exceptionally intelligent.

“Yan Ge, Eldest Disciple. His aptitude is common. I have already passed on the cultivation methods for Demonic Silver Hand over to him. Before I left, he was twelve years old. His temperament is average.

“Zhao Kun, Second Disciple. I already passed on the Sleeping Dragon Arts to him. Before my departure, he was ten years old. His temperament is indiscernible.

“Ma Kongtian, my sworn little brother. He serves as a protector for the Fearsome Flood Dragon Association. His temperament…

…………

Han Li held in his hand a paper filled with handwriting: Doctor Mo’s will. Currently, he was inside Hui Yuan Inn’s top room, walking to and fro repeatedly as he remained lost in thought.

The will was written attentively. Not only did it clearly explain the powerhouse that Doctor Mo had established, the Fearsome Flood Dragon Association, but it also crudely described the temperament of his wives thoroughly. This caused Han Li’s heart to sink slightly.

What was mentioned in his will were matters from ten years ago. The present state of affairs were sure to have had undergone an absolutely earth-shaking change.

How should this be done? Should he contact Doctor Mo’s wives or steal the Yang Jaded Treasure and escape without a trace? These decisions required Han Li to fully understand the current state of affairs.

Thus, the local thug he subdued yesterday, Sun Ergou, was of great use to him. Han Li could probably acquire a lot of useful information from him.

After Han Li carefully read through the will, he put it away into his bosom. Then, lost in thought, he raised his head, walked to the bed, and sat down.

He spread his legs and raised his palms to the sky before setting them on his knees. Afterwards, he shut his eyes and began to inspect his body’s condition.

The thread of cold yin poison inside his dantian[3] had started spreading outward a month ago. It was originally just a trace of an indistinct shadow, but it had currently condensed into a black pea-sized sphere. In addition, it slowly beginning to grow in size.

According to Han Li’s estimates, he would have two months at most before this yin poison thoroughly broke out. When that time came, he feared that he would truly be hard-pressed to escape death.

Just as Han Li was worried sick as he secretly resolved himself to acquire the “Warm Yang Precious Jade”, someone knocked on his door.

“Come in!” Han Li coldly said, as he opened his eyes.

The room door softly opened, and Sun Ergou walked in with his head lowered. As soon as he saw Han Li, he acted with the greatest of courtesy, declaring respectfully, “Greetings, Young Master! Sun Ergou has come to hear Young Master’s assignments!”

“Not bad, you found me quite quickly. You truly do have some skill!” Han Li said in satisfaction. He then stood up from the bed, and then, with his hands behind his back, he walked in front of Sun Ergou.

“I am indebted by Young Master’s praise. If I could not perform such a small, trivial task, then for what reason would Young Master have spared my humble life?” Sun Ergou’s happy face showed a great loyalty.

When Sun Ergou had returned that day, it wasn’t as if he hadn’t thought of informing his superiors of the matter regarding Han Li and have experts come to take revenge. But when he thought of the “Rotten Heart Pill” that he had consumed, his courage thoroughly disappeared.

After a night of great consideration, he couldn’t think of any other options and was left with no choice but to obediently pay Han Li a visit. He only wished that when he provided his assistance in the future, he would be given the antidote to this frightening “Rotten Heart Pill”.

“First tell me your status! From your appearance that day, it would seem that you’re a small chief.” Han Li indifferently said.

“I am a dock overseer for the Western City district’s Fourth Level Gang. I have about 450 subordinates, and could be considered a minor gang leader.” Sun Ergou replied respectfully.

“Fourth Level Gang?” Han Li dully asked.

“That’s right. Fourth Level Gang is one of the 33 small gangs in the western part of Jia Yuan City. It has about a thousand gang members, but most of them are dock coolies.[4] The gang head is the ape, Shen Zhong Shan. He has three great protectors as subordinates.” Sun Ergou immediately gave the complete details discreetly. Although he had revealed information about his gang to an outsider, his face didn’t have the slightest amount of shame.

“That large dark skinned man I took care of yesterday, was he also part of the Fourth Level Gang?”

“He was not. That person was called Black Bear, and he was a gang leader of the Iron Fist Group, another one of the 33 gangs. We were not on good terms with one another.” Sun Ergou replied with a flattering smile.

“Even though this is just the western part of the city, there are already so many small gangs. Thus, in the entire Jia Yuan City, the total number must be quite large, right?” With his hands behind his back, Han Li unhurriedly returned to the front of the bed.

“Of course. In the entire Jia Yun City, there are more than forty small gangs with a thousand members or less. There are seven to eight medium-sized gangs with three to four thousand members. With regards to the large gangs that have over ten thousand members, there are only three.” Sun Ergou stood there, speaking with absolute honesty.

“Tell me about the state of affairs in the both the large and medium-sized gangs. You don’t need to tell me about the small gangs!” Han Li pulled up his sleeves and sat down on the bed. Afterwards, the calm Sun Ergou started talking.

[1]. When talking about his wives, Doctor Mo is listing the order in which he married them and their maiden clan name.

[Back]

[2]. TL: “Quling” means “crooked tomb”

[Back]

[3]. Dantian generally references to a place below your navel where essence and Qi gathers.

[Back]

[4]. Coolie: an unskilled native laborer.

[Back]

Chapter 106: Blue-Clothed Man

On Southern District’s busiest street, South Hill Street, there was a huge residence the size of several acres. The residence’s courtyard had a large black gate from which a hanging sign revealed two words: Mo Estate. Beneath the sign, eight large, imposing men were stationed evenly on both sides of the gate. Each of these formidable men held his head high and chest out with complete concentration. With just a glance, people would never dare to look down upon their well-trained and valiant appearances.

The three-story Fragrant Restaurant was just across the street from the Mo Estate. The popularity of this large restaurant resounded in the entire Jia Yuan City. In addition, its signature drink, Hundred Scents, was famous for being a great wine, and it attracted many famous customers who passed by.

It was currently time for the midday meal. As a result, the Fragrant Restaurant was packed with people. All the tables from the first floor to the third floor were packed with eating patrons.

On the road, those who were about to pass by restaurant would smell the strong aroma of food and drool with hunger, completely captivated by the smell.

On the second story, a youth sat next to the window, watching the street. There were quite a few tasty side dishes on his table, along with a bottle of the famous “Hundred Scents”. Behind the youth stood a large, intimidating man. This youth was none other than Han Li, who was scouting for information.

At this moment, Han Li gazed down at something from the window. He turned a small wine cup that was filled to the brim in his hand, but his food sat on the table, untouched. Overall, he seemed absent-minded and careless.

Han Li shot a tilted glance at the nearby Mo Estate before looking down to the streets below him. His face’s expression didn’t change in the slightest. Raising his head to drink the cup of wine, he continued to look outside mysteriously.

Han Li had already asked about Doctor Mo’s two biological daughters and his adopted daughter. They had all grown up to become as delicate as a flower, as refined as a precious jade, beautiful and charming. They were known as Jia Yuan City’s three great beauties. As a result, they were often referred to as the three prides of the Mo Estate.

Because of their beauty’s great fame, they have been wooed by far too many young masters and heroic elites to count.

Among these women was Mo Yuzhu, a peerless beauty. Amongst the three, she was the one who was the most pursued. Thus, the news of her betrothal roused a great ruckus and broke the hearts of the men who were trying to woo her. There were a few martial artists that had challenged this Young Master Wu one after another. Wu Jian Ming ended up defeating sixteen of these rivals of love in succession, thus consolidating his reputation as a peerless martial artist and causing him to be inseparable and closely intimate with Mo Yuzhu.

Han Li thought that this matter was truly somewhat amusing and ridiculous. Others didn’t know that this Young Master Wu had some sort of inside information. However, Han Li was aware of the entire situation.

Wu Jianming was sure to have been dispatched from Doctor Mo’s enemy school. It seemed that the Doctor Mo’s long absence had caused his enemies to grow suspicious; this Young Master Wu had probably arrived to scout out the situation. Han Li did not know by what means he had been able to obtain the trust of the Mo Estate, but the letter alone probably shouldn’t have been enough to easily convince Doctor Mo’s wives.

Han Li used his finger to lightly tap the table as he contemplated about the matter.

“Young Master, please sit here! The dishes you ordered should arrive at once.” The waiter wearing a short, white jacket hurriedly led a blue-clothed man, who was twenty-seven to twenty-eight years old, to the second floor. In addition, the waiter had the man sit at an empty table next to Han Li. He then hastily returned to the first floor to take care of the other customers.

This blue-clothed man was handsome. He had thick eyebrows, big eyes, and somewhat of a heroic air about him.

After he sat down, he took a quick glimpse around his surroundings and just happened to meet Han Li’s gaze.

Han Li felt a profound indescribable valiance from within the man’s gaze that made him feel as if his very being was being absorbed. After a moment of shock, Han Li quickly turned his head away as his complexion faintly changed.

This person was also greatly surprised. However, after giving Han Li a cold glance, he immediately turned his head, no longer paying any heed to Han Li.

Han Li’s complexion turned somewhat pale. Just a moment ago, a glimpse at that person had given him a feeling like that of having one’s guts seen from inside out, overwhelming him with great shock.

This was Han Li’s first time experiencing such a glance, the kind of glance that made him feel as if his entire being had been completely exposed.

After the blue-clothed man waited for his dishes to fill the table, he began to eat. Not only did he eat quite heartily, he also ate as if there were no one else there.

At this moment, the frustrated Han Li was somewhat restless and worried.

Although he currently didn’t use the Heaven’s Eye Technique to observe the man, he felt quite a large amount of spiritual energy faintly emitting from the man’s body, making Han Li stiff from awe. He clearly understood from this person’s magic power that the man’s cultivation no doubt was far deeper than his own.

Back when he looked at the cultivators Yu Zhitong and Monk Golden Light, he had only seen feeble, pathetic magic powers that completely lacked the fundamental essence of life. Upon his encounters with them, he had been able to easily get rid of them both. Thus, Han Li still didn’t understand a lot about cultivators. In his mind, cultivators were a mysterious existence. He truly didn’t know how how he should respond to another cultivator stronger than himself.

“Could I not treat this blue-clothed man like Monk Golden Light and unceremoniously eliminate him with my own hand?” Han Li’s mind could not help but think in the worst direction.

While Han Li’s thoughts were in turmoil and fear, the blue-clothed man had finished eating. He wiped his mouth with a hand towel, dropped a silver ingot on the table, and left like a breeze. From the beginning until the end, he never looked at Han Li again after their initial glance; it seemed that the man had completely forgotten about Han Li.

Han Li waited until after this person had completely left the restaurant before exhaling deeply and lying down on his chair, paralyzed. Although the time during which the blue-clothed man ate was short, Han Li felt as if an entire day had passed by. The stress placed upon his mind was far too great. He felt as as if he had just fought a battle of life and death.

At this moment, the blue-clothed person appeared at the corner of the street. A thirty-year old man wearing a yellow jacket was waiting there for him.

“Old Fourth, why have you come so late? We still have to meet up with Eldest Brother and the others!” The yellow-jacketed man had some discontent in his voice.

“Hehe! Second Eldest Brother, don’t be angry! It’s just that I haven’t had mortal food for several years. I just went to have a taste!” The blue-clothed person said with a joyful smile.

“You glutton! How many times do I have to say this? We Immortal cultivators should cleanse our heart of desires and abstain from gluttony, but you never listen! Your consumption will, at the very least, damage your nature greatly.” The yellow-jacketed man glared at the blue-clothed person and sourly lectured him.

“Hehe! I know, I know, you don’t have to tell me that again! Oh yeah, back at the restaurant, I saw another cultivator.” The blue-clothed person tried to change the topic, hastily mentioning his encounter with Han Li.

“Oh! Really? Was his magic power deep or shallow?” Sure enough, this had captured the yellow-jacketed man’s attention.

“His magic power was quite light. It seemed as if his cultivation base had just reached the seventh or eighth layer. He barely has the qualifications to participate in the Immortal Ascension Assembly.

“This truly does not make sense. With such shallow magic power, did he come to the Lan Province to exploit some sort of opportunity? Could it be that he truly believes that he will come across unexpected success and obtain the final victory at the great Immortal Ascension Assembly?” The blue-clothed man flung these words from his mouth.

“Is he young or old?”

“He looked to be seventeen to eighteen years old.”

“If that is the case, he definitely followed his elders here in order to increase his experience and broaden his horizons. I reckon that in the Immortal Ascension Assembly ten years from now, this talent would genuinely be able to participate.” The yellow-jacketed man said with a smile.

“I say! When you say it like that, his talent can be considered decent. If he comes back in ten years, he could reach my level.” The blue-clothed man said proudly.

“Stop boasting! Your cultivation base has merely reached the tenth layer. Every year the Immortal Ascension Assembly produces many cultivators at this level. Once you’ve trained to the eleventh or twelfth layer, then you will be given the qualifications to boast.” The yellow-jacketed man said while laughing cheerfully.

“Truly, if I hadn’t used the Foundation Establishment Pill, I could have trained to a level higher than the tenth layer, but then, what Immortal Ascension Assembly could I have participated in? I wouldn’t have been able to find a master.” The blue-clothed man pouted and murmured before following the yellow-jacketed man and leaving the area.

Chapter 107: Mo Yuzhu

Han Li naturally did not know about the conversation between the blue-clothed man and the yellow-jacketed man. He was still celebrating the fact that he had just escaped from a calamity. Although he was angered by the blue-clothed man’s disregard for him, Han Li was extremely clear about the disparity in their strengths. Now that he had “escaped”, he felt as though he had just escaped death, so Han Li became extremely relaxed.

After his encounter with the blue-clothed man, Han Li’s heart couldn’t calm down, so he could not recover his initially peaceful state of mind. Sighing, Han Li stood up and prepared to leave the inn.

At this moment, the sounds of horses galloping suddenly rang out in the large street outside of the inn. The sound was getting closer and closer as the horses galloped into the vicinity.

He was just about to stand up, but his attention was piqued. He sat back down and cast his gaze once again to the large street. According to the report by Sun Ergou, the sounds that the incoming horses were making was the sign that the Most Estate’s eldest daughter, Mo Yuzhu, was returning back to the city from her travels outside. Rumors had it that this precious lady from the Mo Estate didn’t enjoy doing what other girls her age did. Ever since she was young, she only showed interest in wielding the spear and becoming the leader of a gang. Thus, her elders organized an expert from the Fearsome Flood Dragon to teach her martial arts.

What was truly shocking was that this Miss Mo especially loved hunting, a sport that was supposed to be an activity exclusive to males. Every two to three days, Miss Mo would travel to the forest outside the city to hunt. This incited the various clans’ young masters, who wanted to woo her, to go hunting with her, chasing after eagles and hounds in hopes of obtaining her good will. Naturally, after Young Master Wu had arrived, he too joined in this activity.

After Han Li had heard the news, he was also curious about this eldest daughter from the Mo Estate. After all, a girl with such a character was rarely seen. He hoped that such a lady wouldn’t disappoint him.

Now, there were over ten horse riders galloping from the end of the street. The frontmost riders consisted of a man and a woman. The male had a pair of sword-shaped eyebrows, a bright gaze, a lanky figure, and the look of a handsome, heroic youth. The female was wearing a fiery red hunting suit, along with a purple-colored veil to cover her face, hiding her facial features.

In the blink of an eye, the group of hunters passed the front of the inn, past Han Li’s sight, and finally stopped at the gate of the Mo Estate.

The two burly guards who were originally standing there immediately greeted them. One of the guards, a man with a face full of pockmarks, respectfully greeted:

“Eldest Miss and Master Wu, both of you are back. How was today’s harvest?”

“Not too bad! Tang Er, lead the horse away and help me take care of this wild game.” The female wearing the hunting suit ordered. Before she dismounted her horse, she extended her hand to take off the veil that had been covering her face, revealing a face that could startle hearts and move souls.

“Roger that, Miss!” The one named Tang Er showed that he dared not to even gaze upon the enchanting visage of this female as he hurriedly took over the reins and led the horse away, walking towards a side gate.

Although the inn and the Mo Estate were a distance away, Han Li could still see about seventy to eighty percent of the girl’s features as he involuntarily drew in a huge breath. That shining snow-white skin, that dainty little nose, those black, sparkling eyes, and those ruby red lips were all capable of sinking fishes and causing geese to fall from the skies.

“This lady is none other than Mo Yuzhu! No wonder she’s capable of causing all the young masters in Jia Yuan City to go crazy for her. For such a supreme beauty, even toppling over empires wouldn’t be strange.” Han Li could not help but to think of her in such a way.

By this time, the other hunters behind the handsome youth had all dismounted. Servants came forth and led their horses away.

The youth smiled as he walked in front of Mo Yuzhu and whispered something to her, causing Miss Mo’s face to redden. She gently hammered the shoulder of the male youth before shyly glancing at him and eventually running through the gate. The youth laughed as he walked inside with a elegant demeanor.

“This person was Wu Jianming? He really does know how to coax a girl. In any case, his looks are still passable.” Han Li sourly stated in his heart. He knew that if they were to compete based on looks, there was no way for him to win against the handsome youth.

“It seems that Mo Yuzhu and this handsome young master have a deep relationship!” He furrowed his brows, feeling slightly pressured. It seemed to him that this matter would not be settled as easily as he had imagined.

“No matter what, I must obtain and secure the Precious Warm Yang Jade. After all, there is an extraordinary yin poison in my body that might explode earlier than the predicted date!” Han Li was deeply worried and anxious.

He contemplated about the Mo Estate again before summoning the waiter, settling his bill, and returning to the inn that he was staying at.

After he pondered long and hard, Han Li decided to use the most direct and effective method. He planned to infiltrate the estate in the middle of the night and visit Lady Yan, the wife of the Fearsome Flood Dragon Association’s former leader. He intended to use the items that Doctor Mo had left for him and expose that imposter in the Mo Estate. As for how he was going to get the precious jade, he could only wait and see, moving step by step.

Since he had already made up his mind, Han Li no longer concerned himself regarding the consequences of his decision. He shut his eyes and began to prepare himself mentally for his night-time activities.

However, Mo Yuzhu’s beautiful face kept surfacing in his mind during this span of time. No matter what he did, he wasn’t able to banish his thoughts about her.

“Did I fall in love with that girl?” Han Li asked himself, somewhat unnaturally.

He consoled himself, saying, “Such a ravishing beauty, it’s only normal that I would be attracted to her. I may not like her for certain.”

As someone who already made half a step onto the path of cultivation, although he had never had a relationship before, Han Li still tried his best to avoid matters such as love and courtship between the opposite s*x even though he had never had a relationship before.

About three in the morning, Han Li changed into a set of black clothes and sneaked out of the inn.

He lightly sped past the roof and easily evaded the patrol on the streets, arriving outside of the Mo Estate. After he checked out the, he smiled to himself, then transformed into smoke. As he drifted past the eyes of the guards, he entered into the backyard of the Mo Estate without alerting them or causing them to notice anything out of the ordinary.

Chapter 108: Entering the Mo Estate at Night

Behind the Mo Estate lay a garden, not small in size, in which many rare flowers and herbs were planted. The flowery fragrance that the garden emanated was still revitalizing even though it was night time. Han Li involuntarily breathed in deeply.

“Ai!” Han Li suddenly slightly exclaimed. Although the fragrance of the flowers was thick, he could still differentiate between the familiar smells of herbal medicine.

“Someone planted medicinal herbs in here.” Han Li lightly smiled. This familiar herbal scent caused him to feel extremely curious about the person who had planted the herbs. It appeared that someone within the Mo Estate had inherited Doctor Mo’s medicinal skills.

Han Li did not dare to hesitate any longer. He continued on the little path and walked towards the areas that were lit up.

Along the way, Han Li discovered that there were quite a few hidden sentries. He would not have detected the Mo Estate’s tight security if it weren’t for his heightened senses.

Since he had already discovered the hidden sentries, sneaking past them became an extremely easy task.

Han Li stopped in front of a small, two-story building.

He chose this spot because he could sense that security was much tighter in this particular location. There were about twenty to thirty people guarding this area.

This particular two-story building was well lit; he knew that there was probably someone of extreme importance who had yet to fall asleep, which coincidentally suited his purposes.

Making use of the dark night, he moved at a lightning-fast pace, his body blinking as he arrived at the bottom of the building. Using the strength in his legs, he easily jumped up onto the second story of the building. The whole process took but an instant. The surrounding sentries did not even notice that Han Li had already infiltrated the building.

Han Li kept his body close to the walls, causing his shadow to merge into the night, before pricking his ears, trying to use his sense of hearing to discern any movements in the building. Although Han Li could only hear a single female talking, he could discern that there was more than one person in this building.

“The branch from Chang Ping Town sent over 7,300 taels of silver

“The branch from Luo Gu Town sent over 5,800 taels of silver.”

“The branch from Lan Yue Town sent over 10,500 taels of silver.”

“Wu Ling Town……”

………

“This is all of the profits that we received last month from our association’s various branches. Overall, it’s about twenty-five percent less than the profits we gained in the same month of last year.”

The sound of a melodious female voice that was filled with vitality drifted into Han Li’s ears. The moment that he had heard it, he speculated that it belonged to a youthful female. She was somewhat unhappy, judging from the last words she had spoken.

“Mother, these branch managers are getting bolder and bolder; the tribute they offer is increasingly less as the months go by.” The youthful girl angrily stated.

“I am well aware!” Another low, attractive voice rang out.

“Could she be one of the three ladies of the Mo Clan?” Han Li was somewhat shocked at his good luck. It seemed that the other woman in the room was Doctor Mo’s wife.

“Every time you say that you’re aware about this, why don’t you offer some ideas on how to settle this? If this continues, then all of our branches will no longer put us in their eyes one day.” The youthful girl complained.

“I don’t have any good ideas right now. You must know that the branches are controlled by Fifth Mother. The others in the Mo Clan have no way to interfere!” The woman could only helplessly reply.

Afterwards, the exchange of words stopped, allowing silence to descend.

After several moments, the youthful girl’s voice rang out in an unwilling tone: “Mother, could it be that we allowed Fifth Mother to have sole control over the branches? After Uncle Ma and the others got into a dispute, their in-fighting pushed into branches into a position where they became the pillar of support for our Fearsome Flood Dragon Association. Mother, since you are the representative for the Flood Dragon Association, this power should instead be in your control.”

“What you said is correct. The year when your father left, he had passed the authority of the branches over to Fifth Mother, I don’t really have an excuse to interfere. And because Fifth Mother grants us a large portion of the monthly tribute, I don’t have the face to bring up the topic.” The woman replied.

“But the strength of our Fearsome Flood Dragon Association is actually extremely weak. If we don’t consolidate our strength, how can we ever rise again? Father is not thinking straight! He handed the reins of the association to you, but why did he also give Fifth Mother the authority over the branches?” The tone of her words was filled with resentment.against her father.

“Stop your nonsense! Your dad did this; naturally, he had a deeper meaning behind his actions. It’s not your place to criticize!” The woman berated the youthful girl.

“I understand. I acknowledge my mistake, alright? Seems like Mother is still deeply in love with Father!” The girl acted out of the ordinary and started laughing at her mother.

“This child……” The woman loved her daughter very much. Speechless, she could only laugh bitterly.

Han Li had already confirmed that the woman in the room was the Lady Yan he was looking for. In addition, the girl should be Mo Caihuan, the daughter of Lady Yan and Doctor Mo. He was fortunate for having found who he had been looking for in such a quick fashion.

Han Li extended his hands, touching the letter and the items left behind by Doctor Mo, and prepared to reveal himself to the two of them.

“Mother, that faker[1] was extremely irritating! Today he found me at the garden and actually tried to shamelessly curry favor with me. He intended to to sell me a few of his strong points, trying to appear as one who is skilled in both studies and martial arts. How disgusting!” The girl added the last bit coquettishly, startling Han Li and making him withdraw the foot that he had originally extended into the room.

“You better be more courteous to the one surnamed Wu. After all, he is your fiancee in name. Don’t let him notice anything that could make him suspicious!” Lady Yan’s tone grew heavy as she reminded the girl.

“Cough! This beautiful me is always surrounded by admirers, but you want me to act as though I’ve fallen head over heels with that man? That’s too difficult of a task for me! If it were up to me, I would have run him through with a sword long ago,” the girl replied.

“This matter is also out of our control. Although we know that the one surnamed Wu is a fake and have fully investigated his background, we have no choice but to sacrifice the reputation of your older sister by interacting with him to buy some more time. After all, our enemy is too strong; if they realize that they can’t win against us through wits, they might use force, making us lose any chance of victory!” Lady Yan’s voice was filled with tiredness, revealing traces of physical and mental exhaustion in her voice.

[1]. TL: use of ‘faker’ is to refer to the person with the fake identity, Wu Jianming

[Back]

Chapter 109: A Visit

“This man surnamed Wu is truly repulsive. Fabricating a letter and actually using Father’s name to marry Eldest Sister… truly infuriating!” Mo Caihuan uttered hatefully. Her despise for Wu Jianming was bone deep.

“Fortunately, it only mentioned your Eldest Sister. If the person that he had requested to marry was either you or Fengwu, I would truly not know what to do! With both of your temperaments, how could either of you possibly endure and falsely cope with this person?! The only one who has to suffer is Yuzhu. I don’t know when Lord Husband will return, and whether or not he will blame this mother”, Lady Yan softly told her daughter and sighed.

“Mother, how could Father blame you? Wasn’t it Eldest Sister who took the initiative to socialize with the man surnamed Wu?” Mo Caihuan immediately consoled Lady Yan.

“Foolish child, Yuzhu has no option but to do this for the sake of the Fearsome Flood Dragon Association and the Mo Estate! However, the most Mother could do was have your eldest sister interact with that fake. There is no way I can truly marry your eldest sister to him. If we cannot delay the wedding, then we will be forced to be hostile and capture him!” Lady Yan’s voice grew cold as she spoke this last sentence.

Once Lady Yan uttered these words, the room’s atmosphere returned to a state of calm. It was clear that this mother-daughter pair knew what hostility would entail.

“When will Father finally return?” Mo Caihuan faintly asked a moment later.

“When your father left, he had said that the latest that he could return would be five to six years from then, the earliest being two to three years,” Lady Yan sadly replied.

“However, it has been almost ten years. I can no longer clearly remember my father’s appearance!” Mo Caihuan slowly said.

“Be at ease! Your father happens to be an outstanding genius of his generation. With his hidden skills, there are no problems that he can’t overcome! He was definitely delayed over some important matter, and will soon return to the Mo Estate.” Although Lady Yan was speaking to her daughter, she was trying to comfort herself as well.

“Oh, that’s right, Second Sister Fengwu concocted a rejuvenating cosmetic elixir for me to give to you. Mother, why don’t you try it out? I heard its effects are quite good!” In order to break the room’s heavy atmosphere, the girl suddenly changed the subject and started chatting about another matter.

“This child…”

………

Following along with the mother-daughter pair’s mundane gossip, Han Li didn’t hear any other useful information.

Han Li discovered from their dialogue that Lady Yan’s relationship with Doctor Mo was quite intimate. It seemed that Han Li could trust her. After a moment of contemplation, Han Li felt that personally appearing and tolerating this fake Young Master Wu was a better alternative by far than allowing the possibility of something insidious occurring. Nevertheless, Han Li had to first secure the Precious Warm Yang Jade.

As he thought as such, Han Li fished out a dragon ring, one of Doctor Mo’s keepsakes, from his bosom. He then quietly walked towards the room window and threw the ring into the room through an opening in the paper window covers.

“Dang” The clear sound of the ring falling to the ground resounded from the room.

A moment later, Lady Yan’s voice, neither arrogant nor humble, came from inside the room.

“Who is this expert that honors my humble home with his presence? Lady Yan has not yet welcomed you. I hope you will forgive me!”

Han Li faintly smiled and refrained from replying. He heard the girl’s frightened voice.

“How strange! How did this ring come from? This ring seems very familiar… it’s just like the ring you wear, Mother!”

“Mother! Come look!” It was clear that Mo Caihuan had picked up the ring and handed the ring over to Lady Yan.

“Dragon ring!” Lady Yan cried out in alarm.

After Han Li had heard the other party recognize the keepsake, he lightly knocked twice on the door before saying in a clear voice, “Under Teacher Mo’s orders, Disciple Han Li has come to pay his respects to Martial Mother!”[1]

After those inside the room had heard Han Li’s words, there was an immediate and absolute silence! Han Li’s words had clearly left them in shock for a short while.

“Come in!” After a moment, Lady Yan’s voice invited him into the room.

It was at this moment that Han Li lightly opened the room door and stepped inside.

Upon entering the room, Han Li saw a beautiful, thirty year-old lady. Sitting behind her was a dainty girl around fifteen to sixteen years old. The girl and the beautiful woman shared a striking resemblance. With just a single glance, one could tell that they were close blood relatives.

At the moment, the beautiful, married Lady Yan fiddled with the dragon ring he had just thrown into the room. Han Li’s arrival had not elicited a change to her flat expression.

Mo Caihuan stood behind Lady Yan and blinked her jet-black eyes, curiously sizing Han Li up. The corner of her mouth rose and revealed a smile that was not a smile. From head to toe, she released a strange, almost supernatural smell.

After they had assessed Han Li, he walked forward and carried out a courtesy toward Lady Yan.

“Greetings to Teacher’s Fourth Wife!”

Lady Yan’s eyes blinked with a look of surprise. Although Han Li’s appearance was not astonishing, his action was quite unexpected.

However, she didn’t immediately respond to Han Li’s greeting; instead, she raised her left hand, revealing her own dragon ring.

Lady Yan gently brought together both rings. In front of their eyes, the two rings’ dragon designs fit together, without even the slightest gap.

“You are right, this keepsake is authentic! However, do you have Lord Husband’s written letter on you?” Lady Yan gently asked, now revealing a few traces of a smile.

As soon as Han Li heard this, he took out the letter that had been prepared long ago and handed it over to her with both hands without saying anything further.

Lady Yan, seeing Han Li act respectfully towards her, nodded her head in satisfaction as she accepted the letter. Then, she unfolded it and carefully read its contents.

Han Li withdrew to the side while calmly observing the expression on the face of his teacher’s wife. He thought about the change in her attitude towards him as a visiting disciple and a future son-in-law.

[1]. TL: “Martial Mother”- literally. ?? Teacher’s Wife.

[Back]

Chapter 111: Beautiful Woman

Han Li quietly used his Eternal Spring Arts to stabilize his mind before daring to even lift his head. His eyes skipped over the alluring woman and moved on to the last woman.

The last wife to enter appeared to be twenty-six to twenty-seven years old. Although she was a charming beauty, one look at her ice-cold face would stop anyone in his or her tracks. In addition, ever since she entered the room, her cold stare had been aimed straight at Han Li.

Lady Yan saw these people come in and stood from her seat, gently greeting them.

“Greetings Second Sister and Third Sister! Fifth Sister has also come!”

“Fourth Sister, you are too formal. We are all of the same family; there is no need to be so polite!” Without waiting for the woman in front to speak, the extremely bewitching young woman covered her almond mouth and laughed. That laugh contained an alluring charm, causing Han Li to experience a burst of desire and a shaken spirit. He was speechless without end.

“Little Sister doesn’t dare. Sisters, please take a seat.” Lady Yan slightly smiled and offered her own chair to the wife in the front. She did not sit until after the wife sat.

The one called “Fifth Sister” was an elegant and refined woman. She silently sat across from Lady Yan.

After the married women entered, Mo Caihuan knowingly closed the door and moved behind her mother. Her bright full moon eyes were spinning randomly across the room. It was unknown what exactly she was thinking.

“This youngster is the one that delivered the message?” The woman of about thirty years of age looked at Han Li and faintly asked.

“That’s right. According to the letter he delivered, this is Lord Husband’s successor.” Lady Yan easily replied. Soon after, she said respectfully to Han Li, “This is your Second Martial Mother.[1] Are you not going to pay your respects?”

“I pay my respects to Second Martial Mother!” Sharp-witted, Han Li stepped forward and formally bowed to the married woman.

“Stand up! Since this is Lord Husband’s favored disciple, there is no need to be overly polite.” The married woman said with a smiling expression.

“This is your Third Martial Mother and Fifth Martial Mother.” Lady Yan pointed to the abnormally gorgeous young woman and the elegant and refined woman, introducing them one by one to Han Li.

“Greetings to Third Martial Mother and Fifth Martial Mother!” Han Li saw the young married women to be no more than a few years older than him. After a second of hesitation, he also bowed courteously.

Han Li looked at Lady Yan with a face of doubt. She faintly smiled and said with a warm voice, “Your Third Martial Mother stopped the aging of her face with a technique. Although she looks to only be of about twenty years, she is about the same age as your Second Martial Mother.”

After Han Li heard this, he inwardly nodded his head, satisfied that his own guess hadn’t been too far off. This alluringly beautiful young woman naturally practiced an unusual secret art, otherwise how else could she have captivated him with her mere appearance and rendered unable to control himself.

“Second Sister, this is Lord Husband’s hand-written letter, please look over it!” Lady Yan handed Han Li’s letter to Second Wife Lady Li. After Lady Li finished reading it, she passed the letter to the other two wives.

Once the elegant and refined young woman, the last wife to read the letter, finished looking over the it, the several wives were stunned into completely silence.

Even the seemingly frivolous and gorgeous young wife, Lady Liu, had a solemn expression on her face. Completely lacking the boldness and alluring charm she possessed a moment ago, Lady Liu was instead showing an unexpected composure.

When Han Li saw the appearance of Doctor Mo’s several wives, he could not help but grow uneasy. He did not know what significant information the letter had revealed to cause these wives to be so serious.

However, Han Li’s calm expression hadn’t changed since he first entered the room, making the wives think that he was reliable and had the bearing of a general.

“Han Li! Your Teacher’s letter has shocked us Martial Mothers far too greatly, so we’ll need to properly talk this over. You’ve come here from far away, surely you must be tired. You should spend the night here at the Mo Estate. Tomorrow, we will call you for questioning.” Since Lady Yan had held the power of the Fearsome Flood Dragon Association in her hand for several years, each and every one of her movements possessed an unspeakable dignity. Ultimately, she was the first to speak and instruct Han Li.

“This junior follows your orders!” Han Li replied with the complete obedience.

The other wives did not block Lady Yan; it seemed they also agreed to have this outsider Han Li withdraw so that they could discuss a few sensitive matters.

“Huan’er! Bring your father’s disciple Han to the rear residence and find him a clean room for him to have a proper rest,” Lady Yan ordered Mo Caihuan.

“Xi! I got it! Senior Disciple Han Li, follow me!” Mo Caihuan blinked her eyes several times, slightly wrinkled her nose, and started to be somewhat unwilling. However, she immediately thought better of it and agreed with a smile across her face.

“You are forbidden from bothering your Senior Disciple! Otherwise you will be punished by clan rules!” Lady Yan knew the thoughts of her good for nothing daughter like the back of her hand, thus giving her a verbal warning in advance.

“Alright, I understand!” Pouting her face, the young girl unwillingly agreed.

Han Li was speechless! If Lady Yan hadn’t said anything, would this dainty young woman have played some tricks on him?

Han Li looked at Mo Caihuan with a peculiar gaze, and for the first time, he no longer saw this girl as adorable.

As a result of her mother’s interference, Mo Caihuan dispiritedly walked out the door.Han Li followed behind with an unmoving expression.

Waiting several moments after Han Li had left the room, Lady Yan broke the silence in the room with her solemn voice.

“Fifth Sister, I’ll have to inconvenience you to take a look around and see whether or not that boy has truly left or if he has secretly returned and is hiding somewhere. We’re still not sure!”

After the elegant, refined Lady Wang heard this, she wordless left the room, and disappeared into the dark.

“Fourth sister, you overestimated that boy. How could he possibly be so skilled?” A light flashed in Third Wife’s pretty eyes.

“Third Sister, you’ve truly forgotten about one thing. A disciple of our Lord Husband can’t possibly be ordinary.”

“I believe our Mo Estate is quite heavily guarded. What’s more, this building is an important location where I handle the association’s affairs. Not far from here, there are twenty to thirty hidden sentries densely standing guard. But even with all of our defenses, he was still able to stealthily infiltrate his place without drawing my or Caihuan’s attention. Do you think that this is something an ordinary expert can achieve?” Lady Yan quietly said.

[1]. TL Note: “Martial Mother”- Literally ?? Teacher’s Wife. Instead of ‘Second Martial Mother’ it could be ‘Teacher’s Second Wife’ and so on.

[Back]

Chapter 115: A Startling Change

Just as they reached the second floor, before Yan Ge could knock on the door, Lady Yan’s voice came from within the room.

“Is it Han Li and Yan Ge?”

“That is right, Fourth Martial Mother!” Yan Ge hastily stopped and respectfully replied.

“Yan Ge, return first. Just Han Li entering alone will do.” Lady Yan’s faint voice could be heard from within. That distinct, cold voice could not help but touch Han Li’s heart.

“As you wish.” Yan Ge was clearly very respectful of Lady Yan, and he followed her command without the slightest hesitation. After he smiled to Han Li, he quietly descended from the second floor. Only Han Li remained upstairs, waiting outside the room.

Han Li coldly looked at the room door, but instead of immediately entering, he released his spiritual sense and scoped out the situation inside the room. He didn’t wish to go in alone, only to be ambushed and killed by a room of hidden soldiers, so it was better to be a bit careful!

It was very quiet in the room, and the number of people inside wasn’t large. Han Li could only hear the breathing and heartbeats of Lady Yan and a few others. It appeared that there wasn’t anyone that shouldn’t be there. This greatly relieved Han Li.

Thus, he stepped forward and lightly knocked on the door twice. He then opened the room door, planning to take a quick look before entering. However, what he saw in the room greatly changed Han Li’s complexion. His step had stiffly halted mid air.

The room was the same as the night before; the chairs, desks, and decorations were all exactly the same. The only thing different were the beautiful women’s style of dress. Lady Yan and the other beautiful wives were all wearing white silk mourning clothes from head to toe. They all sat on chairs and unwaveringly gazed at Han Li with cool eyes.

Han Li’s complexion turned somewhat pale. However he was not scared but rather annoyed with the deceased Doctor Mo.

It was very clear why Doctor Mo, that old fox, had forced him to travel such a great distance. It seemed that he had guessed correctly: that letter had contained a hidden message that gave the tigresses news of Doctor Mo’s death. It was as if they were waiting for Doctor Mo’s murderer to visit them voluntarily!

Han Li took a deep breath and returned his complexion to normal. He then entered the room in large strides; without a trace of politeness, he looked for a chair and arrogantly sat across from the wives. After seeing them not say a single word, he planned to observe how these women would deal with him in the end.

It was clear Han Li’s completely unrestrained action was intended to tear away at their faces. However, largely against his expectation, he had thrown them into confusion. each of their expressions having nothing in common.

Second Wife Li’s expression turned green. It was clear this Han Li, who had so clearly said “Martial Mother” yesterday, was now daring to brazenly act as if he were meeting with those of the same generation.[1] This Second Wife was born of a scholarly family and paid great attention to generational separation. Now that she had come across this chap who was unfilial towards his master, how could she not tremble with anger?

Third Wife Liu differed greatly from Lady Li. Not only did she refrain from getting angry, she also looked toward Han Li with a very interested expression. However, because of her astonishing glamor, Han Li didn’t dare to look at her directly, and had simply looked at her with a sweeping gaze.

Lady Yan and the cool, elegant Lady Wang were about the same. They wordlessly looked at Han Li with gazes brimming with a freezing chilliness.

“Your courage is awfully great, my Lord Husband’s last disciple!” After the time it took to make a cup of tea, Lady Yan eventually opened her mouth, her words containing a mocking intention. Everyone could clearly hear her ridicule.

“Martial Mothers, whatever you wish to know or wish to say, please say them directly. I don’t wish to hear nonsense or unnecessary words!” Han Li said with a blank face.

Han Li had clearly understood; if a wife were to bicker about how terrible she felt, and then the other wives would engage in a verbal duel. Rather than expand a great deal of effort to resolve this, he felt that he may as well get straight to the core problem. This was what he believed.

Since there were no saber lights or sword shadows belonging to hidden experts inside the room, Han Li speculated that the wives currently had no plans to dispose of him. It seemed they either had misgivings or had demands for him. Since it was like this, there was no need to be too polite. In any case, Doctor Mo’’s death was an invitation for disaster; he had nothing to be ashamed of.

“You….” Although Lady Yan had much knowledge about all sorts of battles between men, the rupturing tone of Han Li’s words nearly made her speechless.

“Fine, I will ask then! Was my Lord Husband killed by your traitorous hands!?” Second Wife could not help but want to spit fire from her elegant eyes. Her scholarly air had completely vanished, leaving behind only a face of resentment.

“Second Sister!” Lady Yan wrinkled her brow and softly called her as if to prevent the Second Wife’s questions from immediately causing both parties to fall into disagreement.

‘This Lady Li is actually quite frank to directly bring the most crucial question to the table.’ Han Li inwardly sneered, thinking of this.

“It could be said that I killed him, but it could be also said that he killed himself!” Han Li said indifferently.

This sentence caused the wives sitting across from him to be shocked. They believed that Han Li would either readily deny it or simply brazenly admit it. What were they supposed to do if they could not make sense of the answer?

Second Wife Li stared blankly for a moment, but she immediately became agitated. She clearly believed that Han Li was playing with them.

“What is this nonsense? It was clearly you who harmed him.” Lady Li tremblingly retorted.

“How are you certain that I killed him? Did you see it with your own two eyes?” Han Li asked, no longer polite. He clearly understood that Doctor Mo had written that he was murdered in the letter. Naturally, they weren’t completely certain whether or not he had died by Han Li’s hand. Han Li guessed that the letter, which Doctor Mo had set aside for these wives, contained nothing but a few speculative words. As a result, Han Li could completely refute these misgivings.

“Since you’ve said this, tell us women how our Lord Husband was murdered once through. If you were truly unrelated, we won’t deliberately treat you unjustly.” The cool, elegant Fifth Wife Wang, who had been silent all along, finally spoke.

[1]. TL: ?????? separation of the young and old generations- respect your granny, kids

[Back]

Chapter 117: Reconciliation

When these women heard Han Li’s words, their complexion rapidly changed from white to red, slightly increasing their beauty.

Lady Yan was the first to calm down. She lightly straightened the jade pin in her hair bun and once again said calmly, “Even if your esteemed self is a cultivator and does not fear this bewitching scent, are you not worried about the Yin poison in your body?” Nevertheless, she used her last trump card.

The moment Han Li heard what she said, his smiling face immediately turned cold. Sure enough, Doctor Mo gave the only weapon that could be used to blackmail him to these women.

“That’s right, I have the cold poison in my body. But before this poison flares up, I don’t mind turning this entire residence upside down and utterly slaughtering everyone!” Han Li spoke in a flat tone, but the women clearly heard the threat within his words.

Lady Yan was silent for a while and did not open her mouth to speak. The rest of them also did not say anything. It seemed that when it came to life and death matters, the one making decisions in Mo Residence was still Fourth Wife Yan.

“Since the both of us have scruples and we are not willing to let both sides suffer, let’s have a good talk.” Lady Yan said cool-headedly after that moment of silence.

“Of course. I also don’t plan on dying so uselessly at such a young age!” Concerning his own life, Han Li did not put up any airs. He gladly agreed to her suggestion.

Hence, he went back and sat in front of Lady Yan.

“However, before we start discussing, I, your servant, would like your esteemed self to repeat how my Lord Husband got murdered. After all, we were once husband and wife. We would only be reassured if we knew the real cause of his death. But be at ease, even if Lord Husband died by your hands, we would not have any ulterior motives. After all we are orphans and widows, we cannot go looking for trouble and personally seek the road to death.” Lady Yan’s last sentence was spoken so desolately, making it seem as if Han Li was the kind of evil tyrant who bullied women and children.

One look at Lady Yan’s face and Han Li can’t help but have a headache. Even though he knew Lady Yan was just acting, when he saw her miserable state, he felt his heart soften a little.

Wasn’t it just telling them how Doctor Mo was murdered? There was nothing to cover up in this matter. After all, Han Li acknowledged that Doctor Mo’s death was not his fault. Instead it was Doctor Mo and Yu Zhitong who should be blamed for courting disaster.

“Alright, I can describe Teacher Mo’s death in detail. But after you all have listened and still insist on taking revenge on me, I will oblige you at anytime!” Han Li agreed to their suggestion after pondering for a while.

“Many thanks to Young Master!” When Lady Yan heard that Han Li was willing to speak the truth, her face immediately opened up and revealed a delighted look.

“This was what happened. I was deceived by Doctor Mo,after practising Eternal Spring Arts for four years, only then did I discover…”

Han Li patiently told them how he was cheated, poisoned by Doctor Mo and forced to practice the Eternal Spring Arts.

He explained that Doctor Mo had wanted to occupy his flesh body by entering his body and consuming his fundamental essence. Naturally, Yu Zhitong had then appeared and narrated the entirety of his schemes. Han Li finally discovered about his body’s Yin poison and had no choice but to come to the Lan Province and detoxify himself with the Precious Warm Yang Jade. He narrated the events the way they truly happened. Han Li wanted these wives to know that in the occurrence of Doctor Mo’s death, Han Li was the true victim. He hadn’t slighted the Mo Estate in the least.

After Lady Yan and the other wives finished hearing Han Li’s heart-shaking tale tale, they couldn’t help but look at one another.

If Han Li’s words were true, then their Lord Husband’s death was not truly Han Li’s fault. In addition, hearing the methods that Doctor Mo had used and his shrewdness, they greatly matched the long-acquired impression they had of their dead husband. Furthermore, the bits of information that the hidden letter revealed didn’t contradict his story in the slightest. They estimated that his story should more or less be true.

“If your esteemed self had spoken the complete truth, then our Lord Husband’s death truly was not yours to blame. This was rather the fault of Yu Zhitong’s ruse; otherwise how else would our Lord Husband have died?” Lady Yan lightly sighed. Her words made Han Li raise an eyebrow.

‘This Lady Yan is far too favorable toward her own Lord Husband. With a few words, she easily pushed the entirety of Doctor Mo’s wrongdoings onto the deceased Yu Zhitong, cleaning Doctor Mo of the blame entirely, as if he were also a victim.’ Han Li stared at Lady Yan with widened eyes. Although his mouth did not say anything, his expression showed a strange emotion and made his meaning completely clear.

Lady Yan, under Han Li’s attentive gaze, did not blush or jump. She only turned a blind eye.

Han Li inwardly bitterly smiled. This woman’s face was quite thick, not one bit thinner than a man’s! He could not help but turn his head to look at the expressions of the other wives.

Third Wife Liu still had a smiling, cheery appearance and didn’t have the slightest change. When she saw Han Li looking over, she gave him several flirtatious glances, causing Han Li to remain silent.

When Second Wife Li saw Han Li looking at her, she looked ill at ease and faintly lowered her head. She certainly was worthy of being called a girl from a wealthy family, as well as educated and well balanced. It was clear she was somewhat ashamed of Lady Yan’s words from a moment ago.

As for Fifth Wife Wang, although this cool, elegant young woman was expressionless, she was entirely focused on tangling her fingers together, exposing an abnormality of her heart. As for her attitude, Han Li did not know.

“However, according to Young Master’s words just now, we have no deep animosity or hate toward one another. In that case, it would be best to conduct peace talks.” Lady Yan opened her almond lips and faintly said this.

When Han Li heard Lady Yan’s words, he turned his head and faintly stated, “What is there to discuss? Give me the Precious Warm Yang Jade, and I will turn around and leave, certain to no longer disturb the Mo Estate!”

“That is out of the question!” Lady Yan faintly smiled and immediately gave a flat decline.

“Why is it unacceptable?” Han Li said, unagitated.

“Yesterday, Young Master was outside this servant’s room and should have heard much of the vile situation the Mo Estate is in! It should be quite clear to you, sir, that without external assistance, our Mo Estate will be completely exterminated. It is only a matter of time. If it is like this, then it would better to have Young Master cleanly kill us sisters instead and have death end all troubles!” Lady Yan pitifully lamented with red eyes.

When Han Li heard this, he bafflingly stared at Lady Yan without speaking, directly looking at Lady Yan’s scarlet cheeks. However, she stubbornly continued to refuse to meet Han Li’s gaze.

Han Li let out a long sigh. He now knew where Mo Caihuan, that little demoness, learned her clever schemes; it was clearly from imitating this older demoness.

Chapter 118: Choose One

“With all this said and done, what do you all think? Be honest, I don’t want to have to beat around the bush again!” Han Li coldly said. It seemed he wasn’t influenced by Lady Yan’s act in the slightest.

Lady Yan wrinkled her brow. The youth in her presence was far more difficult than she had anticipated. Neither hard nor soft methods were effective; rather, she had no way of knowing how to deal with him.

“Could it be that you truly want us to immediately hand over our last resort and reveal our affairs to the enemy?” Lady Yan was somewhat unresigned. With the many years of handling the Fearsome Flood Dragon Association’s power, she clearly understood when to be a bit lenient and when to immediately put one entire hand on the table!

She turned her head to look at Fifth Wife Wang. Within these sisters, only Lady Wang was able to oppose her decisions. Therefore, she looked at her to see whether or not Lady Wang had a proposal.

“The matter of discussion with this person, I will leave to Fourth Sister, with whom I have no objections whatsoever!” Lady Wang saw the meaning in Lady Yan’s gaze and said, as cold as ice.

When Lady Yan heard this, she was inwardly elated and had somewhat calmed her heart.

“Very well. Since Sir does not want to beat around the bush, then we sisters will get right to the point and directly tell you the conditions.” As these words left Lady Yan’s mouth, she completely regained her bearings as the leader of one of Jia Yuan City’s three major gangs. The feeling of that delicate, powerless young married woman from before was completely obliterated. Her body dispersed the prestige of a leader.

“Good. From the beginning, I wanted to engage in talks as equals!” Han Li faintly smiled.

“So long as you exterminate the Fearsome Flood Dragon Association’s sworn enemies, the Rainbow Sect and The Hegemon’s Villa, the Mo Estate will no longer trouble you in the future, and we will also immediately offer you the Precious Warm Yang Jade. Furthermore, we will let you choose one of our daughters, whomever you fancy, as your wife.”

“However, if you’re unyielding in your plan rob the precious jade from us, or perhaps threaten us sisters, then your esteemed self will have been mistaken. I have already handed over the precious jade to my trusted confidant; if there is the slightest sign of trouble, then it will immediately be destroyed, ending us in mutual destruction.” Lady Yan said with an imposing expression.

“Lady Yan, are you not afraid of the wind cutting your tongue!? Have me, this one person, exterminate the Rainbow Sect and the Hegemon’s Villa? You must be truly absurd for thinking of this!” Han Li seemed to have already anticipated Lady Yan’s threat and wasn’t alarmed at all.

He had already known that the Precious Warm Yang Jade could not be acquired by acting rashly. Aside from their threats, he still didn’t know how many secret recruits they harbored, and thus capturing the other party and interrogating the whereabouts of the precious jade would simply end in failure. It would be best to make the other party willingly give it to him.

“Young Master Han, are you not a cultivator? How could these people of Jiang Hu be a match against your distinguished self? In addition, we don’t want your to kill the gang in its entirety. Causing a few of their main leaders to disappear would be enough.” This time, the gorgeous young Third Wife, after giving Han Li a soul-shaking, enchanting smile, said this with her graceful voice.

“What about being a cultivator? I don’t know of other cultivators, but I do know of my own abilities with clear certainty. You can’t just foolishly send one person to confront a large gang of several thousand members. Do you all truly believe that cultivators can outrageously murder ordinary people without fear of repercussion?”

Han Li coldly glanced at Third Wife. The aweing chilliness froze her smiling expression. Under the effects of the Eternal Spring Arts and a vigilant mind, he returned the gaze of her bewitching charming technique. How could it possibly affect him!?

“Why? Does Young Master mean that there are limitations to what cultivators can do to ordinary people?” Lady Yan asked, somewhat surprised by this revelation.

“I am not very certain of the specific details. After all, I haven’t been a cultivator for long, so I wasn’t truly in contact with these rules.” Han Li dully said. Then he looked at Lady Yan, who looked as if she wanted to say something, and waved his hand, preventing her from talking. He continued coldly, “However, if your brains aren’t lacking, it should be clear that cultivators can’t act against mortals as they desire. After all, your so-called Lan Province’s three great hegemons and the three great gangs of Jia Yuan City still exist. They could have fallen to the schemes of unrighteous cultivators countless times. Perhaps even beautiful women like yourselves would have already become their playthings.”

Han Li final sentence was completely blunt, turning the wives’ complexions across from him to become scarlet and their eyes to show a bit of alarm.

“But this is merely Young Master’s guess. It’s not at all certain to be true!” Lady Han was still somewhat unwilling, still attempting to persuade Han Li.

“So long as there is the possibility, this person will not perform actions that would bring destruction upon himself.” Han Li fundamentally did not give Lady Yan’s fantasies the slightest leeway, and he said this without a trace of politeness.

“Don’t tell me that your venerable self plans to take our daughters’ dowry with a sleight of hand and leave us with nothing?” Lady Yan’s complexion was somewhat unsightly. She said the word ‘dowry’ with an especially heavy emphasis.

Hearing her say this, although Han Li’s expression did not change, his heart could not help but be somewhat depressed.

“The Yin poison within me was originally given to me by your Lord Husband. Right now, I won’t trouble you even if I am cured. What is there to think about?” Han Li thought somewhat hatefully.

However, Han Li knew if he were to say these words at this moment, these wives would not take it well and certainly wouldn’t give him the Precious Warm Yang Jade.

As a result, Han Li gave in and muttered to himself. Then he raised his hand, cleared his throat, and said with a clear voice, “I will give you two choices. Choose whichever you fancy.”

“One is to have your Mo Estate immediately pack your baggage and prepare to travel far from the Lan Province. Find a place where the power of your enemy clans cannot reach you and live as a common wealthy household. You would live the rest of your lives peacefully and completely separate yourselves from the fights between Jiang Hu’s factions. This entire journey will be safe, I completely guarantee it; any forces that your enemies send to pursue you will unable to be harm you.”

Han Li stopped there and looked at the change in the wives’ expressions.

Apart from a slight change from Second Wife Li, Lady Yan and Third Wife Liu were completely silent. It was clear what they thought of the proposal. Han Li didn’t feel the need to look at Fifth Wife Wang since it would be impossible to make out anything useful from her icy appearance.

Han Li looked at this situation and inwardly sneered several times. Lady Yan and Lady Liu were rather ambitious people. It was impossible for them to want to give up the power of the Fearsome Flood Dragon Association and live as rural village women. When he had raised this proposal, he already understood this clearly.

“And the other choice?” Third Wife Liu noticed that Han Li stopped and could not but question him.

“There is one other choice…”

Han Li left his chair and stood. He looked up to the room before slowly telling the wives the other choice.

Chapter 120: Scheming to Seize a Gang

“He did not mention the time, but from the way he spoke, it appears that it’s going to be not too long from now. As for the meeting place, it seems like it was not mentioned.” Sun Ergou said as he scratched his head, somewhat embarrassed.

Han Li frowned. Apparently, the information that Sun Ergou possessed was not one hundred percent accurate. There were definitely some aspects that were overlooked.

Han Li bowed his head and pondered for a while. Suddenly, he had an epiphany and thought of a brilliant idea.

He cautiously gave Sun Ergou a once-over, then abruptly smiled and said, “Sun Ergou, I’m very pleased with the way you handle affairs recently, especially the major contribution you’ve made with the latest information. As a result, I am prepared to reward you heavily!”

When Sun Ergou heard this, he was so elated that his face brightened up subconsciously.

Sun Ergou never would have thought that a few pieces of information would merit the appreciation of this esteemed Young Master and lead to a reward. It seemed that handling affairs for this person was truly refreshing. Although he didn’t know why Han Li would reward him so handsomely, Han Li wouldn’t give him a large amount of gold and silver treasure, would he?

Sun Ergou couldn’t help but let his imagination run wild.

“Do you have any interest in becoming the Commander of the Fourth Level Gang?” Han Li’s question was so earth-shattering that Sun Ergou’s surprised face changed so drastically, and he nearly jumped out of his skin.

“Young Master must be joking and teasing this servant! This servant has little ability and character, how could I qualify to be a Commander?!” Sun Ergou muttered sullenly.

“Why not? With me supporting you from behind, even a small group like Fourth Level Gang would be easy to obtain! Or are you willing to just be a minor gang leader and take care of the harbor for the rest of your life?” Han Li said cajolingly as he laughed softly.

When Sun Ergou heard this, many expressions crossed his face. There was surprise, fear and mostly excitement.

As a man, who would not imagine himself being surrounded by beauties one day? Having all the authority in his hands and being able to control someone’s life or death…what a marvelous idea!

Buried at the bottom of his heart, Sun Ergou’s innermost ambition was lightly ignited by Han Li’s few words. But Sun Ergou still had a few qualms and thus did not immediately agree with Han Li.

“The martial arts of our Commander and the three great Protectors is certainly not weak. Can Young Master be certain that he can subdue them?” Sun Ergou asked tentatively in a low voice.

“Subdue them? Haha, what’s the use of that? Just kill them all!” Han Li said coldly as he regarded them with little importance.

Sun Ergou couldn’t help but to shudder when he heard this. This Young Master’s killing intent was truly too great! If he did not agree, Sun Ergou was afraid that he might be dealt with immediately.

“Since Young Master speaks highly of this servant, this servant’s life is bound to Young Master. I will listen to and obey your every command.” Under Han Li’s coercion and persuasion, Sun Ergou was finally willing to take some risks.

“Good, this is how it should be!” Han Li nodded his head in satisfaction.

“Give me your Commander’s most recent movements.” Han Li asked willfully.

“There is one that is noteworthy. Recently, he has been going to the Eastern City’s most popular brothel, the Clear River Brothel, every afternoon. He has been entranced by the leading girl, Xiao Jinzhi. However, the three great Protectors would also accompany him, so I’m afraid it might be a bit hard to deal with. Why not wait for a few more days and find a better opportunity?” Since Sun Ergou had already agreed with Han Li, he would immediately do everything he could for sake of his life and glory.

“No need. Since we already know the time and place, taking their small lives will be very easy.” Han Li mentioned causally.

“But once they die, you’re afraid you won’t have the capability to take over Fourth Level Gang, correct?”

“Yes. Within the gang, this servant is only a minor leader. There are many other who have higher ranks and better qualifications than me” Sun Ergou said shamefully.

“Don’t worry, if I said I’d make you the Commander of the Fourth Level Gang, you’ll definitely be the Commander. I will temporarily dispatch Crooked Soul to watch over you. He can get rid of all those that rebel against you and be your personal guard for the time being.” Han Li declared confidently.

Afterwards, Han Li rushed to the room next door and knocked calmly three times. A short moment later, Crooked Soul appeared in front of them.

“Keep this close to you and conceal it well. As long as you have this object on you, Crooked Soul will obey all your orders. He will get rid of your enemies and help you ascend to the position of Commander.”

Han Li took out the Soul Luring watch from his bosom. He caressed it softly for a while, then handed it over to Sun Ergou.

Although the person holding Soul Luring Watch was not the master of Crooked Soul, he could still command Crooked Soul. This was another method of control on Crooked Soul that Doctor Mo taught Han Li. Furthermore, if the former owner dripped his blood essence onto the Soul Luring Watch, other people would not be able to tamper with it. Hence, Han Li was not afraid that Sun Ergou might have evil plans or other intentions.

Sun Ergou had personally seen Crooked Soul’s display of his mighty power, so he was especially surprised to receive the watch, increasing his courage drastically.

“Many thanks to Young Master’s great kindness. This servant will definitely repay this favor with my life!” But Sun Ergou was very clever. He knew that despite being the Commander of the Fourth Level Gang, he was actually just this Young Master’s puppet. Thus, whenever there was an opportunity, he would fervently express his loyalty.

“Head back and prepare first then! Once that Commander is dead, you should take advantage of the confusion and assume control of Fourth Level Gang. But you must remember this: send me the fellow who saw the Immortal couple. I want him unharmed as I have things to ask him. Did you get that?” Han Li’s last sentences were very strict, clearly attaching great importance to this task.

“Please be at ease, Young Master. This servant will definitely send him to you in one piece. I will absolutely not disappoint Young Master!” Sun Ergou immediately patted his chest and vowed with devotion written on his face.

“As long as you understand, then that’s good. Bring Crooked Soul along with you then. The next time you see me, you will already be the Commander!” Han Li told him without batting an eye.

“This servant will retire now!” Sun Ergou noted Han Li’s notice to leave and tactfully retreated out of the house with great speed. Crooked Soul followed closely behind.

The moment Sun Ergou left the house, Han Li stood up. Within the house, Han Li turned in a semicircle and suddenly let out a prolonged mellow whistle. Then, from the outside, the Cloud-Winged Bird dived in and landed on Han Li’s shoulder.

Han Li extracted a bottle from his bosom and poured out the Cloud-Winged Bird’s favorite Yellow Chestnut Pill, which he gently fed to the bird. Then he softly said, “Little fellow, catch up with the person who just left the house. If he leaves the city walls to escape, immediately return and tell me.”

When the Cloud-Winged Bird finished listening to Han Li’s words, it chirped intelligently and proceeded to fly out of the window, disappearing into the sky.

Chapter 123: Business Deal

“Topic? What topic? I came here asking for your final decision! Do you want to depart from here and live in secrecy? Or would you rather have me dispose of one of your great adversaries?” After Han Li withdrew his gaze from the yellow jacketed beauty, he straightened his face and said this, not polite in the least.

After Lady Yan heard Han Li’s words, she wrinkled her brow and slowly said this to Han Li, “Young Master Han, don’t be in such a hurry! After we sisters thoroughly thought this through yesterday, we had decided to choose the second option. However, we wish to change the terms a bit.”

“I already emphasized that I do not wish to haggle with the several madams over the terms. This matter cannot be changed. Agree to my conditions and choose!” Han Li said, suddenly showing displeasure.

“Young Master, what do you think about my daughters’ looks?” Lady Yan did not take notice of Han Li’s displeasure and unexpectedly turned the conversation toward the three Mo sisters.

“National grace[1] with the scent of divinity. To praise the innate beauty of these women with these words would not be excessive!” Han Li was surprised but immediately replied with a light smile. He somewhat vaguely understood Lady Yan’s plan.

“Our request is well within reason. So long as your distinguished self can eliminate the heads of the Rainbow Sect and the Hegemon’s Villa, not only will we give you the Precious Warm Yang Jade for detoxification, but you can also take all three sisters as your wives and concubines. Were you not looking at Fengwu just a moment ago? So long as you agree, she could be of your Han clan!” Lady Yan earnestly said, pointing behind her to Mo Yuzhu and the their daughters.

“Fourth Mother!”

“Mother!”

Mo Yuzhu and Mo Caihuan’s expressions greatly changed, and they could not help but cry out. It was clear that these two had not been informed of this and were frightened pale by Lady Yan’s rash promise.

Apart from Lady Yan’s complexion turning slightly pale, she had still kept her calm.

It was no surprise that they were so alarmed. Han Li’s appearance was truly not astonishing at all, and he was a world of difference away from the two’s image of their ideal husband. They didn’t share a single common trait with him. How could they be willing to marry themselves to Han Li?

“Stop talking! This is a matter that I and your mothers have already decided upon. If you do not comply, you will be expelled from the Mo Estate.” Lady Yan said with a cold voice as she lowered her face.

Hearing these words being uttered, the three Mo sisters were all stunned.

Mo Yuzhu slightly bit her almond lips as her complexion ashened. The dazed Mo Caihuan gazed toward her Second Mother and Fifth Mother, both of whom usually loved her the most dearly, while begging with her eyes. Only Mo Fengwu was somewhat better, but her body had lightly trembled. She motionlessly leaned against the wall.

“There is no need to threaten the young ladies! I cannot agree to your conditions. It’s like how that old saying goes: ‘no matter the circumstances, I will not brave pointless hazards’. I quite cherish my little life!” After a moment of silent, Han Li replied with a lowered voice, flatly rejecting Lady Yan’s proposal.

As for Han Li, to say that his heart was not move when facing the three beautiful Mo Sisters would be a completely false statement. However, Han Li had already carefully considered that if he were to kill the other two hegemons of the Lan Province, it would surely provoke the notice of someone observant and cause life-threatening disaster to descend upon him.

Just by thinking about it, after the Rainbow Sect and the Sole Hegemon’s Villa’s collapse, Lady Yan was certain to bring the Fearsome Flood Dragon Association to great power and become the greatest beneficiary.

In addition, with the abrupt appearance of a stranger in the Mo Estate suddenly taking Mo’s three tender beauties as his wives, it would undoubtedly imply that he was this matter’s greatest contributor as well as the killer!

If this were to provoke some mysterious force that watched over cultivators, then nothing good would happen to this dabbler in cultivation. It was more than likely that he would not be able to keep his little life. In that case, what use would there be for the exquisite, ravishing, dainty beauty of these three Mo Sisters?

As a result, Han Li inwardly gave himself a bitter smile and shoved the appearance and fragrance of the three great beauties to the side.

As for whether the Mo sisters were fond of him or not, Han Li could not care less. So long as he obtained these beautiful women, then acquiring their hearts was only a matter of time! However, to say this at this moment was already useless. If Han Li’s previous words had scalded the hands of the three Mo sisters like a sweet potato, that absolutely didn’t trouble him at all! He currently planned to dissolve the cold Yin poison from his body as soon as possible and then depart from this quarrelsome place. As for whether the Mo Estate would later acquire disaster or fortune, that had nothing to do with him.

Han Li spoke of his rejection. Although the faces of Lady Yan and the other wives weren’t good, the Mo sisters have grown a rather favorable impression of him. Even the youngest, Mo Caihuan, smiled through her fake tears that created a devil’s mask with which she disguised herself in front of Han Li.

In addition, even Mo Yuzhu’s and Mo Fengwu’s impression of Han Li had soften by considerably, causing them to view him in a new light.

Lady Yan sighed. The rest looked at each other with meaningful glances, and then turned their bodies. Helpless, Lady Yan said, “Since Young Master Han hasn’t changed his mind, then we will leave the matter alone! We will reach a deal according to Young Master’s conditions. So long as Young Master Han can kill the Hegemon’s Villa Sovereign, “Furious Lion” Ouyang Feitian, we will hand over the Precious Warm Yang Jade that will let your distinguished self be detoxified.”

“Hehe! You women are quite good at scheming! I heard this Ouyang Feitian is at the prime of his life and has yet to have children. The Hegemon’s Villa will almost certainly collapse immediately after his death. Its subordinates would be in complete disarray, too busy to worry about the Fearsome Flood Dragon Association.” Han Li stroked his nose, softly laughing.

When Lady Yan heard Han Li’s words, she gave Han Li a cold glance.

“It is not as you say. Do you know who it was that sent Wu Jianming here? It was by the order of this Sovereign Ouyang. In addition, Wu Jianming is Ouyang Feitian’s seventh disciple, and is extremely doted upon.

“The Sovereign of Hegemon’s Villa was of the same generation as our Lord Husband and is of nearly the same age. From the beginning, he has been ambitiously wanting to proclaim himself Sovereign of the entire Lan Province, and thus he employed the tactics ‘first weak then strong’, striving to first consume the Fearsome Flood Dragon Association and then deal with the Rainbow Sect. “

“Several years ago, he instigated my Lord Husband’s sword little brother Ma Kongtian and my Lord Husband’s second disciple, Zhao Kun, to attempt to split the Fearsome Flood Dragon Association. In the end, it was seen through by us sisters, and we killed those two and their accomplices in advance. However, the Fearsome Flood Dragon Association’s strength had been greatly damaged. We had to retreat step by step under the pressure from the Hegemon’s Villa’s advancing army. As a result, we had no choice but to pull back our men and entrench ourselves in Jia Yuan City.”

Lady Yan softly spoke of a few of the Fearsome Flood Dragon Association’s secrets.

“However, your current influence in Jia Yuan City seems to not amount to much either. Couldn’t the Hegemon’s Villa just exterminate you in a single vigorous attempt?” Han Li thought for a moment and asked, slightly puzzled.

“Heehee! Ouyang Feitian, that madman, doesn’t dare to attack here. Naturally, he has his reasons. If you want to, so long as you agree to our sister’s original conditions, I will tell Young Master.” Third Wife Liu giggled, telling half-truths with her alluring voice.

“Hehe! Let’s forget about it then. I was just a bit curious!” Han Li remained completely calm and collected.

“Really! Not a single bit masculine, without even the slightest intention of bringing out a bit more force!” Third Wife Liu said with her small mouth, as if teasing Han Li.

Lady Yan and the others turned a blind eye to the Third Wife’s actions; however, the three Mo sister’s faces had turned red. After all, their own elder had teased the man they were originally about to marry right in front of his face. Outrageous!

Mo Caihuan pouted and firmly glared at Han Li.

However, Han Li seemed to not notice this in the least, as if he were in his own world. Instead, he replied, “Third Martial Mother speaks of this quite lightly. Since a bit of force could cost me my own life, I’m fine with not being a masculine man! I’m fine so long as I am a man!”

Perhaps Han Li’s last sentence was a bit too frank, because not only did it stun Third Wife Liu, who pursed the lips of her enchanting smile, it also annoyed Second Wife Li and Lady Yan.

“Young Master, how do you plan to take Ouyang Feitian’s life? This person spends his days hiding deeply within the villa and rarely leaves. Not only is he at the pinnacle of martial arts, his shrewdness is outstanding. He is quite a difficult opponent to deal with.” Lady Yan firmly said with a stiff complexion.

“Lady Fourth shouldn’t worry about that. You just have to prepare me a good horse and a portrait of this person. Then I will make him disappear from this world.”

“I hope so!” Lady Yan softly spoke.

“Back to the previous topic…shouldn’t you give me a guarantee that when I return from my completed task, you women will not become hostile and refuse to acknowledge your debt!?” Han Li intoned, soft as a feather.

“What kind of guarantee does your distinguished self want?” Lady Yan didn’t show any discontent but rather seemed to have already anticipate this demand.

“Inside this bottle, there is a medicine pill. I must ask everyone to take this poison, but I will not say what it is.[2] In any case, wait for day I come back after killing Ouyang to exchange the antidote for the Precious Warm Yang Jade.” Han Li felt around for a porcelain bottle before setting it on the table and coldly staring at Lady Yan and her family members.

Lady Yan did not say anything further and extended her fine lily-white hands to grab the bottle. She poured out a jade green pill and looked to Lady Li and the others before tilting her head up and swallowing it.

“Good courage! Good decisiveness! You are truly worthy of leading the Fearsome Flood Dragon Association.” Han Li could not help but give praise. His gaze then moved toward the rest of the women.

[1]. TL: “Outstanding beauty”: ????, national grace, divine fragrance

[Back]

[2]. TL: In Chinese the word of medicine “?” also means poison.

[Back]

Chapter 125: Plans

“Time? Place?” When Xi Tieniu heard this, he was stunned momentarily. It seemed he had no recollection of it. But now, seeing Han Li so serious, he knew this was the crucial point of his service. He lowered his head and pondered deeply, trying to recollect his memory.

Half a quarter of an hour later….

“Got it!” Xi Tieniu suddenly shouted, raising his head. His face was completely cheerful.

“I heard the female Immortal tell her male companion that before they participate in the Immortal’s Great Assembly, he was to accompany her to an Immortal gathering place called the Great South[1] Valley.”

“Great South Valley?” Han Li softly murmured to himself. He had never heard of it before, not even the slightest impression.

Han Li turned his gaze to Sun Ergou. If this place had a name, then this local gang boss should have a bit of information.

“There is no such place in Jia Yuan City! If there is truly such a valley, I would remember it quite clearly.” Sun Ergou creased his brow and shook his head left and right.

“Did you for some reason remember incorrectly?” Han Li brought his gaze back to Xi Tieniu as he spoke in a cold, severe tone.

“I absolutely did not. That woman also said that, as long as they hurry for half a day, she would be able to attend the meeting with her friend at Great South Valley.” Xi Tieniu said, hastily swearing to the heavens.

“Half a day! If a person were to walk by foot then they would no longer be in the vicinity of Jia Yuan City. But if these two were rushing on flying beasts, then the scope would be great. Even so, it shouldn’t stray from the boundaries of Lan Province.” Han Li inwardly pondered.

“Do you two know of any places called ‘Great South Valley’ or with names that include ‘Great South’?” Han Li’s expression eased a bit as he asked the two.

“Sun Ergou and Xi Tieniu looked at each other and spoke nearly at the same time:

“Great South Temple.”

“Great South Mountain.”

“There are two places called Great South?” Han Li was surprised. Groaning, he started to have a small headache.

“Young Master, there isn’t! There is only one!” Sun Ergou hastily replied.

“That Great South Temple was build on Great South Mountain.” Xi Tieniu added, not to be outdone.

“Oh! Very good. Then it seems that Great South Valley should located there,” Han Li easily stated.

“But Young Master, we have never heard of a ‘Great South Valley’ near Great South Mountain! It could be wrong.” Sun Ergou warned with doubt.

When Han Li heard this, he chuckled, “It isn’t wrong, it’s this place!”

‘You aren’t cultivators, so of course you wouldn’t know of this place. I suppose that there should be some sort of cultivator’s residence,’ Han Li excitedly thought.

“Where is the lowest point of this Great South Mountain?” After Han Li’s excitement, he recalled that this place wasn’t well known and asked without thinking.

“Young Master, Great South Mountain is in the Lan Province’s southmost area.” Sun Ergou respectfully said.

“Lan Province’s south?” Han Li wrinkled his brow. The Hegemon’s Villa and the Sovereign he was to assassinate were right in the center of the Lan Province, out of the way and absolutely inconvenient. It seemed that he would have to make several trips.

“Sun Ergou, after you return, have Xi Tieniu become the Fourth Level Gang’s Vice Commander. I know you aren’t too willing but since I already promised this person, the promise must be kept.” Han Li instructed Sun Ergou.

“I don’t dare to refuse, Young Master. Your wish is my command. I wouldn’t voice even half a complaint!” When Sun Ergou heard this, he had a fright. Recalling what Han Li had said before, his complexion turned pale.

“Be at ease, I am well aware of your loyalty. This bottle contains the antidote that will completely dissolve the poison in your body. Just like I promised, you will have nothing further to fear. I treat everyone fairly, so I will certainly not cheat you.” Han Li removed a bottle of medicine and handed it over to Sun Ergou.

When Sun Ergou saw this, he was pleased beyond expectation. The Rotten Heart Pill inside his body had made his meals unappetizing and his sleep restless. Now that he could completely remove it, how could he not be moved?

“Thank you, Young Master! Thank you, Young Master! This servant will certainly repay this favor even if he were to die the cruelest death!” After Sun Ergou took the bottle, he sincerely said these words.

Han Li non-committedly nodded his head.

The reason why he had given the cure to Sun Ergou so frankly was mostly because he felt that giving Sun Ergou a dose of antidote every month would be far too troublesome! Since he would be far away from Jia Yuan City for a prolonged period of time, he decided to forego using poison to control Sun Ergou. Of course, if someday these two truly betrayed him, Han Li wouldn’t care about it in the least. He would just immediately kill the two and find their replacements.

In addition, Han Li had no use for the Fourth Level Gang as of now. He had already prepared the Fourth Level Gang to be a fallback plan in case all else failed.

Han Li clearly understood that in this world, there were no loyalty nor betrayal without reason. By using force to control others, it would be the easiest method to acquire the desired results. But at the same time, it was also the worst method, because the party being forced may retaliate at any time. As a result, if one were to instill some loyalty, it would be best to include both incentives and punishment.

Hence, Han Li gave Sun Ergou the cure. On one hand, he would greatly raise Sun Ergou’s loyalty for a long period of time. On the other, Xi Tieniu and Sun Ergou would feel meaning behind his words: Results will merit rewards and mistakes will be punished. This benefited Han Li’s long term control over the two.

That was what Han Li had thought after some deliberation.

After Han Li saw Sun Ergou consume the cure, he suddenly said something that made Sun Ergou both frightened and happy.

“I will leave Crooked Soul in your care later on, but I won’t allow you to use it to provoke quarrels. Although this Crooked Soul may be ferocious, there are a great many extraordinary eccentrics in this world. You might be so unlucky as to provoke a deathly calamity. Keep this inmind!” Han Li said with a heavy tone.

“Of course, I will keep this in mind. I will properly make arrangements for Sir Crooked Soul. Esteemed Young Master, please feel at ease.” Sun Ergou was like a chick pecking grain, nodding his head incessantly.

“Were it not for the fact that I no longer need Crooked Soul as a personal bodyguard, his far too eye-catching appearance, and the inconvenience of him following me on a long journey, there is no way I could hand over Crooked Soul to this person’s care!” Thinking this, Han Li sighed and inwardly shook his head, somewhat reluctant to part with his large companion.

“Look out for yourselves! In the coming days, you do not need to come see me, I will soon leave on a prolonged journey far from here, and I do not know when I will return.” Han Li softly waved his hand as he told them to leave.

When Sun Ergou and Xi Tieniu heard these words, they respectfully withdrew from the room, leaving Han Li as the sole person within. Even so, he was still contemplating about something.

“This Great South Valley, at the very bottom of Great South Mountain…what sort of cultivators will there be? If I come to their door without prior notice, would it be improper? Would I encounter danger?” Han Li foolishly thought. As of now, he could not help but let his mind wander and enter a state of selflessness.

Time flew by, and in a blink of an eye, two months had already passed. At this moment, Han Li could not longer be found in Jia Yuan City. Furthermore, Han Li’s silhouette would no longer be seen for quite a long time.

[1]. TL: Great South (Tainan)?? could almost mean southmost or the most southern

[Back]

Chapter 128: Great South Meeting

“Which clan is Brother from?” After the youth finished looking at the dense fog with excitement, he seemed to have remembered something, so he turned his head to ask.

When Han Li had chatted with the youth just a moment ago, he realized that in the world of cultivators, aside from cultivation sects and clans, the number of rogue cultivators was not small.

The majority of these so-called rogue cultivators were either the last generation of a fallen cultivation clan or people like Han Li, mortals who accidentally stumbled upon some cultivation art and voluntarily entered the world of cultivators. Furthermore, the rogue cultivators from declining sects were separated from their inheritance; their cultivation was, for the most part, not at a high stage, generally lingering at Qi Condensation. As a result, cultivation clans have rarely treated rogue cultivators with high regard and had somewhat held them in contempt, just like how rich families from the secular world looked down upon poor and destitute families.

“I do not come from a clan, but rather I’ve cultivated by myself!” After Han Li thought for a moment, he decided to speak the truth. After all, pretending to be a member from another clan was far too easy to expose.

“Your esteemed self is a rogue cultivator!?” Although this was quite unexpected to the youth, his face didn’t wear the slightest look of discrimination but instead had a look of pleasant surprised.

He excitedly circled around Han Li, looking at Han Li as if he were a rare object.

“Didn’t Little Brother just say a moment ago that cultivation clans looked down upon rogue cultivators? How are you still so happy?” Han Li asked, somewhat amazed by this.

“They do, but don’t confuse our Wan clan with other cultivator clans. Our Wan clan has always treated rogue cultivators well!” The youth pridefully replied. He seemed quite proud of his clan’s practices.

“Our Wan clan’s ancestors were originally rogue cultivators. However they were fortunate enough to enter a cultivation school, becoming official disciples of the Giant Sword Sect. At this point, our Wan clan was established, and because of our origins, the rules of our Wan clan have always made it forbidden to discriminate against rogue cultivators.” The youth said with a smile.

“Actually, it isn’t limited to our Wan clan. A few other clans’ ancestors were also rogue cultivators, therefore they also bear no ill will toward rogue cultivators. However, these clans take up far too small a portion of the entirety of cultivation clans. That is why there is the saying that cultivator clans discriminate against rogue cultivators.” The youth added while shaking his head.

“So it’s like that! It seems I am quite lucky. My first meeting was with a little brother from this sort of clan, the Wan clan.” After Han Li heard the other side’s response to his identity as a rogue cultivator, he had somewhat loosened his guard around the youth.

“However Brother, throughout the entire journey, you’ve asked about so many commonly known matters in the world of cultivators. Could it be that brother is a new cultivator that had just left the mountain?” The youth turned his eyes, saying this with sudden realization. It was unknown why he became intelligent all of a sudden.

When Han Li heard this, his face slightly smiled, and he used his hand to pat the youth’s shoulders. He said somewhat apologetically, “I hadn’t meant to deliberately fool Little Brother, but I had just entered the world of cultivation. I had a few misgivings!”

“It doesn’t matter, I don’t mind! However, this Big Brother should tell me his name! In the future, you should directly call me Xiaoshan, I won’t mind.” Wan Xiaoshan was clearly a familiar kind of person, saying this without a care in the world.

“Hehe! I am Han Li. I truly just entered the world of cultivation. I hope Brother Xiaoshan will take care of me!” Han Li’s impression of Wan Xiaoshan was quite favorable, causing the tone of his words to become much more amiable.

“No problem. If there is something Big Brother Han doesn’t understand, do not hesitate to ask. Hehe! Who would have thought that I, Wan Xiaoshan, would be instructing others?” Wan Xiaoshan proudly said.

“If I have any questions, I will certainly ask Xiaoshan. However, shouldn’t we enter the valley?” Han Li slightly smiled, pointing to the sky.

“Aiya! I almost forgot about our true affair.” After Wan Xiaoshan looked to the sky where Han Li’s finger was pointed, he immediately shouted, flustered.

The youth busily searched himself for quite a while before finally taking out a paper talisman from his bosom.

After he made several gestures with his hands and softly spoke several phrases, he threw the paper talisman into the sky. It transformed into a streak of fire that burst into the dense fog, not longer capable of being seen.

“Big Brother Han Li, wait a moment. My announcement talisman will soon enter the valley. The people in the valley will release the spell and guide us there.” After the youth saw Han Li somewhat entranced in the direction that the flame had disappeared, he quickly explained,

“Oh!” Han Li nodded his head, expressing his understanding.

“Big Brother Han Li, on this visit to Great South Valley, surely you have brought quite a few goods to exchange? Can you tell me? Don’t feel embarrassed, this Little Brother will say what he brought first!”

“I brought a dozen elementary low-grade blank paper talismans, two elementary low-grade Invisibility Talismans, two elementary low-grade Fleeing Earth Talismans, one elementary mide-grade Rapid Thunder Talisman, a dozen elementary low-grade Ice Bullet Talismans, an ingot of source iron, a bottle of elementary grade cinnabar, a bundle of whiskers from the Three-Tailed Cat demon beast, medicinal herbs….” Wan Xiaoshan didn’t take notice of the dumbstruck Han Li as he murmured and counted his fingers,listing out his stockpile of items.

“Done! Now it’s Big Brother Han’s turn to say! Big Brother, why is your complexion so white? You…” The youngster blinked. He looked at Han Li, not understanding why Han Li was speechless.

“Don’t tell me that to enter Great South Valley, I must prepare items beforehand?” Han Li complexion was unsightly.

“There is no such rule!” Wan Xiaoshan bluntly replied.

Having heard this, Han Li complexion immediately improved.

“However, those that come to Great South Valley at this time are certain to participate in Great South Meeting. Who wouldn’t bring any items? This only happens once every five years; the occasion is for us younger generation of the Lan Province to set up a trading event! Especially for the great Immortal Ascension Assembly that our Lan Province will hold a month from now. Those who pass by to participate in Great South’s Small Meeting are numerous. Could it be that Big Brother did not come to take part in the famous Great South Valley’s Small Meeting?” The youth said, shocked. He looked at Han Li with a gaze lacking confidence.

Han Li bitterly smiled.

“Brother Xiaoshan, I truly didn’t know that this place would have a Great South Meeting. I merely found out by accident that this place harbored other cultivators. I came to make friends, nothing more. How could I have specially prepared some items beforehand?” Han Li helplessly said as he spread out his hands.

“So it was like that! That is far too unfortunate. Big Brother Han Li has no choice but to squander this golden opportunity. You should know that there are no opportunities to those who lack goods and materials.” Wan Xiaoshan said with a face full of pity, repeatedly sighing at Han Li.

“However, I can’t say that I have nothing on me that I can’t trade. At the very least, do I not have these two talismans?” Han Li thought, mocking himself.

At this moment, the dense fog in front of the two suddenly split as if a person had cut it with a knife, creating a small path that could fit two people shoulder to shoulder. With a glance, one could not see the other end of the small path, which seemed to be quite a distance away.

“Alright, let’s go!” The youth looked toward Han Li with a wry yet happy face before joyfully rushing in first and disappearing onto the road.

Han Li carefully observed the small path with indifference for a moment, before walking in with striding steps. He walked with stable steps, calm and unhurried.

This path seemed to be quite long, but after walking for a short period of time, he arrived at the end.

Once Han Li walked off the path, something was suddenly revealed before him, a rarely seen fully lush, green valley. The valley was closed off from three sides by mountains. Its only entrance was the mountain side sealed off by dense fog where Han Li had originally entered.

This entire region was quite large, no less than sixteen acres. At the center, there was a large fenced off area with a jade palace pavilion where somewhat bizarrely dressed people left and entered.

In front of the pavilion, there was an expansive azure brick plaza occupied by many people resembling small traders. The entire plaza was set up with small vendors’ stalls. From time to time, he would see one or two people pressed against the front of a booth. They would look at a few things or perhaps softly ask a few questions, but Han Li rarely saw anyone who reached a deal.

Having seen this, Han Li couldn’t help but take in a deep breath.This was the world of cultivators! All the people here were cultivators. Being able to see so many cultivators all at once had left Han Li in somewhat of a trance.

Han Li softly shook his head, clearing his mind a bit. He constantly reminded himself that he wanted to enter a previously unimaginable world. The people here were most likely able to eliminate him with ease. He must be more cautious and subdued.

With this thought, Han Li turned his head to look at the path that by now had already completely disappeared and raised his leg to walk toward the bright stage.

Chapter 130: Becoming a Member

“Brother, why are you waiting here by yourself? Are you waiting for a friend?” A bright and clear voice suddenly came from behind Han Li, giving him a start.

Han Li slowly turned around and saw six to seven people standing not far from him. The one who spoke was a 27 or 28 year-old cultivator dressed in Daoist robes. This person had a blemishless white face and regular features. He held a horsetail whisk in his arm and was looking at Han Li with a smile.

“Does this Daoist priest have business with myself?” Han Li did not understand the other party’s questions and instead asked him a question in return.

“Hehe! Don’t misunderstand, we aren’t looking at Brother with evil intentions. It’s just that we saw Brother stand by himself with an appearance of curiosity towards everything. That’s why we guessed your esteemed self was a rogue cultivator that attended the meeting alone and thought we’d come and make friends. We’re all rogue cultivators much like your esteemed self.” The Daoist priest explained with a face of benevolence.

“You are all rogue cultivators?” Han Li was slightly shocked.

“That’s right. If your esteemed self is a rogue cultivator, then it would be best to stay together with us. That way, everyone will be able to look after each other during this meeting.” These words came from the delicate and pretty face of a young woman with a scar. Beside her was a large, fully bearded man carrying a broadsword on his back. The two seemed to be married.

“Yes, previously lone rogue cultivators that participated in the trade meet were regularly humiliated by those from large clans because they were too weak!” The Daoist priest solemnly said.

Hearing these two’s words, Han Li had somewhat understood the other party’s intentions.

This group of rogue cultivators were afraid of being bullied by those from cultivator clans during the meet. As a result, they voluntarily gathered together and created a small gang in an attempt to acquire the ability to defend themselves. That was why they looked everywhere for lone rogue cultivators.

Since the other party’s intent was clear, Han Li naturally could not refuse these kinds of good intentions. After all, he truly needed a small group to shield him from the rain; he did not care that this could only be considered a temporary thing.

However, he still needed to carefully ask the other party several questions before being able to join them with ease.

“Since you several people have looked out for me, I won’t conceal anything. I truly am a rogue cultivator. However, if you wish for me to join your group, could you first introduce yourselves and say what I must do as a member of your group?” Han Li calmly admitted his identity as a rogue cultivator, but as soon as the people in front of him revealed happy expressions, he put forth his request.

“It seems that Brother still has some misgivings! Haha! This is no matter. When the others had barely joined, they spoke almost the same exact words as your esteemed self!” After the Daoist priest and the others heard Han Li’s words, not only did they not show an expression of displeasure but instead, they looked at each other and laughed heartily. Afterwards, the Daoist priest said these words:

“I will give you an introduction of these several friends!” The Daoist priest pointed to the several rogue cultivators and said to Han Li with a smile.

“These two are blood brothers from the Dark Blue Wolf Mountains, Hei Mu and Hei Jin.”[1] The Daoist priest pointed to the youthful pair and calmly introduced them.

These two cupped their hands towards Han Li, and Han Li calmly returned the courtesy.

“This is Flying Lotus Cave’s Vagabond Hong Lian[2] and Pu Lu Mountain’s Master Ku Sang.” This time, he pointed to the ordinary young lady and the small, bitter faced Buddhist monk.

“As for them…”

“We are a married couple from Skywater Village, Hu Pinggu and Xiong Dali.” The Daoist priest had pointed to the young woman and that large bearded man who had not yet spoken. With a chuckle, the young woman quickly took over the conversation.

The Daoist priest wasn’t angry from being interrupted and calmly laughed instead.

“This humble Daoist is the Daoist Priest of Crouching Ox Mountain’s Young Ox Crown, Gua Shan. My Daoist name is ‘Qing Wen’.[3] Hehe, this humble Daoist is this small group’s founder and current leader for the time being. However this humble Daoist cannot command anyone and only speaks first during external affairs!” The Daoist priest humbly introduced himself last and also gave the general characteristics of this small gang.

This Daoist priest also had quite a bit of bearing. This person didn’t seem bad at all!

In addition, the others’ magic power didn’t seem weak for the most part. Most of them had the magic power equivalent to the seventh or eighth layer of Eternal Spring Arts! This Daoist Priest Qing Wen was even more formidable. Although he hadn’t reached the level of the blue-clothed man, he was much stronger than Han Li.

After Han Li pondered for a moment, he felt that joining these people had many advantages with no disadvantages. He then said, “Since everyone is a rogue cultivator and group affairs are handled well, I, Han Li, would like to join you for the time being.

“Very good, Brother Han has joined. The strength of our group has increased yet again!” After Daoist priest Qing Wen heard Han Li’s words, he immediately replied in a cheerful tone.

The others had also revealed a happy expression. After all, Han Li’s magic powered seemed to be not weak and would be of no small assistance to them.

“Is our entire group here?” Han Li asked, currently looking left and right.

“There are still two more. One is currently sound asleep in a room. The other is strolling around.” Hu Pinggu curled her lip. It seemed she did not look at these two people particularly favorably.

“It isn’t as bad as Lady Hu says. One simply wanted to sleep for a bit, and the other wanted to have some fun!” The small Buddhist monk defended on behalf of the two people.

“You…” Hu Pinggu felt some discontent upon hearing Buddhist Monk Ku Sang words, and wanted to say a few other things.

“Enough! Everyone mustn’t argue. After all everyone had originally come to an agreement. Except for when we battle an external power, when we all must unite and follow orders. We all have freedom during all other times and can do as we wish!” Daoist Priest Qing Wen hastily stepped forward to mediate.

Although this Lady Hu did not appear outwardly happy, she did not pester and argue afterwards. After all, Daoist Priest Qing Wen’s strength was quite powerful, so she could not help but give him face.

“Wait until evening, then Brother Han will be able to meet with the two. I will give you an introduction at that time. Those two truly stand out from the masses!” The Daoist priest had a helpless appearance. It seemed the two were quite troublesome.

When Han Li saw this, although his interest was greatly piqued, he found it embarrassing to question this matter closely.

Next, Daoist Priest Qing Wen asked Han Li if he planned to move together with them or stroll by himself.

Han Li naturally chose the latter, not surprising Daoist Priest Qing Wen. Because those who had just entered Great South Valley were naturally quite curious, they would for the most part favor moving alone. However, it would take about the same time for him to finish looking if they were to move together.

The Daoist priest was also quite conscientious. After telling Han Li a few taboo subjects and a few common conventions, making sure he understood the Great South Small Meeting completely, he gave Han Li a talisman.

He pointed to a pavilion’s small bannered floor and told Han Li that the pavilion was where they were staying. The talisman he gave Han Li was a key to open the small floor’s restrictive spell, allowing Han Li to rest there when he were tired.

Afterwards these several people said their goodbyes to Han Li and disappeared from the dim light of night, leaving him not knowing whether they were continuing to look for other rogue cultivators.

Han Li continued to looked at the rear figures of these several people until they were already too far away to be seen. He then lowered his head to look at the talisman in his hand. There was a silver glisten on the yellow talisman. It was a talisman charm he was unable to make sense of. It seemed truly quite clever.

After Han Li muttered to himself for a moment, he softly smiled.

He folded the paper talisman and put it into his bosom. Then, after a deep look in the direction that Daoist Priest Qing Wen disappeared, he turned around and walked toward the plaza without the slightest hesitation.

After he entered the plaza, Han Li became like the other cultivators; he slowly walked on one side while turning his head to look at the goods of each and every vendor’s stall.

According to what Daoist Priest Qing Wen had mentioned a moment ago, these cultivator transactions generally used two methods.

The first method would be to exchange items for items. A few cultivators would trade a few goods they didn’t need but were still hesitant to part with for goods that they urgently needed. As a result, those who set up a vendor stall would not have any successful transactions for several days. This was quite a common occurrence.

[1]. TL: ?? Hei Mu – Black Tree, ?? Hei Jin- Black Gold.

[Back]

[2]. TL: ?? Hong Lian means Red Lotus.

[Back]

[3]. In this chapter, the Daoist priest was originally named Song Wen ??, but the author changes this to Qing Wen ?? in all later chapters.

[Back]

Chapter 131: Spirit Stones and Spirit Talisman

Another more popular method was to use something called “spirit stones” as a form of currency in business transactions among cultivators to buy and sell goods.

As the name implies, a “spirit stone” is a type of stone that was full of the world’s Spiritual Qi. The amount of Spiritual Qi accumulated in the spirit stone is a huge supplement for cultivators.

If a cultivator absorbed the Spiritual Qi within the spirit stone during meditation as he cultivated, his speed of cultivation would reach astonishing rates. After all, the scattered Spiritual Qi that a cultivator would have to absorb and refine by himself was quite different from having pure, refined Spiritual Qi next to him that he could absorb and refine as he wished.

However, this was not a spirit stone’s greatest effect. The most important usage of the spirit stone was for magic techniques and to set up a formation spell.

Whether or not a high-grade formation spell succeeded and was effective, it all depended upon the effectiveness of the spirit stones used. A good spirit stone would not only guarantee the success of the formation spell, it would also increase the power dramatically.

However, the amount of spirit stones used for magic techniques was far above the utility of formation spells. This was because a cultivator had to rely on his own magic power cultivation to determine the grade and effectiveness of the magic technique he wanted to execute. Since it was almost impossible to rely on oneself and use a high-grade magic technique, spirit stones became the best magic power amplification object.

If a cultivator cast a very powerful magic spell while holding a spirit stone in his hand, the Spiritual Qi within the spirit stone would continuously replenish the cultivator’s loss of magic power during magic casting. In this manner, it was able to support magic techniques one would originally be unable to use.

Therefore, the spirit stones had become the best option for cultivators to gain the upper hand and win from a position of weakness. They were also the best strength recovery tonic after magic power was greatly depleted, and would increase one’s chances of survival during a fight by leaps and bounds.

Spirit stones have so many uses and amazing effects, so naturally, the value for a spirit stone rose as well.

But because of the vast consumption of the spirit stones, along with the excessive exploitation and continuous decline of their ore veins, spirit stones had gradually became a precious luxury good in the present day of the cultivating world. In short, it became a cultivator’s optimal safeguard for business transactions and the only circulating monetary currency. Furthermore, there was even a collaborative decision on the detailed differentiation on a spirit stone’s specifications and grade.

Spirit stones were grade into four grades according to the amount of spirit power they contained. The four grades comprised of low-grade spirit stone, mid-grade spirit stone, high-grade spirit stone and top-grade spirit stone. In addition, according to the different attribute of spirit power spirit stones stored, they could also be categorised into the five elements: Metal spirit stone, Wood spirit stone, Water spirit stone, Earth spirit stone, and Fire spirit stone. Moreover, there are also rarely seen spirit stone attributes such as Wind (?) spirit stone and Thunder spirit stone. But those spirit stones were very rare.

These kind of extremely precious items like spirit stones, Han Li don’t even possess a single piece of it.

He admitted that he did not have any sort of goods on him to use for an exchange. Hence from the start, he had intentions to widen his horizon, so he looked around without any restraint and continued his journey.

Even though Han Li’s appearance was indifferent and calm, the items at the vendors’ stalls made his heart stir and greatly envious.

Ignoring the rest of the items, even the plain white talisman paper that every vending stall offered was subject to his attention. Despite the fact that this object was very common, it was currently what Han Li needed the most.

Even though Han Li still did not know the meaning of the level or grade of this talisman paper and what specific difference it had, he knew that with his present power, the elementary low-grade talisman paper was definitely enough for him to fully execute the Soul-Lock Talisman.

Therefore, if he could acquire a few talisman papers, he could immediately use one more type of magic spell, instantly increasing his strength quite a bit.

Of course other than the talisman paper, there was a rich variety of spirit talisman such as “Thunder Fire Talisman”, “Fire Dragon Talisman”, and the “Huge Force Talisman”. All of these caused Han Li to be rather tempted.

While Han Li was still standing in front of an unassuming vendor’s stall, he saw a spirit talisman that was exactly the same as the Daoist paper talisman that released a golden barrier, which he owned. Beside it, a signboard clearly wrote: “Guardian Talisman, metal elementary mid-grade defensive spirit talisman, worth nine low-grade spirit stones”.

Han Li had shopped at many vending stalls, so he had come to understand the prices of these Daoist paper talisman. One low-grade spirit stone could buy a dozen elementary low-grade plain white talisman paper. But fully refined elementary low-grade Daoist paper talismans, depending on the different types of magic spell, were sold separately for two pieces of low-grade spirit stones.

As for the elementary mid-grade spirit talisman, promptly translating a few could sell for six to ten spirit stones. Moreover, defensive spirit talisman were more expensive than offensive spirit talisman.

As Han Li himself had the same type of object, he naturally wanted to take note of it.

After carefully examining stall’s Guardian Talisman, Han Li discovered the other talisman’s Spiritual Qi was much better than the one he kept in his bosom. It was clearly a new product that has not yet been used, but he reckoned that his worn and old product could only be sold at one third of its price at best.

Coming to this conclusion, Han Li laughed bitterly. It seemed that among cultivators, he was still a pauper. He couldn’t help but to touch the article he had on him. Suddenly, he jolted when he remembered that he had a spirit talisman inscribed with a picture of a small sword in his bosom.

Although he still didn’t know the name of the talisman, Han Li believed that this talisman was worthed more than the Guardian Talisman.

When he thought of this, Han Li began to pay close attention to every vendor, taking note to see whether the same Daoist paper talisman with the picture of a small sword was being sold.

Unfortunately, after going around so many stalls, he still did not see a similar product. Instead, at an area with five to six cultivators gathering around, Han Li found someone selling an elementary high-grade spirit talisman.

The signboard beside the spirit talisman wrote: “Soaring Sky Talisman, Wind-attribute elementary high-grade flying-type spirit talisman, price is at 30 low-grade spirit stone or exchange for consolidation-type pill medicine of equal value”.

The moment Han Li saw the signboard, his heart was startled.

After going around many stalls, this was the first elementary high-grade spirit talisman that Han Li had seen. He couldn’t help but to attentively view it. As expected, that spirit paper talisman’s Spiritual Qi was astonishingly rich unlike all the previous low-grade and mid-grade spirit talisman he inspected in the other stalls.

A huge barefooted horsefaced man, who was standing around and viewing the talisman, was unable to restrain himself and asked, “20 pieces of spirit stones, are you willing to exchange?”

The stall’s owner was a capable and vigorous youth. He used his hand and pointed to the signboard, then paid no heed to that person any longer.

“It’s only a flying-type talisman. It’s not even an offensive or defensive spirit talisman. 20 pieces is more than enough!” The horsefaced man made a bid mentioned, dissatisfied.

“Hmph! If it was really an offensive or defensive spirit talisman, you think I would still settle for only 30 pieces? If you don’t have 50 pieces, I won’t even let you have a look! If you want to benefit at the others’ expense, go to other places! I don’t welcome it here.” The youth finally said coldly. But the moment he opened his mouth, he made the huge man’s face turn entirely red.

“Good lad! I, Qin Yeling’s Ye Bao,[1] will remember you. After this gathering ends, let’s compare skills with each other.” The horsefaced huge man said exasperatedly.

“Qin Yeling.” Originally Han Li was beaming happily as he viewed by the side, but after suddenly hearing the name of this place, he grew alarmed.

“Isn’t that the birthplace of the dwarf I killed? Although the midget’s words might not have been true, I must still be careful of this huge man who claims to be from the Ye Clan.”

Thinking up until here, Han Li subconsciously retreated back a few steps, quietly left the area, and went to the next vendor. But he already kept in mind the exchange of consolidation-type pill medicine written on the signboard.

Han Li remembered that he still had a lot of unfinished Yellow Dragon Pellets and Gold Essence Pills, but he didn’t know if those were the types of pills that the youth was requesting for. When there were less people around, he would go again and ask! If he was really successful, then he would have some capital and would be able to exchange for some necessary items.

After Han Li considered this, he turned his head to glance at the youth’s stall and discovered that Ye Bao had unknowingly left to go somewhere else and was no longer there. Among the remaining people left, there was another person who fished out a bottle and handed it over to the youth.

The youth opened the bottle and smelled it a bit, but he then shook his head and returned the bottle to the owner. The owner of the bottle could only leave the place with a face full of regret. The others seemed to have come together with that person and also left shortly afterwards. Currently, there was no one in front of that stall.

Seeing this, Han Li was delighted and slowly returned to the front of the youth’s stall. When the youth saw Han Li, he smiled distractedly, clearly recognising the person who came by once just now.

Han Li did not care that the youth laughed and said, “I have two types of medicine. Can we see if they are suitable for your request?”

After speaking, he took out two small porcelain bottles, one green and one blue, and placed it in front of the youth.

Instead of speaking nonsense, the youth reached his hand out to take the two porcelain bottles and opened the lid one by one. He then brought the bottle openings closer to his nose and smelled hard at both bottles separately. Afterwards, his face revealed a thoughtful expression.

The youth muttered to himself for a while and did not immediately return to normal. Instead he gently pushed the porcelain bottles towards Han Li.

“What is it?” Han Li blinked and asked.

“To tell you the truth, the pill medicines in both bottles were better than the ones I saw from the previous few people. But to me, they still not enough.” The youth hesitated for a moment, but he still shook his head and refused.

[1]. TL: ‘Ye Bao’ (??) means ‘Leaf Leopard’

[Back]

Chapter 132: The Harvest

When Han Li heard this, he was greatly disappointed, but it also did not surprise him. After all, the Yellow Dragon Pellet and Gold Essence Pill were mortal spiritual medicines. To ordinary people these may be miracle medicines, but to Immortal cultivators, these were indeed lacking.

Since the youth did not look up, Han Li also did not want to be long-winded, so he reached out to take the porcelain bottles back.

“Although these pill medicines are indeed a bit lacking, if you have more bottles, I will exchange with you!” The youth suddenly spoke, looking quite sympathetic.

After hearing the youth’s words, Han Li’s arm that was reaching out was immediately withdrawn. He laughed lightly.

“Did I say that I only have two medicinal bottles?” Han Li spoke slowly as he narrowed his eyes to focus on the youth.

“You have more?” The youth was slightly surprised, but he immediately revealed a cheerful expression.

“Of course, but if you want too many, I would still need to consider whether to agree with this transaction.” Han Li said noncommittally, as he was afraid that the youth might take advantage of the situation.

“That’s great! I don’t need a lot, just three bottles will do. It will be enough to allow me to break through the bottleneck in a short period of time.” The youth cheered up, appearing very passionate, which was very different from his previously cold demeanor.

This wasn’t surprising. Who would bear to part with any consolidation pill medicine that was able to improve one's cultivation? There wasn’t even enough to use on oneself! This was also the main reason why the youth had not exchanged the flight talisman these past few days.

Han Li’s Yellow Dragon Pellet and Gold Essence Pill were not considered top-notch spiritual medicine to Immortal cultivators, but thanks to the advantage of quantity, it was sufficient to allow the youth to break through to the tenth layer after being stuck at the peak of ninth layer for so long, thus increasing the youth’s power drastically.

However, only Han Li, a rascal who ate this type of medicine as mere snacks, could afford to use pill medicine for the exchange. Even so, Han Li was fully aware of the reason behind not exposing one’s wealth. Han Li didn’t want to the youth to have the impression that he could easily take out huge amounts of pill medicine without having any regrets.

Hence, Han Li touched his chin, making an appearance of pain as well as reluctance to part with his belongings.

“Is that so? Isn’t it too many? I have to exchange all the medicine I have on me!” Han Li intentionally muttered softly.

“This isn’t a lot! After all, this is an elementary high-grade spirit talisman. Think about it, if you had this spirit talisman with you, when you meet any dangers, you can immediately soar far into the sky. You can even fly faster than most of the birds. It’s equivalent to having another chance to live! Furthermore, as long as the talisman’s Spiritual Qi doesn’t disperse, it can be used repeatedly many times. It is truly a useful spirit talisman!” The youth saw Han Li looking like he was going to give all his pill medicine, so he strongly promoted the advantages of his Soaring Sky Talisman and flourished the smile on his face even more, afraid that Han Li would be unwilling and back out of the transaction.

“If we want to exchange, then fine. Give me a dozen of those talisman papers as a treat. That book too!” Han Li added when saw that the youth really wanted his pill medicine, so he straightforwardly pointed at a dozen slips of plain white talisman paper and an old book titled “Manual of Basic Incantations”.

The youth was shocked for a moment, but when he saw Han Li pointed to the low-rank talisman paper and an incantation book that was impossible to sell off, he was immediately delighted and agreed to it.

So this was how Han Li obtained Soaring Sky Talisman and even managed to acquire a dozen slips of talisman paper as well as the incantation book that he had his eye on from the very beginning.

Han Li flipped through the old book. In the book, there were all kinds of most basic elementary incantations, including seven to eight low-grade magic techniques and an elementary mid-grade “Earth Thrust Technique”.

To other Immortal cultivators, this kind of book was worthless, but it made Han Li extremely satisfied.

This was because Han Li was currently lacking in these types of basic incantation techniques. Even though the stall in front of him sold manuals that were better and more complete, their prices were astonishing.

One manual titled “Comprehensive Collection of Elementary Incantations of the Five Elements”[1] was priced at 90 pieces of low-grade spirit stones, and another called “Fundamental Water Incantation Talisman Techniques” was priced at 60 pieces of low-grade spirit stones. Although all these books were thick and contained more incantation techniques, the current Han Li really couldn’t buy them at all.

After obtaining these goods, Han Li felt a little tired and was not in the mood to continue strolling, so he directly exited the plaza and headed towards the pavilion.

Not long after leaving the plaza, Han Li turned his head to look and discovered that there were even more people within the plaza. It seemed like there were many of those night owl-like Immortal cultivators who prefered the nighttime.

When Han Li got closer to these palace-type buildings, he discovered that the towers were actually built using extremely precious paulownia wood and large pieces of limestone. Not only was every floor carved with a picture of dragons and phoenix and was very refinely constructed, there was even a faint fluctuation of spirit power coming from one of the nearby towers. Perhaps it was the restraining technique that Daoist Priest Qing Wen mentioned.

Han Li walked around for a lap, and and after finally finding the pavilion he was looking for, he walked towards it.

But about three meters away from his destination, Han Li suddenly felt like he slammed into something after an invisible immense force abruptly pushed him and forcibly forced him to retreat far back.

Han Li was somewhat startled yet excited. It appeared that there was a lot of things he still didn’t know about in the cultivation world, and he desperately wanted to learn everything.

As Han Li thought about this, his heart beat faster. He used the Heaven’s Eye Technique and gazed towards the small building.

In the end, Han Li saw a faint layer of green light in front of him, obstructing the way. The whole pavilion was covered in the same green light, as if a huge bowl had been overthrown and was covering it.

Han Li stepped forward once again, extended a finger, and lightly jabbed the green light. There was a soft and extremely elastic feeling. Using a bit more strength, there was a faint force that bounced back. The defense power of the green light was quite effective.

Since Han Li managed to understand the effect of the green light, he stopped investigating it. He took out the talisman that Daoist Priest Qing Wen gave him and walked closer towards the light screen. In the end, the green coloured light screen immediately cleared away in ripples. A round hole soon appeared for Han Li to pass through.

Han Li kept the talisman properly and strided in unceremoniously towards the tower. At this moment, the round hole slowly became smaller until it finally closed fully, returning the light screen back to its normal appearance.

The tower in front was not considered to be very big. There were only two stories and was about 33 meters tall. But from the looks of the area of the land, there was plenty of space to spare for ten or more people to live.

Han Li smiled and lifted his leg to enter the building. Upon entering the first floor’s hall, other than the two large eight-seat square table, there were ten wooden chairs with simple and elegant upholstery. There was even a few Immortal cultivators.

The small Buddhist Monk Ku Sang was sitting on the floor at the corner of the hall with his head lowered. His eyes were shut and he was chanting Sanskrit, looking like he was a senior monk. As for the other people, Han Li has not seen them before.

“Master Ku Sang, is Daoist Priest Qing Wen not back yet?” Han Li asked politely as he walked towards the Buddhist monk.

The small Buddhist monk paid no heed to Han Li and continued to mutter some words, until Han Li became impatient with waiting. The Buddhist monk opened his eyes and said to Han Li with a look of apology, “Almsgiver Han, please do not blame me. I was reciting the Diamond Sutra up to a crucial point, so I was unable to reply to your question immediately. Please do not get mad at me!”

Han Li heard the Buddhist monk’s reply and laughed dryly, “How is that possible? I admire focused people the most.”

Hearing Han Li say that, the small Buddhist monk laughed and leisurely said. “Daoist Priest Qing Wen and the others are currently waiting for Almsgiver Han[2] at the second floor. They instructed me to immediately tell you to go up once I saw you. It seems like they are looking for Almsgiver for some matters.”

Han Li became somewhat gloomy when he heard this.

Really! Even though there were people looking for Han Li, this small Buddhist monk not only failed to immediately tell Han Li, he was still so slow and long-winded. In the future, it would be better to be further away from the same type of people as the small Buddhist monk. The further the better!

Han Li silently cursed in his heart, but his face remained unchanged as he nodded his head. He walked towards nearby stairs in the hall and headed up to the second floor.

Upon entering the second floor, Han Li saw the two brothers Hei Mu and Hei Jin talking at the stairway entrance. Once they saw Han Li coming up, they quickly stopped their conversation and welcomed Han Li.

“Brother Han, Daoist Priest Qing Wen is currently waiting for you in the house. Follow both of us brothers to go over there!” Han Li’s expression was calm, and he did not utter a single word. He followed the two brothers around seven to eight turns along the corridor and entered a house.

There were many people in the house. Apart from the Buddhist monk, everyone else was here. There were even two strangers that Han Li did not recognise.

One of them was a 16 to 17 year-old youth, and the other was a 21 to 22 year-old fatty with fair skin. It seemed that these two were the rascals that even caused a headache for Daoist Priest Qing Wen.

“Brother Han is here! Quickly sit!” Daoist Priest Qing Wen said to Han Li as he very politely pointed to a chair beside him.

Han Li nodded and sat there.

“These two people are Yunmen Ravine’s Wu Jiuzhi[3] and Shitou Valley’s Huang Xiaotian,” Qing Wen pointed to the youth and fatty separately and introduced them to Han Li.

[1]. “Five elements” refer to the Five Phases: Wood (? ), Fire (? ), Earth (? ), Metal (?), and Water (? )

[Back]

[2]. TL: ?? Almsgiver or benefactor is a traditional way buddhist monks address others.

[Back]

[3]. TL: ?? (Jiuzhi) means nine fingers. ?? (Xiaotian) means filial piety, sky/heaven

[Back]

Chapter 134: Great Immortal Ascension Assembly

“Now is not the time to talk about some Immortal Ascension Assembly. The topic we should be discussing right now is regarding the issue of our fellow cultivators going missing.” Hu Pinggu said somewhat resentfully towards the youth.

“It’s not a problem. Give Brother Wu a proper explanation. Maybe there are others who are unclear of the details about the Immortal Ascension Assembly.” Daoist Priest Qing Wen said with a smile, but Han Li felt that he was intentionally looking at Han Li.

Han LI’s heart trembled with fear, could it be that Daoist Priest Qing Wen saw through something? Han Li already tried his best to hide characteristics of a new Immortal cultivator and even go as far as to avoid touching certain people. But nowadays, it seemed that it was still unable to be conceal from these certain people’s eyes. This Daoist Priest Qing Wen’s eyes were definitely really fierce.

“Since Daoist Priest Qing Wen said it like that, then I better explain it properly to Brother Wu!” Seeing this, Hei Mu’s spirits were lifted, and he looked like he had a lot to say.

So everyone returned to their original seats once again, except for Fatty Huang Xiaotian.

“I already know about the Great Immortal Ascension Assembly. I will return to rest first, you guys go ahead.”

Fatty said with a cold expression. He did not wait for anyone else to speak and left the house, leaving behind a house full of people looking at each other in dismay.

“Everyone, don’t take offense. Brother Huang’s cultivation art is a bit weird, and he is relatively addicted to sleep. It is not that he intentionally treats people coldy!” Qing Wen, with irreproachable manners, hurriedly exonerated Huang Xiaotian on his behalf.

The majority of the people in the room who heard this all laughed bitterly. Take offense? Who dared to take offense? That person was a powerful man who had more magic power than the Daoist priest!

The atmosphere in the room became somewhat awkward.

“Brother Hei Mu, please continue!” Wu Jiuzhi broke the atmosphere as he urged on.

Hei Mu heard it and laughed, then continued to talk about it.

“When talking about Great Immortal Ascension Assembly, one must mention the Foundation Establishment Pill, the medicine pill that makes all the Qi Condensation stage cultivators go mad.…..”

In order for a Qi Condensation cultivator were to enter Foundation Establishment and become a part of the true cultivating world, aside from cultivating their foundation cultivation techniques to the seventh layer, they still needed to consume the spirit medicine, “Foundation Establishment Pill”, which only major sects could manufacture. Only then would there be hope of breaking through the bottleneck of that realm and succeed into Foundation Establishment.

This contributed to Foundation Establishment Pill’s famous name “Immortal Ascension Pill”, making those Immortal Cultivators go mad.

Even in the Immortal cultivator major factions, the Foundation Establishment Pill was in critically short shortage.

Because the Foundation Establishment Pill’s raw materials were extremely hard to find, even if all the cultivators’ sects throughout the entire state of Yue collaborated and acted together to provide materials and great effort every ten years, they could only hope to make a few new cauldron medicine pills, about one thousand measly pieces.

But even if all these medicine pills were to be divided equally among every faction, there would be no way to satisfy their own needs. As a result, the Foundation Establishment Pill never appeared outside the world of cultivators.

However, in the cultivating world of the entire state of Yue, there were still a lot of existing cultivators who practiced their foundation cultivation techniques until the seventh layer. These people were in urgent need of Foundation Establishment Pills to attempt to break through the bottleneck.

Thus, on one hand, because of the shortage of Foundation Establishment Pills, the big sects had monopolized the medicine pill. On the other hand, there was an increasing number of rogue Immortal cultivators that were in need of Foundation Establishment Pills but could not find a single piece in the outside world. There were already conflicting views from both sides very early on. So much so that at one time, there was deep animosity from short-tempered minor Immortal cultivators towards these sects.

Those from the major Immortal cultivator factions naturally became aware of the poor outlook of the situation, but they couldn’t do anything about it for the time being. After all, they didn’t have enough Foundation Establishment Pill for themselves, so how could they take out some and give them to outsiders!

But in this whole world, there were no difficult problems that couldn’t be solved. Eventually in this crisis, there was an unknown genius from a sect who solved it.

Unexpectedly, he thought an idea. Every time there were freshly manufactured Foundation Establishment Pills, major sects would pick out outstanding rogue cultivators from the outside world, allow them to join the major sects, and give them the Foundation Establishment Pill to consume.

This way, the sects could stem the outflow of Foundation Establishment Pill, thereby preventing manure water from flowing to other fields.[1] This also eliminated the dissatisfaction of minor Immortal cultivators. After all, to be able to join one of the major Immoral cultivator factions, how could these cultivators not be content? The factions could even pick out disciples who have outstanding aptitudes. It truly was a good situation that could satisfy everyone.

But the method of selection must be fair and strict to prevent any disputes caused by gossips. If not, there would be an opposite effect.

Hence, the sects would choose their elites and use arena-style combat to let newcomers strive for the chance to enter their sects.

Each of the Seven Great Sects would take ten disciples and ten pieces of Foundation Establishment Pills to award the final victors.

Naturally, they would set an age limit. Anyone above forty years old would not be allowed to enter. Even though these people may have good aptitudes, their future prospects in cultivation would not be good.

This was how the Great Immortal Ascension Assembly was born!

The majority of the people who were able to obtain victory in the arena were those with profound magic power as well as talented individuals with aptitudes surpassing others, making those Immortal cultivator sects very pleased to obtain these excellent quality disciples.

All the grievances of the other Immortal cultivators disappeared after the establishment of this Great Assembly. All their attention was focused on the once-in-a-decade opportunity to make a big break.

Thus, the Great Immortal Ascension Assembly was organised in this way. And every time there would be 70 lucky winners who became disciples of the Seven Great Sects, making other Immortal cultivators go even more frantic.

At the end, almost all of the Immortal cultivators who were of an appropriate age and were in the Qi Condensation stage felt that they are no weaker than their peers. They would go all out and try a few times to fight on the arena, hoping to gain an unexpected success and transform from a carp into a dragon.

But this arena was not easy to beat since magic was not easy to control for these second-rate Immortal cultivators. Each assembly would have a lot of dead or injured casualties, which also created intense rancor among the challengers.

Hei Mu spent half a day talking about this. Qu Jiuzhi, who was listening with keen interest, gained a lot from this. Han Li, who was sitting beside and listening in, benefited even more from this lecture and had a deeper understanding towards the world of cultivators.

“If I were to succeed, would I also be able to become a disciple of a major sect?” After listening, Wu Jiuzhi’s face was full of yearning.

“Are you dreaming? With your level, you would be dead if you tried to rush and grind even if you weren’t injured!” Hu Pinggu ridiculed without restraint when she heard Wu Jiuzhi’s words of reverie.

“Oh, why can’t I do it? Although my cultivation art is at the eighth layer, am I still qualifications to get on stage and fight?” Wu Jiuzhi did not get angry this time, and instead he consulted with Hu Pinggu.

Hu Pinggu was somewhat shocked, but after hesitating for a while, he said, “Boy Wu, do you know what kind of people were in the seventy winners last time? And how many cultivators, who were of similar caliber as yourself, were injured or dead?”

“I hope Lady Hu would be so kind as to give me a reply.” Wu Jiuzhi replied rather sincerely.

“I witnessed the previous Great Immortal Ascension Assembly’s entire battle, and there’s still some lingering fear when I think about it.” It was as if Hu Pinggu remembered something very frightening, as her complexion turned paler.

When her fully bearded husband saw this, he immediately placed his hand on her shoulder to comfort her. Hu Pinggu turned her head and lovingly looked at her husband, her complexion easing up.

“Both of us don’t want to participate in the single-elimination open tournament, only to look. We are prepared to stay in Qi Condensation forever. Since you all still have ambitious goals, then let me tell you some cruel aspects of the tournament. Otherwise, you will die without ever knowing what happened to you.” Hu Pinggu said indifferently.

[1]. TL: ??????? lit: don’t let one’s own fertile water flow into others’ field , keep the valuables within the family

[Back]

Chapter 135: Frightening News

“First of all, those registering in the competition must have achieved the seventh layer of their Five Elements foundation cultivation technique.[1] This is the minimum requirement to take a Foundation Establishment Pill. Secondly, their age must be less than forty. Those surpassing this age shouldn’t even think of slipping through because those in charge of the great assembly’s registrations are able to use bone observation techniques to look at every participant’s true age.”

“So long as one follows those two conditions, then anyone can register. There are no other restrictions! As a result, however, these open single elimination tournaments become even more desperate!”

“You think that the many people here at Great South Valley are ordinary? The majority of those here actually came here for the Immortal Ascension Assembly. It should be known that the Great South Meeting was originally but a trade meet for the local young cultivators of the Lan Province. During meetings in previous years, there were only several hundred people! Take a look. As of now this valley has at least a thousand people. In addition, people that come from even farther regions will arrive one after another during the last few days. During that time, the business of the Great South Meeting will be at its highest level.”

“These people are the reason why we’ve come to participate in the Great South Meeting early. On one hand, we wish to exchange for a few necessary goods. On the other, how could one not want take advantage of this opportunity? First, one may observe potential opponents of the Immortal Ascension Assembly. It is good to not only know ourselves but also know our enemies!” Hu Pinggu added with a bitter smile.

When Wu Jiuzhi heard this, his complexion greatly changed, and he aghastly said, “According to Lady Hu, there were experts in the valley that cultivated to the tenth layer in their cultivation technique. Will they also participate in the Immortal Ascension Assembly? What is there to compete in? Aren’t those with lower cultivation courting death?”

“This might not be certain. Who said that higher tier experts would always beat those of lower tiers? Even if their magic power is slightly weaker, they can use a somewhat more powerful magic talisman or use some formidable magic tool that they’re carrying to beat down those with greater magic power.” From those who originally entered the room, Hei Jin, who had yet to speak, suddenly spoke out boldly, shocking everyone in the room!

“That’s right, what Brother Hei Jin said makes sense. In a war of cultivators such as ourselves, the slightest deepness or shallowness of one’s magic power is not most important. What is most important is one’s control of their magic might and its agile usage as well as the power they can draw from items they are carrying!” Daoist Priest Qing Wen said, completely agreeing.

“Brother Hei Jin and Daoist Priest Qing Wen’s words must indeed hold some truth, otherwise this Great Immortal Ascension Assembly need not convene at all. They would only have to compare the depth of their magic power.” Hu Pinggu smiled.

After hearing Hei Jin and the others’ words, Wi Jiuzhi still wasn’t happy. With a brow of worry and a face on the verge of tears, he incessantly muttered, “Formidable magic tools… powerful magic talismans….”

Hu Pinggu didn’t take notice of Wu Jiuzhi at this time but instead continued, saying, “Because there are too many people participating in the single elimination tournament, there will be seven stages set up at the Immortal Ascension Assembly, representing the Seven Great Cultivator Sects of the State of Yue. Whoever wishes to become that sect’s disciple, can advance onto the stage to compete. The match selection uses an instant win policy. Two people will compete, the winner will stay for next stage, and the loser will be immediately eliminated. Then another two will have a match. This will continue until everyone competes once. Then they will start the next stage of the competition, which will continue until the final ten remain. These ten will become the cultivation sects’ inner disciples and need not to participate in the sect’s greatly intense competition to obtain the qualifications to receive Foundation Establishment Pills. It could be said to have reached the heavens with a single step! The course of the Great Immortal Ascension Assembly tournament were as such. However, it is is not as simple as I have said. In reality, the matches are a desperate sight to behold and are simply indescribable.” After Hu Pinggu said this, she let out a sorrowful sigh.

“I remember that in the fights from the last competition, there were nineteen tenth layer cultivators who died. Even a couple of eleventh layer experts also met the same end by mutually taking one another down! As for ninth and eighth layer cultivators, those who died during the match were much greater in number. No less than a hundred had died. After all, in the final several rounds, there would be no one that would lightly renounce their path to become a dragon. The number of dead and injured then would be even more tremendous.” Having said this, Hu Pinggu had an expression of regret.

“When one’s foundation cultivation technique reaches the eleventh layer, do they still have to go compete in a match? I’ve heard people say that cultivation sects voluntarily recruit these sort of outstanding talents. Why did those two people have to fight in a match as if their life depended on it!” A woman’s voice suddenly spoke. It was actually the habitually silent young woman, Vagabond Hong Lian, that had spoken.

When Hu Pinggu heard her words, she smiled.

“I also had the same question as Young Sister Hong Lian during that particular year. I was completely puzzled despite a great amount of pondering. Afterwards, I met an old senior that was a rogue cultivator like us. His explanation allowed me to realize why!”

“Brother Wu and Brother Han, it seems you also have this question!”

“They are not the only ones who don’t understand. Us two brothers also don’t understand. Tenth layer geniuses have a well lit path that they do not walk. Why would they possibly want to insist on walking a small wooden plank? A moment of distraction will cause one’s death!” Hei Mu also tensed his brow with a face of puzzlement.

“I see Daoist Priest Qing Wen is calm and composed. He probably figured this out already. How about Daoist Priest come and explain it to them?”Hu Pinggu chuckled several times and lightly threw the question toward the Daoist priest.

This somewhat surprised Daoist Priest Qing Wen but he immediately and silently conceded. After muttering to himself for a moment, he said, “Actually, those two were from cultivator clans. Their eleventh layer cultivation was the result of consuming many medicinal pills.” He shook his head, seemingly disapproving of the two’s methods.

“Is using medical pills to promote their cultivation level not a normal thing? They should still be able to join a cultivation sect!” Wu Jiuzhi widely opened his eyes, somewhat unconvinced.

“Brother Wu forgot one thing. Those who are above forty and have practiced to the eleventh layer in their cultivation technique may be considered geniuses by us, but those ancient great sects see those people as having merely common talents. They would barely qualify to enter the sect as a reserve disciple. Otherwise, these people would have entered the large cultivation sects at an earlier time when they were younger as official disciples. It’s just that their clan members felt that being able to barely enter a cultivation sect as such would have no future prospects. Therefore, they agreed to not compete against those disciples more talented than themselves for the qualifications to obtain Foundation Establishment Pills and simply stayed behind for closed-door cultivation. After several tens of years later, they would simply come out to the Immortal Ascension Assembly to amaze the world in a single feat and immediately acquire the qualifications to obtain a Foundation Establishment Pill through a shortcut. However, their clan hadn’t expected that two with the same plan would coincidentally come across one another, resulting in mutual destruction. Were it not for that, their wishes were certain to have been fulfilled.”

While Daoist Priest Qing Wen said this, he incessantly sighed. Everyone had attentively listened from the beginning.

“I’ve said that recent Immortal Ascension Assemblies have grown more and more intense. Eleventh and tenth layer experts previously unheard of have appeared one after another.” Hei Mu muttered to himself.

Young Lady Hong Lian and Wu Jiuzhi were shocked silent. It was clear that this information had greatly surprised them.

“Think about it. On one side there are great experts meticulously nurtured and fully armed by cultivator clans. On the other hand, there are us: destitute rogue cultivators. Do you think us rogue cultivators are more likely to succeed?”

Hu Pinggu’s expression was cold with slight self-deprecation!

“According to what was said, those cultivation sects obtain the disciples they want through the Great Immortal Ascension Assembly. It is an overjoyous yet phoney affair. Are we slapping our own face to look big and imposing?” Han Li stroked his nose, seemingly in thought.

“Brother Han isn’t wrong. In this world, what is three parts completely beautiful and good? Having two parts beautiful is good enough!” Hu Pinggu threw a glance at Hei Mu, making him faintly blush.

“Could it be us rogue cultivators are truly inferior to disciples of cultivator clans? Even those leftovers from the cultivator sects are that much stronger than us common rogue cultivators.”

“Although I don’t want to admit it, the odds of a master emerging from us rogue cultivators are far lower than that from the cultivator clans. Let alone a single one of us, all of our manpower and resources can not be compared to ours. The conditions outside of a sect are far too lacking when compared!“ Daoist Qing Wen added somewhat bitterly.

“I’ve also heard from a friend that even if we were to luckily become a disciple of a cultivator sect and consumed a Foundation Establishment Pill, the number of those successful in achieving Foundation Establishment is far too low!” Hei Mu said dejectedly.

“Enough, everyone don’t be crestfallen! We are still young. If we are unsuccessful this time, we still have an opportunity in ten years! Perhaps in the future we will enter a cultivator clan as a disciple! For now, let’s talk about how we will gather together after the assembly!”

After Daoist Priest Qing Wen let everyone blew off steam, he changed the subject.

“There is nothing to say. At that time, I will leave with everyone. After hearing about how amazing the people of the world of Immortal cultivators are, I truly wouldn’t dare to travel by myself.”

Daoist Priest Qing Wen helplessly shook his head and looked toward Vagabond Hong Lian.

[1]. “Five Elements”Five Phases: Wood, Fire, Earth, Metal, and Water

[Back]

Chapter 137: Golden Sincerity Brush

“Two spirit stones!” A clear, melodious female voice reached Han Li’s ear.

Han Li was shocked. He discovered that the vendor sitting across from him with their head buried in a book was actually a sweet and charming young lady.

“This book doesn’t have anything missing?” Han Li asked after he recovered.

“Nothing. First through thirteenth layer of the Eternal Spring Cultivation Art is completely there, with not a single missing line.” The young lady answered with an easy-going manner.

Han Li nodded his head. Then he flipped through several pages before closing the book.

“Would you exchange it for medicine pills?” Han Li asked straightforwardly.

“Medicine pills?” The young lady was somewhat stunned, widely opening her beautiful eyes.

“ It depends on the medicine. If it’s for healing or illness, it will be extremely costly!” The young girl spout out as she stroked her forehead.

Hearing this young lady’s words, Han Li knew this matter was of great importance and bluntly handed over a bottle of “Yellow Dragon Pellets”.

“Consolidation medicine, it can progress once’s magic power!” Han Li said assuredly.

“Consolidation medicine?”

The young woman who was originally calm grew somewhat tense. She moved toward Han Li and lightly took the jade bottle. She tossed out a medicine pill and lowered her head to smell the medicinal quality.

Han Li stood above her and clearly saw the young lady’s exposed, flawless neck. In addition, because the young woman was too close to him, the scent of a refined clan daughter assailed his nose and caused Han Li’s heartbeat to involuntarily speed up. His complexion also grew slightly red.

“It truly is a medicine pill that can progress one’s magic power!” A moment after the young woman smelled it, she shouted with pleasant surprise.

She raised her head and looked at Han Li with a happy expression, expectantly saying, “Do you still have more of this medicine pill? If so, I will exchange for how much you have. You can select the things in my stall as you wish. If there is nothing that will do, I can also purchase it with spirit stones!”

With this said, the young woman tightly held the medicine bottle. Her eyes were unblinkingly fixed onto Han Li, afraid that she would hear him say ‘no’.

Seeing the charming and gentle young woman suddenly tense up, Han Li found it funny. However, he could not help but think to himself that he had underestimated the value of this medicine pills a bit. In the future, he should be a bit more prudent!

“Young woman, don’t be anxious. First let’s finish the business before us. Will it be fine to talk about it further then?” Han Li originally thought to refuse her. However, when he saw the clear expression in her eyes, he unknowingly recalled his little sister all of a sudden. His heart softened for a moment and those words slipped out.

“I am truly embarrassed! I’ve somewhat forgotten my manners.” The young woman seemed to have became aware of her lack of manners, and her complexion turned scarlet.

“This book only requires two pills of this kind of medicine.” The young lady said after she calmed down.

When Han Li heard this, he felt the her price could be regarded as fair, so he agreed. Then his gaze swept across the other goods in her stall.

“What is this?”

An unremarkable small grey bag piqued Han Li’s interest. This bag was unusual; the bag’s opening was bound tightly by a thin red rope, and its interior was bulging! Han Li reached out to grab it.

“This is a bag of Seven Star Grass seeds. Seven Star Grass of ten years or more is the best material to create paper talismans.” The young lady clearly said.

Han Li’s heart was moved. This would be quite useful. However, he put it down in front of him without the slightest hesitation.

“The other items seem to be of no use to me.” Han Li slowly said after looking through once more.

“You truly won’t select anything else? This Cold Ice Talisman is quite power. There is also this Returning Spring Talisman, it can restore a great portion of your physical strength…” The young lady was somewhat resigned and took the initiative to give Han Li recommendations.

Having seen the young woman’s “you’re young and naive so you don’t know” appearance, Han Li could not help but laugh.

“What’s so funny?” The young woman blushed once more.

“I actually only wanted to buy cinnabar powder and a brush for drawing talismans. Unfortunately, you have neither here!” Han Li spoke the rarely said truth.

“Cinnabar powder and talisman drawing brush!” The young lady wrinkled her brow and exclaimed somewhat hesitantly.

She lowered her head and muttered to herself for a moment. It greatly seemed that she had made up her mind. Suddenly, she raised her head toward Han Li and said, “I don’t have cinnabar powder, but I have a top quality talisman brush made from the neck hair of the demonic beast, Golden Eyed Ape. However, its price is quite high. I don’t know if you have enough medicine pills to exchange for it.”

When Han Li heard this, he was somewhat amazed. However, he kept smiling and said, “So long as it is good, I will be able to satisfy young lady with regards to the medicine pills.”

When the young lady heard this, she felt relieved.

She took out a spiritual talisman and used her hand to make several cutting motions over the talismans. She then threw it into the air, and it disappeared in a blaze.

“Your esteemed self, please wait a moment. My elder brother will bring it shortly!” The young woman added, somewhat embarrassed.

“No problem. So long as it is truly a good item, I don’t care about waiting for a bit longer!” Han Li calmly said.

After this, Han Li and the young woman had nothing to say during this time, which caused them feel a rather ambiguous feeling.

Han Li actually somewhat indulged in this peculiar feeling and faintly smelled her delicate fragrance as he breathed. The young lady had her head lowered and was looking at the end of her feet. It was unknown what she was thinking. However, when Han Li saw her spotlessly white neck, he blushed a bit.

“Little Sister!” A large voice abruptly shattered the subtle atmosphere, causing Han Li to not help but want to ferociously glare at the voice’s owner. However, when Han Li turned around, he could not help but startled after he clearly saw the figure approaching.

He was a large tall and sturdy man with a stature no less than that of Crooked Soul. He was currently rushing toward them. On the way, he bumped into a few cultivators, pushing them off to the side. Those cultivators were originally angry. However, after seeing the huge man’s far beyond normal stature, they all exposed an expression of shock and hesitated; without a better option, they pinched their noses and let it go.

When the young woman saw the large man’s actions, she had a bit of a headache. Her elder brother’s behavior was far too rude and careless. Did this not give cause and reason for other cultivators to arouse dislike for him?

“This is for Little Sister! I brought the items over.” The huge man was enveloped with a squall as he charged toward Han Li’s side. He extended his hand, which was the size of a palm-leaf fan, and revealed a slender wooden box that he handed over to the young woman.

The young lady inwardly complained about her elder brother’s rudeness and carelessness. Then she handed over the wooden box toward Han Li, indicating that Han Li should open it and examine the contents.

Han Li took the case. After taking a glance at the young woman, he opened the case, exposing a golden brush that emitted a faint yellow light from tip to shaft.

“This brush is called Golden Sincerity. Its tip was created from the neck hair of the grade two demonic beast Golden Eyed Ape, and its shaft was created from a blend of gold essence and crow iron. Then it was refined under a Foundation Establishment cultivator’s well-learned ritual fire for three days and three nights. Only then was this brush successfully completed.” The young woman softly explained. However, this woman stared at the brush with an expression that she was reluctant to part with it.

Although he didn’t completely understand what the young woman said, he knew this brush was not at all ordinary and had a great origin. He couldn’t help but feel amazed that she was willing to part with this object. Could it be for those medicine pills?

“This young woman truly wants to exchange this brush with me? This is an impressive treasure!” Han Li used his finger to lightly stroke the smooth shaft and looked at the engraving on brush’s tip. “Golden Sincerity”, he confirmed with a deep voice.

The young woman saw Han Li’s doubt. After hesitating for a moment, she decided to speak the truth and dismiss the other party’s doubts of the object’s origin, else he dare not trade.

“This brush is an item handed down by my clan. It was used by some talisman creation expert. However, it is unfortunate that us two siblings do not have the slightest talent for creating talismans and would only squander this item in vain. In addition, my elder brother wishes to participate in this upcoming Great Immortal Ascension Assembly. His cultivation arts have already reached some sort of bottleneck and must break through with the support of medicinal power. As a result, I wish to use this object to exchange for your esteemed self’s medicine pills.”

“How is it that when I met you, the man’s cultivation had reached a bottleneck! Isn’t this too timely?” Han Li thought with doubt.

Actually, Han Li thought incorrectly!

Of those in preparations for the Immortal Ascension Assembly’s competition, seven to eight out of ten were stuck at a bottleneck and were unable to break through. Because each and every person understood that they still had potential to push forward to another layer, they would not likely immediately participate in the Immortal Ascension Assembly’s tournament, but rather hide away and continue painstakingly cultivating, hoping to reach a further layer. When they would participate in the next great assembly, they would break through and hold a higher position in the assembly. This caused every Immortal Ascension Assembly to have an amazing demand for medicine pills that progressed ones magic power.

Chapter 140: Determination to Win

“You…” The man seemed to be extremely angry. His two hands formed fists, and he advanced a step.

“What? Could it be that you’re thinking of forcing the trade? Those of our Ye Clan aren’t good targets to bully!” The vendor turned his eyes and said without a trace of politeness.

“Humph! The Ye Clan is quite impressive!” Although the dark man did not apologize, he released his fists. He was clearly afraid of retaliation from the Ye Clan.

The man was suppressed by the mere mention of the Ye Clan and was exceptionally angry. He was a tenth layer expert and was accustomed to others speaking highly of him. Currently he had accepted this embarrassment and had planned to brush his sleeve then ago. However, in his heart, he would truly hate to part with this “Returning Winds Alms Bowl” as this magic tool was well-suited with his cultivation art. If he were able to acquire it, his strength would increase greatly. However as of current, apart from the destroyed magic treasure fragment, his other possessions were quite useful, and his spirit stones had been used up over the past several days, leaving him in his current predicament.

“Brother, sell your treasure fragment to me, I will give ten spirit stones.” A grey-clothed man that was watching emerged from the crowd. He sincerely said, cupping his fist in front of the man.

“I won’t sell it! If you want to buy it, then give me thirty spirit stones.” The dark man shook his head as if he were beating a drum with it. That price was fundamentally unacceptable.

“ Sigh. Your esteemed self’s destroyed magic treasure fragment, if it were only a slightly great price, then it would be worth it. Unfortunately, it is truly too small. The amount of goods it can conceal is too few!” The grey-clothed man, having been rejected by the man, exposed an expression of regret and returned into the crowd without further negotiation.

“Would you sell it for twelve spirit stones?”

“Thirteen?”

……

Cultivators from all directions were looking at the destroyed magic treasure fragment with great interest. Even if they couldn’t use this item, they could slowly study it! Who knows what they would be able to achieve enlightenment in!

Like that, the price rose to twenty after a moment, bidded by a naive-looking, round-faced youth.

In face of such a high price, others no longer spoke out. They all felt this price was quite high. If the were to grow any higher, it would be far too damaging! After all, to these low level cultivators, having ten spirit stones would be regarded as quite well-off. In addition, the man from a moment ago was most likely the disciple of a clan. Only they could possibly be that rich!

“Twenty?” The dark man’s expression changed. The bid had reached his minimum! If he were to pair it with a few other objects, he would be able to exchange with the vendor for the “Returning Wind Alms Bowl.”

“You want to pay twenty spirit stones?” The man amiably said toward the round-faced youth.

Although nobody knew why, after a moment, the youth’s face was red. Then after another moment, his face turned white, and he became extremely frantic.

“I…. don’t…. have that many spirit stones!” After the round-faced youth stammered these words with frustration and unease, the surrounding spectators were shocked.

“You don’t! They why did you just yell that? Could it be you said it to deliberately amuse me!” When the dark man heard this, the man’s belly full of anger erupted out from his body, rigidly pressing down onto the youth with formidable grandeur.

“I simply saw everyone shouting out prices for fun! Without thinking, I also opened my mouth! Brother, please forgive me!” The round-faced youth hastily apologized to absolve himself. His brow was beaded with sweat, and soybean-sized sweat-drops tumbled down. He was merely a fifth layer cultivator; how could he resist such spiritual pressure!

“Who just shouted nineteen? I am willing to freely give a spirit stone to allow your esteemed self to purchase this item!” The youth resourcefully yelled at once.

Unfortunately, those all around were extremely quiet. It seemed that person had already changed their mind!

“How about the brother who shouted eighteen!” When the youth say the dark man’s increasingly scornful face, he nearly wept. He was an insignificant, young cultivator. He only had two spirit stones on him, acquired from a year of bitter labor.

Just as the people thought they were about to see quite a good show, “Wait a moment!”, a relaxed voice suddenly sounded out. A person entered the stage, calling out to the dark man.

“What do you want?” The black man looked at the person with a gloomy face. His temper had already been ground to dust. If this person wanted to have a feud, he wouldn’t mind taking them both out. Although this person was not weak, he was only of the ninth layer!

“This person has taken an interest in this item and desires it!” That individual pointed at that “cloth” and said with a smile.

The one the dark man had mistaken to be a cultivator looking for a fight was not a bystander, but Han Li.

Originally when Han Li heard this person say that this destroyed magic treasure fragment could turn things invisible and conceal Spiritual Qi, his heart was stirred, and his mind formed a vague opinion.

By the time the dark man had concealed the knife, Han Li’s opinion in his mind grew clear. He became determined to possess this destroyed treasure fragment.

“How much will you purchase for it?” The dark man was surprised, but a moment later, his expression eased as he asked this question.

“This person does not plan to purchase it, but rather use this object to exchange for it.” Han Li calmly took out a talisman from his sleeve, allowing those surrounding the stall to clearly see it.

“A flight talisman!” A few knowledgeable people cried out in alarm!

“It’s an elementary high-grade spiritual talisman!” The other cultivators were awed. After all, elementary high-grade talismans had only appeared five or six times since the beginning of this Great South Meeting. In addition, each and every one of them had been sold at astonishing prices!

Chapter 141: Writ of Immortal Ascension

With a look at this flight talisman, the dark man and the vendor stall owner were visibly moved. Their view of Han Li grew much more serious. After all, those possessing elementary high-grade talismans were unlikely to be a nobody.

“Good, I will exchange!” The dark man was very straightforward. With such an obviously advantageous trade, who wouldn’t trade?

“However, before we trade, I wish to try something you have said before, whether or not this treasure fragment will obstruct a concealed object from absorbing the Spiritual Qi from the outside world. If it is true, this person will immediately trade for it. If it is not true, this person will not take the loss and trade!”

When the dark man heard Han Li’s words, he was surprised. However, after clearly hearing the content of his words, he smiled.

“The words I have spoke regarding this object’s effects are all true. Please do not hesitate to test it!” The dark man confidently spoke.

When Han Li heard this, he was was not polite. He took out a object resembling a wine cup from his body. He then picked up the ‘cloth’ and covered it. Waiting until after the wine cup disappeared, Han Li extended his finger and condensed a white ball of Spiritual Qi the size of a bean. He lightly dropped it on the cloth, resulting in the ball of light completely disappearing, as if it were swallowed.

When Han Li saw this, his face showed a happy expression. He lightly grabbed the ‘cloth’ in his hand and removed it. The wine cup appeared, and ball of light that disappeared a moment ago was flowing inside.

“Not bad! Brother did not speak falsely. I want this destroyed magic treasure fragment. As for this flight talisman, it belongs to your esteemed self!” Han Li took the ‘cloth’ and put it in his cuff. Afterwards, he cupped his fist toward the dark man.

“Good! Your esteemed self is straightforward.” When the dark man heard this, he was exalted and lowered his body to take the flight talisman. After he hastily looked all over it to confirm it wasn’t fake, he smiled.

Han Li faintly smiled and did not say anything further. He turned around and squeezed through the crowd. However, before he even took a few steps, he heard several comments from the crowd.

“This man is foolish! To actually trade a high-grade talisman for such a weak item!”

“That’s right. That fragment is so small, what use does it have? To exchange for such a thing is fundamentally not worth it!”

“Don’t say it like that, maybe he has a clever use for it!”

……

When Han Li heard this, he inwardly sneered several times. ‘How could these cultivators know that this object is of immense importance to me?’

“This brother, please wait! Wait for me!” Having not walked very far, Han Li heard a voice from behind him, approaching him in a hurry.

Han Li was slightly surprised. Could they be yelling him? He could not help but turn his head.

He saw a person not too far away, running towards him with a forehead beaded with sweat while calling out to him. It was unexpectedly the round-faced youth who had nearly brought disaster upon himself.

Han Li blinked a few times and then stopped. He curiously wanted to know what business this buffoon would have with him to have pursued him at the very end.

“Brother, I’ve finally caught up to you!” The youth chasing him said while gasping for breath.

“Does this brother have something on his mind?” Han Li looked at him with doubt.

“This is for you! It could be considered thanks for Elder Brother’s help out of the troublesome situation.” Without saying anything further, the youth handed Han Li a booklet. Then he bashfully ran back.

Han Li was slightly surprised, but he immediately smiled. There was such a simple and honest person among the cultivators. This was truly unexpected. He did not pursue him, and instead he took a look at the book in his hand.

“Record of Qing Xi”[1] was the book’s title. It didn’t seem to be a magic item. Han Li looked through a few pages with interest.

It seemed to be the journal of a senior cultivator “Daoist Master Qing Xi” of the State of Yue who did not like cultivating but instead enjoyed travelling to different places. It contained allusive legends and such with detailed notes. There were also some pages with relevant vivid and lifelike drawings. Although Han Li only looked through a few pages, he held quite an interest in this item and put the booklet into his bosom.

After that Han Li didn’t come across any particular affairs. He felt a bit bored and returned to his residence. Inside his room, Han Li lied down on his bed and looked through “The Record of Qing Xi”.

Of the contents in the book, a few were Master Qing Xi’s personal experiences and others were merely gossip. However, not one of them wasn’t bizarre. There were rarely heard unusual matters and secrets that cultivator clans would never tell others. It was unknown how Master Qing Xi had learned of them.

Han Li read with great interest. However, when he reached the final page of the booklet, there were the drawings of seven distinct command medallions. At the very bottom of the drawings were several lines of words: “Writ of Immortal Ascension”, created by the Seven Great Cultivator sects of the State of Yue. It was the each cultivator sect’s award for accomplishing tremendous achievements within a cultivator sect. So long as one holds the cultivator’s sect command medallion, they would receive the same treatment as the final victor of the Immortal Ascension Assembly! It would bestow the qualifications to become an inner court disciple and receive Foundation Establishment Pills. However, this object had always been handed down within the sect. Common cultivators would have no chance of seeing them. As a result, these portrayals were simply according to their appearances from rumors.

At the end, Master Qing Xi used somewhat smaller characters to write these words: this writ can be traded between cultivator clans. The age when writs were first issued was a time long ago. As a result, the cultivator clans that issued writs recognized the writs but not the people! So long as someone holds a writ, they would take a step toward the heavens. It could be said to be a low level cultivator’s defiance of the natural order!

After Han Li finished reading the explanation below, he took another look at the seven illustrations and felt his tongue dry up. His heart beated with intensity.

Originally when Han Li heard the words “Great Immortal Ascension Assembly”, he faintly made an association with the dwarf’s strange command medallion. One side of the command medallion had two words engraved: “Immortal Ascension”. This made Han Li feel as if these two things had something in common.

After he heard the others talk about the Great Immortal Ascension Assembly in detail, there were no words relating to the Writ of Immortal Ascension. He believed this to be no more than a coincidence and left it in the back of his mind. However, he didn’t expect the booklet he unexpectedly received to have the object’s origin and true use. In addition, the function of this Writ of Immortal Ascension was this great!

Han Li grew more and more excited, hastily taking out the black command medallion. After briefly comparing it with the illustration, he found it to be grealy similar to its design.

“‘Yellow Maple Valley’, This Writ of Immortal Ascension was issued by the Yellow Maple Valley!” Han Li muttered to himself as he stroked the command medallion in his hand.

“However, how did this precious item enter the hands of a lowly cultivator like Monk Golden Light?” Han Li doubtedly thought after calming down.

In fact, that dwarf was truly the previous owner of that command medallion!

It turned out that in the outstanding and famous Qin Ye Mountain Range, apart from the Ye Clan, there was also another equivalent Clan that resided there, the Qin Clan. Because those two clans had many intermarried relationships, they got along quite well!

This Writ of Immortal Ascension was an object passed down from the ancestors of the Qin Clan. However, they did not use it because the Qin Clan could no longer find a genius cultivator who deserved the writ! That was why they would rather continue to pass it down and were unwilling to waste this treasure for no reason.

However, after many generations, because the males of the Qin Clan grew more sparse, they gradually declined. In contrast, the Ye Clan grew even more prosperous and developed. They influenced the cultivation world so much that everyone knew that the Qin Ye Mountain housed the Ye Clan, while the Qin Clan became forgotten!

During Monk Golden Light’s generation, he was actually the sole remaining male from the Qin Clan, and his aptitude was strange and lacking. He fundamentally could not possibly achieve Foundation Establishment. Because of his aptitude, the large difference in strength between the two clans, and the fact that their relationship as in-laws was a matter long expired, the Ye Clan decided to acquire the several treasures of the Qin Clan. In addition, that Writ of Immortal Ascension was the treasure they wanted to possess to most!

Although Monk Golden Light’s cultivation talent was lacking, his ability to read body language was actually quite good. With the fact that he was also cowardly, just as the Ye Clan had planned to make a move, the dwarf, having caught wind of this earlier, had already fled, taking a small sword talisman and the Writ of Immortal Ascension. As for the other treasures, because they were sealed away, Monk Golden Light could not acquire them in a short amount of time and was forced to reluctantly abandon them, setting them aside for the Ye Clan.

As a result, Monk Golden Light had been on the run for over ten years, and lived in seclusion in some Daoist temple deep within the wilderness. He relied on his shallow magic power to plunder drink and food and became free and unfettered. After a period of time, he had thought to use the Writ of Immortal Ascension, but that notion had gradually weakened. He reached the conclusion even if he were to take the Foundation Establishment Pill, he would not be able to achieve Foundation Establishment. Since that was the case, there was no need to go to a large cultivator sect as a low level disciple and suffer hardship!

Like that, after the assault on the Seven Mysteries Sect, Han Li had conveniently acquired this Writ of Immortal Ascension.

[1]. TL: Qing Xi ?? means Young Creek

[Back]

Chapter 143: Beheading

The large man that had just emerged from the ground and the yellow-clothed man started to chase after Han Li.

As they chased him, they were afraid that Han Li would run far away again. After recovering a bit of magic power, they immediately grouped up and planned their next attack.

At this time, Han Li felt a scorching pain from his wounded thigh. It seemed that his movements from a moment ago had worsened his injury.

However, now was not the time to think about that problem! The large man that had concealed himself in the ground a moment ago took out a long saber covered in black Qi and fiercely charged toward Han Li.

When Han Li saw his opponents’ figures, he observed that although they were quite fast, their movements were stiff. It was clear these people only relied on the support of magic techniques. His heart could not help but slightly relax. It should be known that Han Li’s strange and quick movements would prevent them from catching up to him!

With that thought, Han Li no longer paid attention to the large overbearing man and placed his attention onto the yellow-clothed man instead, as the man had taken out a dark green gourd. He had pointed the mouth of the gourd toward Han Li, seemingly wanting to cast a magic technique!

“Where do you think you’re looking? Die!”

The large man charged next to Han Li with a greatly flourished yellow light on his body. He lifted his demonic long saber and chopped it down toward Han Li.

Han Li snorted. His body flashed, appearing outside the reach of the saber.

“You were fooled, boy!” The large man wildly laughed.

A black light from the long saber in his hand flashed, and turned into a long black rope. Like a long snake, it closely followed and twisted toward Han Li, neither locking him down nor letting him go!

Han Li was startled, and his body immediately grew strangely indistinct. One moment he was at the left, then right, then front, then back, as if there were several Han Li’s encircling the large man.

When the large man saw this, he grew greatly intimidated. However, he immediately protected his body with the “Earth Armor Technique” and no longer paid it any attention to Han Li’s afterimages. Instead, he hastily moved his flexible black rope and did his utmost to pursue Han Li’s true body.

Pengpeng. Pengpeng. Han Li swept past the side of the large man. During that instant, he fiercely shot fireballs at the large man with both hands around him. As they hit his body, the yellow light shook for a moment. Unfortunately, it recovered at once.

“How could this meager Fireball Technique break through this Uncle’s defensive technique!” The large man’s face was savage, and the movement of his hands grew even more rapid; the movements of the black rope didn’t relax even the slightest.

Han Li felt somewhat anxious! Although the large man’s black rope was somewhat slower than him, he was unable to cope with it. His dared not slow down his body’s movements, else he was certain to be caught. Although he didn’t know what sort of magic tool the black rope was, it was quite troublesome! However, he didn’t dare to negligently let it wrap around him!

He busily glanced toward the yellow-clothed man and saw that his expression was solemn. The magic tool gourd in his hand started to release a secretive azure light. It was unknown what would about to emerge from within!

“This won’t do. If this continues, I won’t be able to survive! If I don’t brave a few risks, I will die!” Han Li thought to himself, having seen the desperate circumstances.

As a result, Han Li rushed to take out the guardian talisman he received from Monk Golden Light. This Guardian Talisman was a type of talisman technique. Its incantation had long been acquired from Buddhist Monk Ku Sang. Now he had finally used it.

Han Li softly chanted the incantation verses. Because he was in the middle of moving, it sounded somewhat ambiguous. However, the talisman’s golden characters started to brighten. When the golden characters were completely shining, Han Li suddenly slapped the talisman onto his body. A golden light suddenly appeared and covered his body with a golden barrier. However, his body suddenly became slower, and the black chain overtook him and wrapped around him.

The usage of a Guardian Talisman caused one’s movements to slow. Han Li had already tested this and was well aware. Although the black rope wound around him several times, when it was obstructed by the golden light, he did not panic! He knew that his gamble was correct as the golden barrier protected him against the magic tool’s assault.

When the large man saw this, he let out a low roar. He charged forward with large strides, with obnoxious, dazzling yellow light on his fists. They seemed to be supported by an unknown cultivation technique.

Having learned a lesson from last time, Han LI did not let the large man get close. He suddenly crouched and pressed both hands against the floor. Then he muttered an incantation, suddenly causing his hands be slightly enveloped in a yellow light.

When the large man saw this, he was slightly startled and hastily stopped. However, it was already too late. The floor below him completely turned into soft and weak quicksand, causing his legs to be deeply buried to his thighs and to become flustered.

“Strike!” A sharp voice entered Han Li’s ear.

Han Li’s heart sunk as he looked toward the yellow-clothed man.

With only a single look, Han Li saw seven to eight black spheres the size of chicken eggs emerge from the mouth of the black gourd and rush toward him.

Han Li’s face grew very unsightly, and the yellow light in his hands scattered. He then took out a wooden box from his bosom.

At this time, the several spheres were already in front of him and ruthless pounded against Han Li’s barrier. The barrier was incessantly deformed, as if it could break at any moment.

Han Li didn’t take notice of this crisis and sat down cross-legged, putting the wooden box on his knee. He then rushed an incantation.

Pengpeng! Pengpeng! Pengpeng! The spheres’ attacks were fierce and didn’t cease attacking the golden barrier for even a moment, causing the golden light to gradually dim. It seemed the barrier would break and that death would approach.

At this time, Han Li shouted with a roar, “Rise!”

With this order, a gray light about three meters long shot forth from within the wooden box. This ray of light resembled a flood dragon that had emerged from the water; it flew several circles and all directions, and hacked all of the spheres into two one after another as if they were its nemesis, turning them to dust.

“Treasure talisman!” The yellow-clothed man loudly shouted as if he had seen a ghost.

When Han Li heard this, his heart stirred. However, he did not think of it further as the large man had already escaped from the trap. However, after seeing Han Li’s gray sword light, his complexion grew deathly white! Not only did he not think to rush toward Han Li, but he also turned around and wildly fled.

Thought at this time, Han Li was already resolved to kill. How could he let these people leave? He pointed to the large person, and the sword light immediately and fiercely pursued, appearing behind the large man’s body.

It coiled around the large man’s neck and his skull easily tumbled to the ground. It was as if the yellow light protecting his body didn’t exist, not affecting it in the slightest.

When the yellow-clothed man saw this, he had actually dared to stay there for the moment. He took out a talisman and slapped it onto his body, causing him to spout out a pair of large yellow wings. He lightly flapped them and soared off, flying to a distant place.

Han Li then commanded the sword light to pursue, closely following behind the yellow-clothed man. The yellow-clothed man flew even faster, and the grey light was unexpectedly unable to overtake him for a time.

Han Li felt slightly anxious, and his heart grew fierce. He then used all of the magic power he had without reserve. It was as if that grey streak had immediately consumed a tonic and suddenly sped up, piercing through the chest of the yellow-clothed man and thoroughly bringing peace to Han Li’s heart.

The yellow-clothed man screamed and fell from the air.

Han Li grew greatly cheerful and recalled the gray light. He dashed toward the man, hoping to capture him alive and carefully interrogate him.

Unfortunately when Han Li arrived at the crash site, the yellow-clothed man couldn’t possibly be any more dead. He simply fell to his death, causing Han Li to be quite depressed!

Since there were no living mouths, he could only search the two bodies and see whether he could find any useful clues.

After Han Li impolitely plundered all the items on the two men’s bodies, he did not find any relevant items. Even so, he struck it rich! These two men actually had fifty low-grade spirit stones as well as a few talismans and magic tools!

Han Li could not make head or tails of their assault and was somewhat puzzled. He also did not know whether or not these two had anything to do with the missing rogue cultivators. However, he didn’t dare to stay here too long. After consuming a few medicine pills, he continued on his way.

Chapter 145: The Unexpected Guest

“That’s right! Senior Martial Brother Wu truly has a good idea!” The old man surnamed Ye’s two eyes shined with excitement.

Then he turned his head to Zhong Lingdao and expectantly requested, “Sect Master, could I see the owner of the Writ of Immortal Ascension? I wish to do business with him and exchange something for his voluntary renouncement of the Foundation Establishment Pill!”

When Zhong Lingdao heard this, he muttered to himself hesitantly before nodding. However, he reminded the old man that he mustn’t overstep his boundaries and force the transaction before letting Junior Martial Brother Wang see the uninvited guest.

The old man and Junior Martial Brother Wang exited the main hall. After stepping on a leaf-shaped magic tool, they immediately soared into the sky toward Yellow Maple Valley’s guest-welcoming building.

In a room of the Yellow Maple Valley’s guest-welcoming building, a youth was lying on a bed, looking at the roof while lost in thought. He was precisely Han Li who followed them to Yellow Maple Valley after the Great Immortal Ascension Assembly’s conclusion.

After Han Li had killed the two cultivators who ambushed him, with no further external encounters, he hurried to some hidden mountain peak in the Lan Province to participate in the Great Immortal Ascension Assembly that was soon to convene and compare what he saw with the desperately fought tournaments described by Hu Pinggu.

After the life-and-death contests, with each stage having a final victor, the Seven Great Sects’ representatives finally emerged. Yellow Maple Valley’s representative was that Junior Martial Brother Wang.

After having seen Yellow Maple Valley’s representative and taking a moment of careful deliberation, he still resolved himself to take the risk and hand over the Writ of Immortal Ascension for this man to see, causing the representative to be startled.

The representative immediately stated that he could bring Han Li back to the sect. As for the specifics towards him and the Writ of Immortal Ascension, it would be the decision of their Sect Master. After all, regaining the Writ of Immortal Ascension was a matter four to five hundred years overdue!

Han Li was naturally unopposed, otherwise he would have to find Yellow Maple Valley’s mountain entrance by himself. It would be far too exhausting for him.

Like that, the other cultivators looked at Han Li with gazes of amazement. He sat on an immense boat-shaped magic tool with ten victors from the tournament and the representative Junior Martial Brother Wang. When he returned to Yellow Maple Valley, he was brought here to wait for a reply. As for the other ten, they had parted. It was unknown where they had gone.

Han Li waited here for three to four days and did not leave his room. Aside from an eleven to twelve year-old male servant delivering him food every day on schedule, he did not see anyone else.

It wasn’t that Han Li was actually obedient and sincere, but after that representative surnamed Wang arranged his living conditions and tested his spiritual root attributes, he immediately told him that because he still wasn’t a disciple of Yellow Maple Valley, the room would have a few restrictive techniques. For the time being, he would be unable to leave the room, otherwise he would trigger the restrictive techniques, causing him to be restrained.

Having heard the representative surnamed Wang, Han Li naturally did not bring embarrassment upon himself. In addition, after having become aware that he possessed four attribute false spiritual roots, Han Li mood took a turn for the worse.

Although Han Li already knew that his own cultivation aptitude was rather poor, after hearing it with his own ears, he became sad and dispirited for an entire day. It seemed that if he wished to remain on his path of cultivation, he would have to rely on the external power of medicine pills and such.

However, after he ascended to the ninth layer of the Eternal Spring Arts, he felt the effectiveness of “Yellow Dragon Pellet” and “Golden Essence Pill” greatly lessening. They did not aid him as greatly as before. It seemed he must find several other spiritual medicine recipes and concoct some medicine pills truly fit for a cultivator, else the pace of his cultivation would be delayed.

Just as Han Li was immersed in thought, the sound of footsteps came from outside the door. In addition, it was the sound of not just one person. Han Li roused his spirit. It seemed that after suffering through several days, the information he was waiting for had come.

“Young Friend, have you become accustomed to living here?”

The room’s door softly opened, and the voice of the representative named Wang spoke. This man soon entered the room, followed by a blushing old man.

“Greetings, Immortal Wang!” Han Li immediately jumped from the bed and respectfully greeted him. He was fully aware that nobody would find fault with extra courtesy. Were he to humble his attitude a bit, he would only receive benefit and no detriments.

“This is…?” Han Li glanced at the old man and asked, puzzled.

“This is my Senior Martial Brother, surnamed Ye.” Junior Martial Brother Wang smiled and then explained.

Surnamed Ye? Han Li was startled. Could it be that the matter of having taken the writ after killing Monk Golden Light was revealed? Was it the Ye Clan member who sought him? However, although this old man’s complexion wasn’t too good, he did not have the appearance of great anger. It seemed he had some other mysterious reason. Han Li felt apprehensive, though this was not expressed in the slightest on his face. With the same respectful tone, he said, “So it was Immortal Ye!”

The old man sized up Han Li once through. How could Han Li look and feel so terribly ordinary? There wasn’t anything the slightest bit out of the ordinary. He couldn’t help but feel uncertain toward his purpose coming here.

As a result, after he heard Han Li’s greeting, he put on a gracious face and smiled, saying, “Hehe! Young Friend Han need not be overly courteous. Since Young Friend Han arrived to our Yellow Maple Valley holding the Writ of Immortal Ascension, Young Friend is already a sect disciple. Calling me Martial Uncle Ye will suffice; you need not regard yourself as an outsider!”

After Han Li heard the old man’s words, his heart greatly lightened. However, his mind was still somewhat unconvinced.

Since the other party had spoken so politely, it seems he did not have a vendetta against him. Though, wasn’t this level of politely a bit too excessive? How could he be said to not be an outsider! Han Li was at a loss.

“Young Friend Han, Senior Martial Brother Ye did not speak wrongly! The current Sect Master had already agreed to allow Young Friend to become a sect disciple. In addition, a Foundation Establishment Pill has been prepared for Young Friend!” Junior Martial Brother Wang said with a light smile.

“Truly?” When the always steady and calm Han Li heard those words, he could not help but grow excited. He wished he could dance for joy and vent his feelings.

Seeing Han Li act in such a manner, Junior Martial Brother Wang smiled. He did not feel very surprised; it seemed he had already predicted Han Li’s reaction!

“Junior Martial Brother Wang, I wish to speak with Martial Nephew Han alone. Could you withdraw for a moment?” The old man had grown somewhat impatient and finally spoke what he wanted to ever since he entered the room.

“Of course, this Junior Martial Brother will return to sect master first. After Senior Martial Brother and Martial Nephew Han finish speaking, come back together!” Junior Martial Brother Wang inwardly sighed. After giving Han Li a faint glance, he left the room.

At this moment, the only two remaining in the room were old man Ye and Han Li.

Han Li was stunned at what had happened before him. How could this one surnamed Wang just walk away after being told? The one left along with him, the fellow calling himself Martial Uncle, what matter does he have to speak with him! Although he didn’t know what this Senior Martial Brother Ye was up to, Han Li had a faintly bad premonition.

The old man saw that Han Li was uneasy, but he didn’t care in the slightest. He was convinced the things he could put forward were certain to cause this youth inexperienced with the world to widely open his eyes and smoothly complete the transaction.

“Martial Nephew Han, Martial Uncle is a straightforward person, therefore I will not beat around the bush and openly say it! My business is related to your given Foundation Establishment Pill. I wish to purchase it from Martial Nephew. What does Martial Nephew think about it?” The old man got right to the point.

‘He actually wants to purchase my Foundation Establishment Pill! Did he not mishear? How could he sell it to someone else!’ When Han Li heard this, he was shocked. However soon after, his complexion greatly changed and became unsightly.

“Martial Nephew Han, do not hesitate to be at ease. I will not offer nothing in exchange for Martial Nephew’s Foundation Establishment Pill. Seven or Eight mid-grade spirit stones, a few elementary mid to high grade spiritual talismans, and several kinds of first-rate magic tools. Martial Uncle still can bring out more things. If these truly won’t do, Martial Uncle still has a few magic power progressing medicine pills. Although they are incapable of being compared to a Foundation Establishment Pill, they are spiritual medicines hard to come by even in the sect.” The old man hastily explained after clearly seeing Han Li’s complexion change.

After Han Li heard these words, his complexion was much better. He heard the sincerity in the other party’s words. It seemed this Martial Uncle had no intention of harshly and unreasonably scramble to rob him. Indeed, he truly wished to buy his Foundation Establishment Pill.

Chapter 148: Old Man in Gray

Martial Uncle Wang took Han Li with him on a leaf-shaped magic tool and flew for a couple of hours. They landed on a lush verdant mountain range, within an area crowded with flat houses. These shabby houses were built using rocks from the mountain, and there wasn’t a single person inside these houses. They seemed like they were all empty, and this puzzled Han Li!

“Don’t be surprised. These houses are truly empty. This place is meant for the new disciples to live in until they improved their magic power, then they will move out and look for somewhere else to live. It happens it is currently the beginning of the ten-year rotational cycle . The new disciples haven’t joined the sect yet, so the houses are temporarily empty,” Martial Uncle Wang spotted Han Li’s confusion and explained softly. This cleared Han Li’s bewilderment.

Martial Uncle Wang led Han Li the way as they walked among houses, making so many turns that Han Li felt dizzy. Then they finally stopped at a house that was larger than the other normal stone houses. He didn’t explained much to Han Li and started yelling loudly, “Junior Martial Brother Lin, open the door. I brought a new disciple to pick up the items!”

As soon as Martial Uncle Wang finished yelling, the door opened outwards automatically in a whoosh. Seeing this, Martial Uncle Wang walked in without any hesitation. Han Li paused a little, and followed him into the house.

Inside the house, it was more spacious than it looked outside. This amazed Han Li, wondering what the house was tempered with.

But the specific situation inside the house gave Han Li a certain feeling, and it was the word “messy.”

All kinds of different items were piled here and there. Some were clothes, some were weapons such as knives and swords. But from the wave of spiritual power the weapons were giving off, they seemed to actually be pretty well-made magic tools.

Aside from these things, there were also some other daily items such as shovels and hammers. Those items were also giving off strong spiritual power, it seemed like the items had been. refined into something like a magic tool. This broadened Han Li’s horizons. What kind of special effect did these tools have?

At the center of the house, there was an eight-seater square table. Facing the door and sitting behind the table was an old man in gray clothes with fluffy hair. The old man ignored them as the two of them walked in the house, instead being focused on a small shiny knife, carving a yellow wood about the size of his palms that he held in his hands.

Martial Uncle Wang saw this, he frowned slightly, but his facial expression turned back to normal immediately. He didn’t walk up and interrupt the old man working, instead he pulled a chair from the corner of the room, sat across the old man, and waited quietly for the old man to finish carving the wood.

Han Li blinked his eyes when he saw the situation and stood behind Martial Uncle Wang without saying a word while waiting sensibly with him.

The old man in gray was moving his hands fast like the wind while wood chips fell from in between his finger. After merely the time it took to make a cup of tea, a life-like little monkey appeared within his palms.

“Junior Martial Brother Lin’s carving skills have improved a lot since the last time I saw you!” Martial Uncle Wang just then complimented while smiling.

“It’s nothing impressive. I had nothing to do, so I was just killing time! How come Martial Brother Wang has the time to come and visit my humble residence?” The old man in gray said carelessly, but his eyes were already looking straight at Han Li and seemed to have guessed what the two of them were doing here.

“It’s nothing too important, just wanted to get the equipments that all new disciples who join the valley’s sect would receive for this Martial Nephew Han,” he smiled and answered.

“Didn’t all the new disciples from the Immortal Ascension Assembly receive their equipments? How come there’s another one? And his aptitude is so poor! Did our Sect Leader Zhong’s standards really became that low, he would recruit someone so untalented into the valley!” The old man in gray said bluntly right in front of Han Li, making Han Li sound completely useless. From his tone of attitude, it doesn’t seemed like he respected the Sect Leader Zhong as much either.

Hearing this, Han Li naturally felt extremely awkward, and Martial Uncle Wang was also smiling bitterly.

He knew that because of what happened back then, this Junior Martial Brother Lin had been holding a grudge against their Senior Martial Brother, the Sect Leader, ever since. But in front of this junior, Han Li, how could he possibly pick on the young!

So, he coughed a little and changed the topic, “Junior Martial Brother, this Martial Nephew Han was the one who brought the Writ of Immortal Ascension and joined us in the Yellow Maple Valley! It counts as an exception, so his aptitude is not important. What’s important is that the sect needs to keep our promise.”

“The Writ of Immortal Ascension!” The old man in gray was very surprised and looked at Han Li once again.

“Tsk tsk! If you say so, then this fellow must have a lot of luck, and he can take a Foundation Establishment Pill?” The old man said with a loud voice and looked at him with a look that said, ‘fellow, you’re truly a lucky b*stard!’

“Hehe, normally that would be the case. But Martial Nephew Han and Martial Brother Ye made a deal, and he gave up this Foundation Establishment Pill automatically,” Martial Uncle Wang smiled and mentioned.

“Gave up the Foundation Establishment Pill?” The old man was startled at first, but for some reason his expression darkened right away, and after a moment of silent, he said something that surprised Han Li.

“It’s a good thing he could give it up! The most important thing about being human is knowing your limits. Knowing what to give up and what to take at this young age, this quality is a lot stronger in him than in me!” The expression of the old man in gray seemed to be incredibly lonely. The expression in his eyes, which were originally cold, became more kind.

But after Han Li heard what the old man said, he was confused and didn’t take it to heart!

‘Knowing your limits? That was because I had no choice, so I gave up the precious Foundation Establishment Pill! If it weren’t so, who would give it up!’

Without Han Li mentioning the complaints his heart, the old man suddenly put on a straight face and stood up. He used his hands to lightly and continuously claw at the space around them. An item suddenly appeared in his hand, and the items kept increasing. The whole process stunned Han Li.

“A Yellow Silk Shirt, a Azure Leaf Magic Tool, an everyday refinery set, one Fierce Sun Sword and Cold Moon Saber each, and a tenfold storage pouch,” The old man listed all the items in his hands coldly and put them on the table.

“The items are all here. Little fellow, take them away! As for Martial Brother Wang, who is a busy person, I will not ask you to stay. Please see yourselves out!” After saying this, the old man took out another piece of wood from his chest, started sculpting once again, no longer paying attention to the two of them.

Seeing this, Martial Uncle Wang sighed, stopped saying anything else, and told Han Li to pick up the items. As soon as the two of them walked out of the stone house, the door automatically closed up with a loud bang!

Martial Uncle Wang looked at the shut door and shook his head. He then prepared to leave the place with Han Li.

“Oh! You don’t have to carry that many items in your arms, just put them in your storage pouch!” Martial Uncle Wang turned around and saw Han Li carrying everything in his arms, standing like an idiot beside him. His foolish look amused him, so he spoke to remind him.

After Han Li heard what he said, he put the things in his arms on the ground and found the black cloth pouch among the items. “This is the tenfold storage pouch?” Han Li was a little confused!

He picked up the pouch, looked at the incredibly small opening, and then looked at the enormous swords and items. He hesitated a little since he didn’t know how to stuff them in the pouch.

“This is your first time using a storage pouch, so let me demonstrate!” Martial Uncle Wang was understanding. After he recognized Han Li’s confusion, he reached over and took the pouch.

“All you have to do is aim the opening of the pouch at what you want to put in, inject some magic power into the pouch, and focus on the item. It will be sucked in automatically!” Martial Uncle Wang said as he demonstrated it himself.

He pointed the opening downwards, and the white light in his hand flickered. A bright, white light shot out from the pouch and covered everything that was on the ground. Those items immediately shrunk under the white light, and as soon as they reached a certain size, they were sucked into the pouch. Han Li, who was watching on the side, was surprised and amazed!

“You use the same method when you want to take out an item. You just have to focus on the item that you want to take out with your magic power beforehand,” Martial Uncle Wang said as he returned the pouch to Han Li.

“But there are a few rules when it comes to using the storage pouch. Martial Nephew Han, you must remember them carefully!” Martial Uncle Wang put his hands behind his back and spoke seriously.

Hearing this, Han Li nodded like a chicken pecking rice.

“Firstly, the storage pouch can only hold and shrink a certain amount or size of items. If the pouch sucked in something that’s too big or too many in quantity, it will lose its ability, and you won’t be able to put more items inside of it anymore.”

“Secondly, the storage pouch cannot store living things. If you put a live creature inside it, then it will die for sure!”

“Lastly, and also the most important rule you must keep at heart: Low–grade storage pouches do not have the ability to recognize their owner, so whoever steals your storage pouch can take the items inside! Hence, don’t reveal your storage pouch easily in front of other cultivators. You should hide it carefully, or else you could get into serious trouble.”

Chapter 153: Yue Lu Hall

Han Li stood on a stone platform halfway up the Great Shaman’s Mountain. About ten meters wide, the stone platform was a huge Immortal’s abode entirely covered by a spell formation: Yue Lu Hall.[1]

This “Yue Lu Hall” was the Yellow Maple Valley’s specialized storage for magic tools, medicine pill recipes, and secret technique manuals. In addition, it offered all sorts of assistance for pill and magic tool refining as well as a few common raw materials. It could be regarded as one of the most important places in the sect. Thus, not only was it covered in many layers of spell formations, but it was also patrolled by over a hundred disciples in case outside enemies invaded. It was also said that there was a Core Formation martial ancestor secluded within, keeping watch all year in case other great experts were to invade this place.

After Han Li went over the relevant information in his mind, he calmly walked forward.

Just as he landed, there were several gazes that sized him up from a secret location. However, upon seeing Han Li’s magic power was ordinary, they quickly vanished. Even if it were merely that, Han Li was secretly startled.

Since Han Li was unable to respond to these people, they demonstrated that they either had first-rate concealment magic tools or their magic power was truly above his, which meant that they were elite disciples of the twelfth layer or above. How could this not cause Han Li to be even more cautious!

After walking forward several steps, he stopped. Then he softly chanted several verses and raised his hand, releasing a stream of red light toward the seemingly empty space in front of him.

As a result, the empty space fluctuated for a moment, and a wall of light appeared with a flash of red light, blocking him. Immediately after, two disciples wearing red clothes appeared behind the wall of light.

“Were you the one who triggered the restrictive spell?” A red-clothed disciple coldly asked.

“This one is Han Li, I…”

“Do we care who you are? Since you haven’t reached Foundation Establishment, you need a sponsor! Bring out the token of trust of one who vouches for you! ” The disciple explained, impatiently interrupting Han Li.

After Han Li heard those impolite words, he did not angry. He took out a jade talisman from his bosom and set it down on the ground in front of the wall of light.

At this time, the cold-mouthed red-clothed disciple held his hand again wall of light. A hole the size of a hand appeared in the wall.

The other red-clothed disciple who had yet to speak lightly waved his hand, causing Han Li’s jade talisman to fly like a small wing through the hole and into his hand.

“Senior Martial Brother Ma is your sponsor?” The red-clothed disciple who looked at the jade talisman exclaimed, somewhat astonished.

“It truly is a token of trust that Martial Senior Ma has given to my humble self.” Han Li honestly replied. However, he was shocked from his heart. The age of these two red-clothed men weren’t very old. However, they were actually Foundation Establishment experts. This had greatly shocked him!

It should be known that in a cultivation sect, status was not determined by seniority. Status was determined by the depths of their cultivation. After all, the path of cultivation could only be tread by the strong!

“That Senior Brother Ma who is obsessed with refining pills all day?” The red-clothed disciple at the side asked in surprise.

“That’s right, he even vouches for people? This is truly shocking! Are you his personal disciple or a blood relative or something else entirely?” The red-clothed disciple holding the jade talisman, repeatedly asked with curiosity.

“No, this junior simply takes care of his medicine garden on Martial Senior Ma’s behalf. For this token of trust, this disciple has agreed to look after the garden for free for a year!” Han Li currently didn’t dare to slight them and respectfully replied with a bitter smile.

What he said was completely true.

Actually, when Han Li began to plan to acquire pill recipes, he thought that because this Martial Senior Ma planted so many medicinal herbs, he would have conducted a great amount of research on pill concoction. He was certain to have many medicine pill recipes on hand! That was why several months before, Han Li took advantage of the period when the small old man arrived to take the medicine ingredients and made a few indirect inquiries.

The result caused Han Li’s eye’s to become foolish-eyed. When the small old man heard these words, he immediately shook his head as if he were beating a drum with it. Regardless of what Han Li said, he was rejected. According to this Martial Senior Ma, his pill recipes were the results of the experience of a pill refining master’s countless failures. How could he possibly give them to others that casually? It was unconditionally impossible!

However, when Han Li earnestly explained that he only wanted those original, unaltered pill recipes, the small old man looked at him and impatiently told Han Li in a blunt manner to go to Yue Lu Hall and find them himself. Why should he be inconvenienced in such a way to help him? Like that, Han Li was forced to work a year for free in exchange for the small old man’s token of trust and was able to presently come to Yue Lu Hall.

“Hehe! It turned out to be like that. I was under the impression of the rumor that Senior Brother Ma’s temper suddenly changed!” After the two red-clothed men listened, they looked at each other with a smile. These words were spoken with a snicker by the one holding the jade talisman.

“Alright, you may enter!”

The red-clothed men simultaneously cast a spell on the wall of light, causing the wall of light to rigidly squeeze open a three-meter-wide passage. It was just enough for one person to pass through.

When Han Li saw this, he hesitated for a moment. Then his figure immediately flashed, and he was within the wall.

After he entered the wall of light, something caused him to become greatly surprised.

When he was outside, because of the red wall of light’s obstruction, Han Li was not able to see the interior. Now that he was inside, apart from a small circular spell formation, he saw that the mountain was unexpectedly bare; there weren’t any buildings at all, causing Han Li to be incomparably puzzled!

“Take care of this jade talisman. Every time you come here, there will be a routine inspection. That is the rule here.” After they released their spell on the wall of light, the person who examined the token of trust returned the jade talisman to Han Li.

“Many thanks to these two martial uncles!” Han Li withdrew his curious glances and saluted as respectfully as he could. He hoped to give these two men a good impression of him. After all, he would be returning here often in the future.

“En, follow me!”

It was obvious Han Li’s inclination was not in vain. These two’s expressions grew much more mild. After all, the majority of those who came here were disciples of the same generation. Naturally they wouldn’t be as overly courteous as Han Li, causing the two to have a favorable impression towards Han Li.

“However, Martial Nephew Han, why did you want to come to this Yue Lu hall? Regardless of whether one is starting to refine pills or magic tools, it would be best to wait until one is Foundation Establishment. You’ve come here a bit too early!” One of the red-clothed men asked. At this time, these two men were bringing Han Li towards the circular spell formation.

“This junior simply witnessed Martial Senior Ma refine many pills. He also saved a few raw materials while caring for the garden. That was why he wished to test his luck and see whether or not he may find a suitable recipe to refine a few medicine pills to progress his cultivation. After all, Martial Nephew’s aptitude is truly poor and can only rely on external power.” Han Li replied half truthfully, deliberately falling behind the two people half a step.

“So it’s like that! However, Martial Nephew shouldn’t be too hopeful. After you enter, you will understand my meaning.” The other man lightly shook his head, not very optimistic of Han Li’s goal.

At this time, the three had already walked in front the circular spell formation. Then a red-clothed person indicated Han Li to stand in the middle of the spell formation. The two stood to the left and right of the spell formation.

“Usually, the use of this transportation formation requires the payment of a low-grade spirit stone. However since it is Martial Nephew’s first time, we will exempt you this time. Next time, however, we will be completely acting in accordance to the rules.” One of the men said with a weak smile.

Just as those words were uttered, the two men each released a stream of red light toward the spell formation in an extremely practiced manner. Then the several spirit stones imbedded in the formation shined brightly.

Without having the chance to thank the two, he suddenly felt the sky spin and saw his surround scenery to become, indistinct. Then a brilliant light flashed and Han Li arrived in an unfamiliar hall. He was currently standing in a spell formation exactly like the one he had used before.

‘So this was the rumored transportation formation. Truly wonderful!’ Han Li inwardly exclaimed in astonishment. After his feelings of discomfort from the formation faded away, he swept his gaze across the large, extraordinary hall.

[1]. TL: ?? Yue Lu of Yue Lu hall, means the base of a tall mountain

[Back]

Chapter 157: Murong Brothers

After Han Li left the Yue Lu Hall, he said goodbye to the two people in red and flew towards the Hundred Medicine Garden with his magic tool.

In the air, Han Li kept thinking about refining the Foundation Establishment Pill, while looking down at the continuous hills with indifference. Suddenly, a loud, rumbling burst came from beneath and surprised him. He couldn’t help but take a closer look…

Only to see lightning flickering on one of the hills, and there were some faint applause coming from there. It brought up Han Li’s curiosity; he landed from his magic tool nearby and automatically started to get close to the source.

“Murong Brothers, another one, show us what you’ve got!”

“That’s right. This is the first time I saw the shape of lightning that closely, it’s so frightening!”

…

As soon as he arrived at the top of the hill, Han Li heard a noise coming from the front, and the name ‘Murong Brothers’ moved his heart.

“The genius brothers with thunder spiritual roots who just entered the sect, isn’t their last name ‘Murong’! The loud burst from before…are these brothers, the focus of so much attention, demonstrating their skills?”

At this moment, he saw clearly that there were about thirty to forty disciples of varying ages on a hilltop, huddled in a loose circle and pointing to two eleven or twelve year-old youngsters in the middle of the circle while talking excitingly.

There were several charred pits within the circle. The edges of the pits were melted because of the high temperature, and they released light cyan-blue smoke. After a breeze blew by, the burnt smell was everywhere.

Seeing this scene, Han Li hastily went over and looked carefully at the youngsters. The two of them had delicate features, fair and tender skin, and they looked very similar. However, when they blinked their eyes, they looked like little elves.

At this moment, because of the crowd’s attention and praise, the two of them were blushing with excitement. After they looked at each other, they chanted a spell at the same time, and lightning flashed in the hands of the two, followed by two thin bolts of lightning flying out. They landed on the ground nearby with two loud bangs and a burst of bright, white light, creating two more pits in the ground.

“This is the thunder attribute’s Thunder Palm? Regardless of its power or sound, this was more powerful than the Fireball Technique, Icicle Technique, or other magic techniques that are of the same level. Thunder attribute magic techniques are indeed the most destructive magic techniques!” Han Li was astonished and also envious of the brothers’ spiritual roots attribute.

Obviously, Han Li wasn’t the only one with this mentality. The other disciples who were watching them were also looking at the two with envious looks, while hating themselves for not being blessed by the Heavens with this kind of high-grade attribute that made everyone jealous!

The brothers demonstrated their thunder spell a few more times among the crowd of applause, but their strength were clearly starting to fall behind their will. After all, they were still too young.

“That’s it? It seems the power of thunder spiritual roots is merely this. I say it’s probably not even as good as my wind spiritual roots!” Just then, a lousy man’s voice sounded from the crowd across where Han Li stood, and the surrounding people couldn’t help but look in that direction.

A young man and woman were standing together side by side. The man was tall and handsome, and the woman was beautiful like a flower. They were obviously a pair of couple who were madly in love. That man looked proud, and seemed to be dismissive of the Murong Brothers’ Thunder Palm, and the woman was blushing because so many people were looking at her. Her reddish face was even more charming.

“Who is this man? He’s so wild!”

“Wind spiritual roots? Isn’t that also a type of mutated spiritual roots! This man has mutated spiritual roots?”

“I know this man. He is Senior Martial Brother Lu, and he indeed has mutated spiritual roots. His wind spells can be very powerful!”

“Even if he also has mutated spiritual roots, why is he saying things like this?”

“Maybe it’s out of jealousy! After all, back then among the low-level disciples, he was the only one who had mutated spiritual roots. But now, there are suddenly two more who are even more qualified than he is. Of course he would feel unbalanced!”

“What? So narrow-minded!”

“Hush! Be quiet, don’t let him hear this. He’s very vengeful. Being targeted by him would be very terrible!”

…

Because of the young man’s appearance, everyone around were whispering together. It appeared that this person wasn’t that popular around here.

“Hmph! Little fellow, I will show you what real mutated spiritual roots are!” The young man’s face sank when he saw people discussing him like this. He walked into the circle and declared proudly, “The two of you, feel free to attack me with your thunder spells. If I dodge for even a half step, I will kowtow and admit my wrongs to you two little demons!”

Seeing Senior Martial Brother Lu being so arrogant and looking down on them for no reason, the Murong Brothers were so mad that their faces became pale.

“You’re not gonna dodge?”

“Of course.”

“And no magic tools allowed?”

“Yes.”

The two brothers were indeed biological brothers. They each added a rule favoring them and finalized it. The young man was also arrogant, so he didn’t even take the two brothers seriously and accepted their conditions without any objections.

“Good, then us two brothers will take care of Senior Martial Brother!” The two teenages said angrily in unison.

“Senior Martial Brother Lu, will you be okay like this?” The young man’s female companion started to worry.

“Hehe! What’s there to worry about dealing with two kids? Martial Sister Cheng can rest assured!” The young man waved his hand indifferently and stood in front of the Murong Brothers in an ostentatious manner.

The two youngsters looked at each other, and suddenly came close together. They each held out their hand and took each other’s hand, while the other finger pointed to the sky. Together, they chanted the same exact spell!

Seeing this, the young man sneered, and casted a defensive spell onto himself. A cyan-blue mask immediately surrounded him, and wrapped him tightly inside.

“Thunder Chain Strike.”

The biological brothers finally finished casting their spell, and they pointed their finger at the top of the young man’s head. A dark cloud about the size of ten meters appeared above him. A white light flashed in the cloud, and a lightning bolt as wide as a finger landed on the cyan-blue shield. The lightning hit the shield so hard that the shield shook violently, and the young man’s expression changed. Apparently the power of the lightning was out of his expectations.

But this lightning-shock was just the beginning. From the dark cloud that was floating in the air, more of the same lightning attack fell and hit the shield until it flickered and grew dark, on the edge of breaking apart.

The young man’s expression darkened again, as he suddenly made some complicated, dazzling finger gestures, growled deeply, and pressed his hands tightly against the light shield wall. The light mask suddenly glowed in blue. Not only was it repaired, but it also seemed to be even thicker than before.

But the Murong Brothers naturally wouldn’t give up the advantages that they possessed, so they also sent a variety of spells up into the air and made the dark cloud expand until its diameter was about ten meters. The falling lightning grew thicker and more frequent.

Faced with the two brothers’ fierce attack, this Senior Martial Brother Lu was even more surprised and angry, and he didn’t know what to do. He never expected them to grasp the elementary mid-grade Thunder Chain Technique at such a young age. He was hit so hard he couldn’t withdraw from the fight, and he could only cast counterattack spells. He suffered at such a disadvantage in front of so many people.

Just like that, the youngsters on one side were using all their strengths to support the dark cloud’s lightning attack, and on the other side, the young man was struggling to keep casting defensive spells to reinforce the cyan-blue shield. This competition turned into an unexpected tug of war.

Normally, if one side attacked and the other defended, the attacker would naturally have a greater advantage, and they could save a lot more magic than the defender. However, the Murong Brothers who were attacking had already used up a lot of magic power during the demonstrations just now, and they didn’t have enough magic power from the beginning. Also, the young man surnamed Lu was a lot older after all, so the maturity of his magic power couldn’t be compared to those that had just entered the sect like them. By fighting a battle of attrition, they had their backs against a wall.

Under everyone’s sight, that dark cloud released the last few bolts of lightning and then dispersed, leaving a clear sky. Depleted of magic power, the youngsters were forced to first stop the lightning.

Chapter 160: Trial by Blood and Fire

After Han Li heard his well-meaning advice, he could not help but casually agree. Afterwards, he asked about the Foundation Establishment Pill medicine ingredients.

“Junior Martial Brother Han wants to know the source of Chalcedony Mushrooms and other spiritual medicines?” Wu Feng asked, astonished.

“That’s right, Senior Martial Brother has already been at the sect for many years. He should know something about this!” Han Li asked expectantly.

After Wu Feng heard this, he murmured to himself for a moment and said, “Naturally, I know a bit. However, I urge Junior Martial Brother to bury this thought! Not only is the place incomparably dangerous but it is also fundamentally impossible to approach. Only during a specific time and place and with the assistance of the Sect Elders would you be able to enter.”

When Han Li initially heard that Wu Feng knew something, Han Li was delighted. But the following words alarmed him and caused him to question it closely.

So it turned out that these spiritual medicines had been scarce in the cultivation world for a long time. They simply disappeared from common regions. The sole places where they could currently be found were those so-called forbidden areas.

Since they were capable of being called forbidden areas by cultivators, these regions must naturally be extremely dangerous. They were generally vile environments located in desolate places. Some were demon lairs and could only be reached by a journey of slaughter. There were also locations with a few ancient restrictive spells that required a great deal of effort to break through them.

For Yellow Maple Valley and the other cultivation sects, all of their Foundation Establishment Pill medicine ingredients previously came from one forbidden area. That location was continuously sealed by an ancient wind attribute restriction.

The restrictive spell was quite impressive. Originally, no matter how much strength the cultivator sects used, they had no hope of opening it. However, though it was unknown how, someone had actually later discovered that this restrictive spell had a five-day period of weakness every five years. During this time, if several Core Formation experts simultaneously used force against the restriction, they could create a temporary opening and let a certain amount of people inside.

However, once the opening appeared and the cultivators tried to go in, something unexpected occurred.

Those of Foundation Establishment and greater were all hindered by another eccentric restriction. But those of Qi Condensation were not obstructed in the least and were able to collect and bring back a great amount of rare spiritual medicines.

This discovery caused a great commotion in the cultivation world of the State of Yue. As a result, the Seven Great Cultivator Sects would dispatch disciples below Foundation Establishment into the forbidden area to gather a great amount of spiritual medicines. Naturally, the Foundation Establishment Pill medicine ingredients were of the highest priority.

At the start, the disciples of cultivation sects could harvest without assault. After the first harvest, the chosen disciples all said that this was a very comfortable task. However, with each passing harvest, the spiritual medicine within the forbidden area gradually grew more sparse, causing each sect to dispute over the wondrous medicines. Greater actions began to continuously occur until several hundred years ago, when a disciple lost his life in the struggle.

The first loss of life caused each of the large sects to completely tear off their faces and bluntly fight; the weak were prey to the strong. The Heavens and Earth favored none, and the sects encouraged their disciples to pillage from others, causing the forbidden area to be thoroughly stained with the color of blood.

Like that, the spiritual medicines gradually decreased, and the fights within the forbidden area grew increasingly fierce and bloody.

In the last hundred years, due to the great brutality of close combat, less than one third of the disciples who entered the forbidden area were able to come back alive. Each of the sects’ loss of junior elite disciples was not small! This caused each of the sects’ disciples to call the forbidden area the “Trial by Blood and Fire”. One by one they began to avoid going. One time, there was even an awkward scene where not a single person wished to enter.

As for forcing people, that was naturally out of the question.

If the disciples didn’t sincerely enter the forbidden area to search for medicines, then they were certain to work halfheartedly. A majority of them would hide and wait until it was safe before leaving.

This hadn’t previously happened before, causing the upper echelon to seethe with anger. However, they had no alternative. After all, these people were originally unwilling to go. Being forced to brave those strange dangers, how could they possibly be criticized for not being willing!

As a result, each of the sects in the State of Yue steadily watched the spiritual medicines with increasing interest. However, the amount of disciples willing to accept the risks were very few; thus causing the sects to start using heavier rewards to recruit disciples to enter the forbidden area. Those who brought back spiritual medicines from the forbidden area would be given even greater rewards, attracting much attention.

The other sects did not say this, only Yellow Maple Valley did!

Several times after the tradition began, the sect directly stipulated in writing that so long as a disciple registered to participate, they would be bestowed a mid-grade spirit stone and spiritual tool beforehand to serve as encouragement.

As for those who were truly capable of bringing spiritual medicines from the forbidden area, the sect would further reward them according to the quality and quantity of the medicines. From spirit stones and spiritual pills to magic tools, all that one could think of was possible, even secretive rewards as great as a Foundation Establishment Pill. This was sufficient for low level disciples to stake it all.

These great rewards naturally caused the cultivation sect to experience a great surge of registrations for a time. This surge was maintained for the next two to three times and then completely declined.

The bloody reality caused the many disciples to wake to the realization that these great rewards did not come without cost!

Because of the initial excitement over the great rewards, the original survival rate of those who fought in the forbidden area actually lowered from less than one third to less than one fourth after the introduction of greater rewards. Of those who survived, those capable of bringing out spiritual medicines were even fewer, and the majority of them were gravely injured. They fundamentally didn’t reap any rewards, not to speak of even recieving a Foundation Establishment Pill.

This was what Han Li was told after asking Wu Feng about the source of the spiritual medicines.

After hearing everything he had to say, Han Li felt nothing except depression!

He didn’t expect that gathering some medicine ingredients would require going to some forbidden area and, moreover, engaging in close combat with the disciples of other sects. Only by being the final victor would one be able to leave. Furthermore, the rate of survival was astonishing. Less than one fourth of the disciples were able to leave this so-called, “Trial by Blood and Fire”.

The hazards one would have to brave were far too great! Han Li wasn’t some expert. Among the low level disciples of Yellow Maple Valley, he was merely of medium strength.

As a result, without profound magic power and no powerful magic techniques, he could only rely on their several magic tools and his mind’s quick wit.

Relying on just this, how could Han Li believe himself to be one of the four that survive?

This caused Han Li to become angry, and he could not help but ask Wu Feng, “Why doesn’t each Immortal sect restrict their disciples and collaboratively divide the spiritual medicines? It should be known these medicines will inevitably be refined into Foundation Establishment Pills. Isn’t there no need to quarrel and tear into one another, thereby planting the seeds of hatred and revenge?”

After Wu Feng heard this, he immediately replied with a bitter laugh, “Junior Martial Brother does not understand. Although they will all be used to refine Foundation Establishment Pills, the distribution of the number of medicine pills would completely depend on the spiritual medicines available. Under these circumstances, how could they not do their utmost to fight for the spiritual medicines?”

After Han Li heard this, he remained silent for a long while.

Finally, with a belly full of worry, he asked about the next “ Trial by Blood and Fire ” and found out that it was in half a year. After several warnings from Senior Martial Brother Wu, Han Li left the Cultivation Guidance Pavilion and returned to Hundred Medicine Garden.

Over the course of the next few days, Han Li dispiritedly thought of this matter, repeatedly pondering about the stakes and risks involved. He attempted to compel himself to pick the more sensible option.

It was clear that in the State of Yue, apart from this forbidden area, these three spiritual medicines would not be found. Otherwise, the Seven Great Immortal Sects need not shed blood every five years and cripple themselves.

If Han Li did not want to brave these strange dangers, he could only hope to find the spiritual medicines in regions outside the State of Yue. Else, he would be completely without hope of achieving Foundation Establishment and become a pile of bones within a hundred years. However, after a careful thought, he knew that leaving the country to look for spiritual medicines was even more hopeless.

However, if he truly participated in the “ Trial by Blood and Fire ”, the three-fourth death rate was far too large! At that point, his possibility of death was immense! This truly caused Han Li to feel bewildered!

Chapter 162: Myriad Treasures Store

Yellow Maple Valley’s market city looked like Han Li’s hometown, Green Ox City. The entire market was only one street that pointed north and south. In the south, there were dozens of houses of various sizes. Some were tall, some were short. Some were buildings, while others were just huts. It was very inconsistent and uneven.

These were all industries of the Yellow Maple Valley, but only less than half were personally managed by Yellow Maple Valley’s disciples. The other large half was leased to the cultivator families and rogue cultivators who usually dealt business here. Most of these businesses were stores that traded raw materials, talismans, and magic tools. There was also a five elements bookstore that specialized in selling elementary spells, and there were two restaurants and inns that were convenient for people to get food and rest.

Aside from the lower level disciples at the market city, there were also a number of Foundation Establishment experts who stayed there regularly, keeping order in the city and preventing people from causing trouble.

A large portion of the northern part of the street was empty. It was reserved for cultivators who wanted to set up a shop on the spur of the moment. As long as they paid the Yellow Maple Valley disciples with a low-grade spirit stone, foreigners could set up a shop for a whole day on the side of the empty street without any interference. They would even have the protection of the disciples during the time that they had set up a shop, enabling them to have no fear of any enemies who would want to take revenge.

With these measures encouraging foreign cultivators to come here and do business, along with the special geographical location of the market city, the Yellow Maple Valley’s market city had been prosperous for many years. There would even be rare items that would appear from time to time in the market city, attracting even more cultivators.

However, because Han Li wanted to avoid arousing suspicion, he didn’t enter the market city from the convenient south street entrance. Instead, he circled around and entered from the north. Before setting foot into the street entrance, he covered his face with a blue cloak in case there was anyone here who could recognize him.

It was already the afternoon. The street of the market city didn’t seem to have many people at a first glance. However, this was normal. After all, this market city was not some secular world downtown market that would be noisy all day long. The people who were qualified to come here were unique cultivators; you would only find one cultivator in ten thousand people! It was already pretty good to have this many people.

Han Li mocked himself a little after realizing this fact and walked towards the small shops on the side of the street. He decided to see if there was anything worthwhile in the small shops before going to the large stores.

After going through all the small shops, Han Li’s heart sank. The magic tools and talismans at these small shops were completely useless to him, with the exception of three or four items that could barely be considered passable. Buying them would only be a foolish expense, so he stopped wasting his time. He turned around and sprinted towards the large stores.

“Seven Opportunities Pavilion.”

“Wind Guiding Study.”

“Heavenly Crafts Store.”

……

…

This time, Han Li didn’t recklessly find a random store to walk into. He took his time and slowly strolled along the street. After he familiarized himself with the name, size, and type of each store, he picked the one that looked the largest and frequently had cultivators streaming in and out: Myriad Treasures Store. He went inside.

From simply hearing the store’s name, one could tell that the owner of the store was confident of his goods, so Han Li hoped to find some rare treasures here and not leave empty-handed.

Han Li slightly hesitated as soon as he entered.

The bright hall was large enough to accommodate dozens of people without feeling crowded. There was an extraordinarily long front desk, built with precious Red Aleurite wood, and seven or eight servants in blue uniforms. All of this gave off an impressive atmosphere of grandeur.

In the hall, two of the servants in blue were explaining something to a few people who looked like customers.

Inside the counter, there was a large variety of items. From the style of the items, it seemed like they were things that only cultivators would use. From the lowest grade raw materials to the commonly used talismans and magic tools, the Myriad Store had everything.

Han Li smiled. It seemed like he had really found the right place.

At this moment, a servant in blue came over and said with a big smile, “Esteemed customer, what are you looking for? Do you want me to help introduce you to something? This store’s goods will definitely satisfy all of our customers’ needs!”

“I want to look at magic tools and talismans, but I only want the best. Do not show me inferior goods!” Han Li spoke softly through his cloak.

The servant in blue was slightly stunned by this remark, but then he carefully looked and judged Han Li’s manners. After making sure he wasn’t joking, the smile on his face grew even wider. He knew he must be a big customer, so he quickly invited Han Li in and personally led him to the VIP room on the second floor.

The furnishings upstairs were different from the decor downstairs. Not only was the scale of the second floor a lot smaller, but there were some antique furniture on the second floor. It was decorated in an elegant, comfortable, and cozy manner. The most surprising thing was that there was a precious incense burner and a bundle of burning incense in the corner of the room that filled the room with a faint smell of sandalwood.

A gentle-looking, middle-aged man holding an old book was standing in the room, reading its contents aloud. He seemed to not have any magic power like a completely ordinary man.

Han Li was somewhat stunned. This place did not look like a place to do business. Instead, it looked like some rich person’s home. The person who was reading saw Han Li come in and calmly closed the book. The servant in blue who had escorted Han Li quickly walked up to the man and whispered a few words.

After the middle-aged man finished listening, he cupped his hands and said with a smile,

“I am Myriad Treasures Store’s shopkeeper, Tian Buli. How should I address you?”

“Li Feiyu,” Han Li unceremoniously borrowed his good friend’s name.

“Oh it’s Brother Li. Brother, please sit down!”

The middle-aged man led Han Li to sit down, then ordered the servant, “Go brew a pot of our best Jade Cloud Tea!”

After Han Li sat down, the middle-aged man started asking politely. “This is the first time Brother Li came to this store, right?”

“Hehe! Shopkeeper Tian is really observant. This is indeed the first time I have visited this store.” Han Li deliberately changed his voice and made himself sound like a tough man with a deep voice.

“It doesn’t matter if it’s your first time visiting this place. As long as you are willing to come here, it shows your favour to our Myriad Treasures Store. This store will definitely satisfy Brother!” Shopkeeper Tian confidently said.

“I wouldn’t want to go through the trouble of going to multiple stores if I could just find all the items I need at one store! I hope this store’s goods are really exceptional,” said Han Li in a dubious tone.

“Hehe! Brother Li can rest assured about that. Our store’s credibility is definitely one of the best on this street. If this store can’t satisfy Brother, then there’s no need to bother checking out the other stores!” said the shopkeeper unhurriedly, exuding confidence.

At this moment, a serving maid came upstairs with a teapot and several teacups. The refreshing smell of tea filled the room before she had even approached the two of them.

Shopkeeper Tian waited for the serving maid to set up the tea set and took a sip first. While smiling, he said, “This is a special tea made here in the store. It’s rare in other places. Not only does it smell refreshing, but drinking it can make people energized. Brother Li can give it a taste.”

Han Li looked at the fragrant tea in front of him. He shook his head lightly and said in a slightly impatient tone,

“Shopkeeper Tian, we can drink tea later. First, let’s get down to business!”

“I never thought Brother would have such an impatient personality! Very well! Please wait a moment, I will be right back!” Shopkeeper Tian stood up with a slightly disappointed expression. He cupped his hands towards Han Li and went downstairs, leaving Han Li alone.

After approximately the time to brew a cup of tea had passed, Shopkeeper Tian once again appeared before Han Li. However, this time he was carrying a few brocade boxes that were in different sizes.

Shopkeeper Tian patted the brocade boxes and spoke with a grin. “I heard that Brother Li wants the best magic tools and talismans from the servant downstairs, so I went downstairs to the collection room and brought up a few pieces of treasure that I have collected for a long time for Brother to see. I hope Brother Li is happy with them!”

Han Li’s eyes widened when he heard this. He was very curious about the content in the brocade boxes. He wondered what rare items they would have to be in order for them to be called treasures by the shopkeeper, and whether or not the content would be above his expectations.

Shopkeeper Tian had already placed the brocade boxes on the table and opened each of them for him to see. However, Han Li noticed that as soon as the brocade boxes were opened, two magic pressures that were definitely stronger than him came out of nowhere and tightly locked onto his every move.

Han Li was surprised at first, but quickly understood that this was a security measure that the Myriad Treasures Store had employed to secure the treasures in case he were to suddenly steal the items inside the brocade boxes. He then relaxed and had a deeper understanding of the Myriad Treasures Store’s ability.

Chapter 165: Night Encounter

After hearing Shopkeeper Tian’s explanation, Han Li had a better understanding about the treasure talisman. He couldn’t help but look at the treasure talisman inside the brocade box once more.

“This store bought the Golden Light Brick treasure talisman from a small family for a substantial price. It’s a brand new treasure talisman, more than enough to exchange for Brother Li’s thousand year-old spiritual herb!” Shopkeeper Tian promptly said in a tone that suggested he was in an unfavorable position.

Han Li sneered to himself. He did not believe the act the other party was putting on. At most, they were just fulfilling each other’s needs. In Shopkeeper Tian’s eyes, Han Li’s spiritual herb was certainly higher in value than this piece of treasure talisman.

“What do you think? Which item will Brother Li exchange for?” Shopkeeper Tian finally asked with a smile.

Hearing this, Han Li hesitated for a moment and couldn’t make up his mind. He originally wanted to check out a few more stores and see if there were any better magic tools, but the items in front of him were pretty decent and satisfied him. He was reluctant to give up any of the items, especially that Golden Light Brick treasure talisman. That would be of help to him in the future, so he absolutely had to get his hands on that item.

“These few items, I like them all. I am planning to have all of them!” After considering for a while, Han Li made a decision.

He felt like it might not be a bad thing if he just bought everything at the Myriad Treasures Store. At least it would reduce the attention he would receive and limit the impact to only the Myriad Treasures Store.

“All of them? Brother Li must be joking!” After Shopkeeper Tian heard what Han Li said, his face darkened. He thought Han Li was being greedy and unrealistically trying to exchange all of the treasures from the brocade boxes with one spiritual herb.

Seeing this, Han Li smiled. He didn’t offer an explanation, but rather took out an identical box from his storage pouch and put it on the table.

“I will use two thousand year-old spiritual herbs to exchange for all of the treasures in your brocade boxes!” Han Li unhurriedly said with control of the matter.

Shopkeeper Tian was surprised and overjoyed. He couldn’t bother to respond to Han Li’s conditions and hastily checked the newly appeared spiritual medicine. When he made sure the new spiritual herb was indeed the same thousand year-old spiritual medicine as the first, he then looked at Han Li once again with a strange gaze. After all, a person who could bring out two rare spiritual medicines was worth his Myriad Treasures Store’s attention.

Han Li was wearing a cloak, so Shopkeeper Tian wasn’t able to clearly see the other party’s expression. Because of this, the other party felt even more mysterious. Therefore, after a slight hesitation, he said decisively, “Very well. Since Brother Li says so, I will take a step back and agree to your conditions. But this person surnamed Tian has a small attached request. In the future, if Brother Li possesses any more of such spiritual medicines, I hope Brother will prioritize this store. This person surnamed Tian will definitely offer a price that will satisfy you.”

Han Li gave a few dry laughs and nodded lightly without giving an actual response, but in his heart he was already sighing, knowing that the other party still became suspicious. It looked like he should limit these types of deals where he exchanged spiritual herbs for treasure as much as possible in the future, else he might attract a fatal disaster.

Shopkeeper Tian didn’t know Han Li’s real thoughts, but seeing that Han Li nodded and agreed, he was overjoyed. If the person in front of him who was surnamed Li could really give him thousand year-old spiritual medicine, the price of taking a step back today would have been completely worth it!

And so, Shopkeeper Tian and Han Li exchanged, and after putting away each of their items, both of them were happy.

Han Li left the Myriad Treasures Store just like that. He didn’t even dare to stay at the market city for even a second longer. He quickly walked past the market city’s flying limit, and he immediately flew away from this place.

Because he was afraid that the Myriad Treasures Store would sent some experts to secretly track him, he didn’t blatantly fly directly towards Yellow Maple Valley. Instead, he flew straight away from the Tai Yue Mountain Range. After travelling for three or four entire days, he was then at ease, turned around, and flew back towards the Yellow Maple Valley.

During an evening three days later, Han Li entered the outer ring of the Tai Yue Mountain Range. Because the sky was about to darken, for the sake of his safety, he found a hidden cave to spend the night in and decided to head back to Yellow Maple Valley the following day.

This cave happened to be located halfway up a certain hill. There was even a messy pile of rocks blocking the entrance of the cave. From the outside, it was hard to discover the cave. Han Li just happened to be able to stay inside.

After eating something, he changed his clothing, leaned against the stone wall, and started meditating. It unknowingly passed to the second half of the night while Han Li seemed to be asleep, when he suddenly heard the sound of rustling clothes and moving wind. Bang. It seemed like someone outside the cave had landed on the ground on both feet. Han Li was startled and suddenly awoke.

“Could it be that people from the Thousand Treasures Store are coming after me?” Han Li couldn’t help but think of the worst possible scenario.

“Junior Martial Sister, this is a good, remote location. I think this place is it!” A familiar male voice sounded outside the cave.

Han Li was a bit shocked, but he was finally relieved. If it wasn’t the Myriad Treasures Store coming after him for the treasure, then the other party was just passing through. There was nothing for him to worry about.

“Junior Martial Sister, there’s no need to look at me like that. Since you have never enjoyed the feeling of a s*xual relationship between a man and a woman, this Senior Martial Brother will love you dearly so that Junior Martial Sister will not waste her life as a woman. Your beauty will vanish at any moment, which would be a waste of your fair skin.” The man’s voice was neither fast nor slow. It was extremely tender, but the contents of his words were truly obscene and ruthless.

Han Li breathed in a cold breath of air. Who was the person outside? How could he use this kind of tone and say these ‘r*pe first then kill’ words? It was really impressive! Outside, there was only the sound of the man, but not the sound of the woman. This meant that this “Junior Martial Sister” had already been suppressed. She probably wasn’t able to open her mouth right now.

But the man’s voice was so familiar. He should be someone whom Han Li had seen before. Thinking of this, Han Li’s curiosity increased, and he couldn’t help but quietly move towards the entrance of the cave.

Rip! The sound of the woman’s clothing cut through the air, along with the man’s indecent laugh.

“Here, first take a Joyful Meeting Pill! Otherwise it won’t be pleasurable!”

“ Cough , Junior Martial Sister! Why do you look at Senior Brother like that? Actually, didn’t you really want to pair cultivate with me after reaching Foundation Establishment?! This could be considered me fulfilling your wish! Haha…” The man seemed to be carried away as he laughed hysterically.

At this moment, Han Li carefully moved to the entrance of the cave and started peaking outside.

A man in white was squatting by a young woman and recklessly caressing her delicate body, pulling down her clothing from time to time.

The woman’s hair was a mess, so Han Li wasn’t able to see her face clearly. But her body was already like a tender-white sheep, half-naked, revealing her white, bouncy skin, especially her half-hidden and half-revealed bosom. Her breasts were capable of elevating people’s blood pressure and deeply evoking a man’s natural instincts.

“So it was him!”

After clearly seeing the man’s face, Han Li was somewhat surprised but also suddenly realized.

The man was the narrow-minded “Martial Brother Lu” who fought against the Murong brothers. He was a malicious, two-faced person. All Han Li wondered was exactly which poor Martial Sister had become the tiny white sheep underneath his claws!

Han Li didn’t know if it was because this “Martial Brother Lu” had heard what Han Li was thinking, but he unintentionally moved aside the messy hair in front of the woman’s face. It revealed a beautiful yet extremely vicious face.

“How could it be her?” After Han Li saw the woman’s face clearly, he almost bit his tongue.

Wasn’t this the “Junior Martial Sister Chen” who had shown affection for “Martial Brother Lu” from the very beginning?! She was already in a relationship with that “Martial Brother Lu”, so why would this “Martial Brother Lu” go out of his mind and play the act of raping and killing his own partner? But as Han Li examined “Junior Martial Sister Chen’s” glaring, fire-shooting eyes, it didn’t seem like the normal teasing between couples!

Han Li blinked his eyes and was feeling a bit confused.

“Found it.”

Suddenly, “Martial Brother Lu” stopped pawing the woman and yelled in glee. A tiny, delicate storage pouch appeared in one of his hands.

“Martial Brother Lu” stopped paying attention to “Junior Martial Sister Chen”. Instead, he poured the storage pouch, and out came a large pile of items, such as magic tools, talismans, and private items like the woman’s clothing and underwear.

“Martial Brother Lu” ignored everything else, and instead went through the items among the jars, bottles, and boxes, as if he were searching for something.

Chapter 169: Fierce Battle (3)

Han Li’s and Senior Martial Brother Lu’s magic power was being steadily being absorbed into the ‘sword talisman’ and the ‘Azure Flood Dragon Banner’. Both their bodies and minds were focused on their struggle. They didn’t dare to be careless or negligent in the slightest.

Neither of them held any effort or magic power in reserve to prevent the other from overwhelming them. They both clearly understood that the slightest carelessness on either side would cause them to immediately lose their life along with the treasure; there was no longer a path for retreat.

Thus, the struggle between the azure flood dragon and the huge sword unexpectedly developed into a battle of attrition to see whose magic power would be exhausted first.

When the two realized that the quantity of their remaining magic power was the crucial point of the battle, they both took action to increase their own spiritual power. They took out spirit stones and held them in their hand to absorb their magic power.

However, Senior Martial Brother Lu had a low-grade wind attribute spirit stone, while Han Li had a mid-grade earth attribute spirit stone. This discovery caused Senior Martial Brother Lu’s complexion to become unsightly, and he became exceptionally frightened and alarmed.

A Qi Condensation disciple unexpectedly possessed a mid-grade spirit stone that only sect cultivators at Foundation Establishment or higher could obtain. This greatly surprised him as it was widely known that mid-grade spirit stones replenished spiritual power far faster than low-grade spirit stones. In terms of replenishing spiritual power, he was at a great disadvantage.

Regardless, Senior Martial Brother thought better of it. His magic power was already much deeper than his opponent’s. Even if his opponent replenished his magic power faster than he did, he wouldn’t be able to persist for long. After all, the little bit of magic power that was replenished would be consumed at the same rate as it was used. It was truly insignificant.

With this thought, Senior Martial Brother Lu calmed down and concentrated.

But when Senior Martial Brother Lu saw Han Li’s next action, Senior Martial Brother Lu’s expression changed once more to an appearance of disbelief and amazement.

Han Li voluntarily removed his blue protective barrier in front of Senior Martial Brother Lu and openly revealed his true body.

Although Senior Martial Brother Lu was outstandingly intelligent, his opponent’s actions caused his mind to be in a state of confusion. He did not know what Han Li was thinking.

Could it be that Han Li was no longer worried that his wind blades could take his life?

Senior Martial Brother Lu’s thoughts surged several times throughout his mind but did not hesitate for long. He decisively extended his left hand toward the sky and formed a faint azure wind blade.

However, Han Li did not wait for Senior Martial Brother Lu to finish condensing his wind blade and flung his arm toward the opponent. The huge sword rigidly tangled with the azure flood dragon suddenly resonated with great radiance. Han Li actually took advantage off his preoccupation with the wind blade to suddenly shake off the azure flood dragon and shot straight toward Senior Martial Brother Lu.

In this short moment, Senior Martial Brother Lu was startled and frightened by no small amount. If he persisted in forming the wind blade and attempted to launch it, he may be able to take Han Li’s life. But equivalently, the giant sword would execute him, and he was also certain to lose his life, ending both sides in mutual destruction.

Although the wind wall had yet to dissipate, this huge sword was able to contend with the Azure Flood Dragon Banner’s transformation. That hurricane would certainly be easily destroyed by the huge sword and would be unable to obstruct it for even a fraction of a second.

This Senior Martial Brother Lu was unable to accept this outcome. He still had vast prospects and a beautiful future. He was simply unwilling to meet his end in the wilderness against this unknown person.

With this in mind, he thought no further. He gave up on the wind blade and wildly channeled all of his magic power toward the azure flood dragon and summoned it toward him.

That Azure Flood Dragon Banner was truly an amazing wind attribute magic tool. With the entirety of Senior Martial Brother Lu strength, it met Han Li’s huge sword halfway and once again entered a struggle.

Seeing this, Senior Martial Brother Lu let out a sigh of relief, his body covered in cold sweat.

Thus, in the following period of time, Senior Martial Brother Lu attempted to cast magic techniques several more times, wanting to attack Han Li.

However, Han Li used the same technique every time, forcing him to withdraw. Although Han Li hadn’t the least bit of protection, he was unable to act against him. Senior Martial Brother Lu was incomparably sullen and was forced to rely on his deeper magic power, thereby continuing to deplete it.

At this moment, Han Li took out various small herbs and such from his storage pouch and stuffed them into his mouth. As he chewed the large mouthfuls, Senior Martial Brother Lu was dumbstruck; he didn’t know what other sinister plot his opponent was planning.

He could not guess what his opponent was planning and was baffled, causing Senior Martial Brother Lu to feel bleak. He had a bad premonition. However, he cherished his life far too much. Although he was far more shrewd than normal people, he had been at his wits end for a while.

As more time passed by, Senior Martial Brother Lu’s heart gradually grew heavier.

At last, the azure dragon’s light began to dim but the huge gray streak was as dazzling as before. Senior Martial Brother Lu could not help but be frightened. He shouted out hoarsely, “Impossible! My magic power far exceeds yours. Even if you’ve been replenished by a mid-grade spirit stone, it is impossible for you to currently have energy remaining. You should have exhausted your magic power before I did!”

Soon, the azure flood dragon was on the verge of collapse. Senior Martial Brother Lu yelled out; his shout was like the last bark of a wild dog that fell into a well, full of objection.

When Han Li saw his plan completely realized, he could not help but smile. After he heard the opponent’s words, his mouth slightly slanted, causing his smile to become a sneer.

He didn’t have the leisure to explain all of this to a dead man as killing him was the most urgent affair. He was also almost entirely out of magic power, so how could he afford to waste that effort on the enemy?

With that thought, Han Li paid no attention to the opponent’s question. He pointed at the huge sword, causing its radiance to become even more magnificent. It gradually whittled away at the azure flood dragon until it was only about three meters long. Its azure light was so dim that it could nearly no longer be seen.

When Senior Martial Brother saw this, he became completely desperate. Thus, the desire to stake it all rose in his heart, and his eyes gradually shone with madness.

Without speaking, he gradually retrieved the little magic power remaining in the Azure Flood Dragon Banner, causing it to return to its original form in an instant and fall from the sky. Then, without regard for the huge sword rushing forth to execute him, he used his remaining magic power to condense a huge wind blade and ruthlessly throw it toward Han Li without the slightest hesitation.

When Han Li saw this, his heart trembled. While the opponent rushed to throw the wind blade, he directed the huge sword to behead the opponent. Then without staying to look at the aftermath, Han Li fled, already rushing out about ten meters away.

After previously receiving the wind blades, Han Li knew of their frightening speed. If he didn’t immediately use “Shifting Smoke Steps” to avoid it, he wouldn’t be able to defend himself. He would have been caught unprepared and be cut into two, dying with grievances and unable to rest in peace.

The wind blade was truly extraordinarily fast. It already reached the location where Han Li had just fled from. However, it unexpectedly followed the direction Han Li was fleeing in and fiercely shot out once more.

Han Li did not think any further and used “Shifting Smoke Steps” to its greatest extent. In a small area, he continuously shifted left and right, transforming into several afterimages, causing the wind blade that was closely chasing him to be unable to catch up.

Han Li clearly understood that if he fled in a straight line, he would certainly be cut down by the wind blade. By using fine and delicate movements, he would be able to defend himself without worry. This was the reason why he dared to abandon his defensive magic technique.

Puchi. The wind blade suddenly lost control and disappeared into the earth, leaving a deep groove.

Han Li let out a long breath. At this moment, he calmed his panicked heart. Using a movement technique from the mortal world to evade a cultivator’s attack was truly a frightening affair.

Han Li sat on the ground and then looked across from him.

He saw that the wind wall had already disappeared and that Senior Martial Lu, who had been hiding behind it, was cut into two pieces. The two-pieced corpse laid there motionlessly. Next to it was a huge sword with a dimming radiance.

Chapter 176: Making a Bet

“No bet! Absolutely not! Do you think that I would do the same thing twice?” Martial Ancestor Li shook his head as if he were beating a drum and voiced his refusal.

“No bet? Benefactor Li’s standards are actually so high. Does the blood from the inner core of a demonic flood dragon not even enter his eyes?” The Daoist priest wore an astonished expression as if he couldn’t believe it.

However, when Han Li saw his expression, he felt it was very false.

“Blood from a flood dragon’s inner core?” Although Martial Ancestor Li originally intended to absolutely refuse to be pulled into a relationship with the Daoist priest, when he heard the name of the item, his expression abruptly changed, and his words somewhat trembled.

“Yes! If Benefactor Li wants to know about this item, I shall explain. Thirty years ago, at the dangerous rapids of the State of Yuan Wu’s Coiling Dragon River, I paid a great price for this item so I could procure it for Benefactor!” The Daoist Priest calmly and leisurely said while eating up the other party’s expression.

“Impossible! How could the blood of a flood dragon be acquired, not to mention blood kept in its inner core. This is not something that can be said without thinking. Are you making fun of me?” Martial Ancestor Li sobered up from his excitement and exposed an appearance of doubt.

“Is this humble Daoist not a monk? I would not lie. Benefactor can take a look for himself.”

The Daoist Priest did not want to waste time explaining and merely flipped his hand, revealing a white sphere filled with wisps of blood. Martial Ancestor Li’s eyes widened, wishing he could rush over and grab it.

“If Benefactor’s Horned Silver Python were to consume this core and undergo secluded cultivation for ten to twenty years, in all likelihood it would leap from the middle stage of Foundation Establishment to the late stage. With another hundred years of bitter cultivation, it wouldn’t be impossible toenter Core Formation.” The Daoist Priest’s words were filled with enticement.

When Martial Ancestor Li heard these words, he coldly snorted and stiffened his face. It seemed he was unmoved, but his indefinite and flickering gaze exposed the restlessness of his heart.

“With such a rare wager, why is Benefactor hesitating for so long? Could it be you truly don’t think very highly of the strength of your valley’s disciples?” The Daoist Priest curled his lips, goading him to accept.

“To say the disciples of our Yellow Maple Valley are inferior to those of your Clear Void Sect is overcritical.” Martial Ancestor Li wore a displeased expression.

He swept his eyes past the party behind the Daoist Priest and immediately gained a rough estimate of the Clear Void Sect’s disciples. Their strength was about the same as that of the Yellow Maple Valley’s disciples.

“Fine, I will gamble! However, what treasure of mine would you have me wager?”

After a moment of consideration from Martial Ancestor Li, he felt that his odds of winning were fifty percent. With the addition of his extreme longing for that inner core, he eventually nodded and agreed. However, he still cautiously asked that question.

“Hehe, this humble Daoist isn’t interested in any of Benefactor’s other treasures. If he happens to luckily win, then he desires Benefactor to give this humble Daoist two equivalent chunks of iron essence twenty years from now. The essence of Benefactor Li’s True Fire is clear. It is quite famous among the Seven Great Sects. For you, this is surely a trivial matter!” The Daoist Priest said with squinted eyes and a smile. Even so, a faint trace of treachery was contained within his words.

“You want two equivalent chunks of iron essence?” Martial Ancestor Li’s complexion was unsightly and he almost jumped immediately after hearing these words.

“You old facetious Daoist, you plan to have me toil bitterly!”

“How is that? So long as you win, you aren’t required to. This is the inner core of a grade two demonic beast, equivalent to that of us initial Core Formation stage experts. It is absolutely worth the price.” The Daoist Priest said while shaking his head.

Martial Ancestor Li’s complexion grew uncertain. After a moment, he eventually extended his palm and coldly asked, “Are we following the same rules as last time? Which sect gathers the most spiritual medicines, followed by the quality, and lastly the number of people who leave the forbidden area alive!?”

“Of course, it will be the same as before.”

The Daoist Priest was greatly happy and hastily extended his palm. He struck it against the other party’s, officializing the bet.

A sharp Pa! sound out.

Although the Daoist Priest struck his palm, he wasn’t happy in the least and was actually grieving.

The palm he struck was not Martial Ancestor Li’s, but rather a different, filthy hand. This hand strangely appeared between the two and was covered with grease and filth. Nobody knew when it had last been washed!

Two sects’ disciples who had been closely paying attention to the two Martial Ancestors’ dialogue were stunned by this ghostly scene.

“Senior Qiong!”

The Daoist Priest and Martial Ancestor Li yelled at the same time with a green complexion.

“Who is a Senior? I don’t dare to be regarded as such. I am at Core Formation, much like yourselves. It’s just that I happened to enter it a few years earlier!” The lazy voice that came from between them was spoken by a queerly dressed man.

This person wore a blue garment with several patches and had short hair that was several inches long. He had an azure cloth bag at his waist that had been washed pale. Even though his bag made it seem like he was a person who loved cleanliness, his face was smothered with dark grease to the point where his true face could not be seen.

“A few years? More like several hundred!”

After clearly seeing the person’s appearance, Martial Ancestor Li and the Daoist Priest bitterly smiled. They both let out a regretful sigh, ‘It was this person as expected’. However, they didn’t dare to show the slightest disrespect.

Not only was this eccentric a step into the Nascent Soul stage, but his age alone was large enough to scare people. Furthermore, his self-created Incorporeal Evasion Technique had shaken the cultivation world and was well-known in the cultivation sects of nearby countries.

It was unknown whether it was because his death was imminent or if he was unable to enter Nascent Soul, but in the past hundred years, he had become more and more eccentric and became very fond of teasing other Core Formation experts. Nearly all of the tens of these high-level experts had been pranked to exhaustion.

However, there was nothing even his sect’s Great Martial Ancestors could do to him.

With regards to the deepness of his magic power, this person was number one among Core Formation Experts. As for background, he was a member of the strongest sect among the Seven Great Sects, the Masked Moon Sect. If one were to look for one of the sect’s Nascent Soul “Authorities” to lecture him, these “Authorities” were likely to ignore those people as they were unwilling to invite trouble over such trivial matters!

As it was, this person was among the higher powers in the cultivation world, known for being an evil tyrant and a hoodlum. Essentially, whoever saw him was subject to the whims of fate! They could only hope that his mood for the day was good, else suffering from his small tricks would be unavoidable!

When this “Senior” suddenly graced them with his presence, how could Martial Ancestor Li and the Daoist Priest not be startled and feel their stomachs grow restless!? These two people have already suffered from his torment!

“Since you’ve made a wager, just so that you’re not too lonely, count this rotten old man in as well!” This great Senior’s mood seemed to be quite good; however, his words caused the two to complain incessantly.

“Senior must be joking. How could the disciples of our sects compare to the Masked Moon Sect’s brilliant students? We would be certain to lose, so there is no need to gamble. We respectfully concede!” said the Daoist Priest with a forced smile.

Martial Ancestor Li closed his lips, but his face revealed an expression that showed he was a hundred and twenty percent in favor of those words.

When the exalted old man heard this, he coldly laughed several times and turned his eyes, strangely saying, “How could I take such an unfair advantage? Be at ease, so long as the performance of both your sects surpass my own, then that will count as my loss. Afterwards, you can then decide who won among yourselves.”

“Really?”

When the Daoist Priest heard this, he could not help but let out a breath of relief. Although this person was moody and laughed or scolded as he desired, his words were certainly resolute and decisive, and he never turned his back on a promise. With that said, this wager could be regarded as fair, even giving the two a small advantage.

“I refined these three Incorporeal Needle treasure talismans at a whim, but I don’t have any juniors, so I will stake them in the gamble!” This Elder raised his hand, suddenly revealing three talismans with a seven-colored needle drawn on each one. He then put them away in an instant.

When Martial Ancestor Li and the Daoist Priest saw this, they were unable to conceal the alarm on their faces. They couldn’t help but look at each other and make out the greed in each other’s eyes.

Chapter 183: Harmonic Spiritual Talisman

Han Li tasted some bitterness from his mouth. He did not think that as greatly careful and tremendously cautious as he was, he would still be ambushed. Furthermore, it was one of the worst possible circumstances, between two people!

Currently, he was in a zone called the “Skyline”. Its environment was extremely dangerous. If one did not use flying magic tools, the entire region only had a narrow small path that led to the central area.

Lining the two sides of the small path were incomparably steep cliffs. Although Han Li was not weak in the light body martial arts of the mortal world, he would not dare to rashly climb them!

As for flying directly over with flying magic tools, the idea was even more absurd. It would be a suicidal action, openly allowing others to launch an attack. Why even think of it!? None of the sects’ disciples would ever perform such folly! Furthermore, the bitter experiences of his predecessors taught him that flying was an absolutely prohibited action in the forbidden area, else one would leave a corpse.

When Han Li entered the vicinity, he hesitated for quite a while. However, he ultimately didn’t dare to take the shortcut by flying over the mountain peak. As a result, he was forced to openly follow the small road on foot.

Naturally, Han Li was completely wary of the dangers in this area. On the entire way, his nerves were tightly strung. But even so, just when he had walked through the path opening, his path was blocked from the front and back by two people without even the slightest warning.

When Han Li saw the bearded man’s fierce expression, he knew that to talk arrogantly at this moment was of no use at all! First he slapped the defensive Water Barrier Talisman on his body, and then he brought out the Flying Dark-Iron Shield. Additionally, he took out the magic tool “Gold Beetle Swarm Blades” and his few elementary high-grade “Earth Prison Technique” talismans.

The fully bearded man and the person behind him looked at Han Li’s actions with cold eyes without the slightest intention of stopping or attacking him. It seemed the two were completely confident; they felt entirely certain that they could handle Han Li and appeared calm.

This was no surprise! The person behind him was already at the peak of the twelfth layer. Not to mention the fully bearded man had already cultivated to the thirteenth layer. Facing an eleventh layer fledgeling such as Han Li, they naturally felt that it would be a trivial matter!

When Han Li saw this, he licked his dry lips and inwardly sneered to himself. Since his opponents were so negligent, he would naturally exploit this opportunity.

Thus, remaining completely calm, Han Li faced his body to the side so that his enemies were to his right and left, as if they were horns, to avoid being attacked in the back. As expected, these two did not take the opportunity to attack jointly.

These were the strongest enemies he had ever faced since he entered the world of cultivation. Even so, Han Li wasn’t fearful of them in the least.

Although he did his utmost to avoid fighting with others, it wasn’t because he had no confidence in himself. Even though Han Li’s magic power was greatly lacking and would be a disadvantage in a battle of attrition, the top quality magic tools and the treasure talisman he possessed were enough to make up for this deficiency.

Furthermore, if it truly did not work out, he could take out the “Heaven’s Lightning Child” and eliminate a person. Was that not an easy matter?

But whether or not he was willing to use it was an entirely different matter.

However, Han Li had a bit of doubt. Why would the fully bearded man and the Heavenly Imperial Fortress disciple not fight one another and instead team up? If they were disciples from the same sect, it would be an ordinary matter. However, these two were obviously not from the same sect!

“Boy, your courage isn’t small! Outside the forbidden area, you actually dared to mock me and exchange flirting glances with that sl*t. Now I will take your life as an apology!” The fully bearded man said fiendishly.

Then he turned to the Heavenly Imperial Fortress disciple and said, “Brother Yan, I have a grudge against this fellow. Hand this person over to me. I want to treat him properly and let him know that you can’t be so reckless in the cultivation world! Before you offend someone in your next life, first remember this before you speak!”

When the Heavenly Imperial Fortress disciple heard this, he shrugged his shoulders without care and said, “Do as you like. I’ll just stand to the side. However, don’t be like last time and throw him off the edge! Otherwise, you’ll owe me a life-saving favor!”

“Haha, that time was a complete accident! This time I’m handling a fledgeling. If I use half my strength, I’ll have enough to spare!” The fully bearded man’s face was red, but soon after he slanted his mouth and said this with disdain.

“Ke, you should do your best! I truly don’t wish for there to be a day I hear of your death. After all, we’ve been good friends for many years. To find a person of agreeable temperament is truly difficult!”

The Heavenly Imperial Fortress disciple shook his head. It seemed the fully bearded man’s arrogance gave him great headaches, but he did not believe that the opponent before him posed any threat to his old friend. Besides, he was attentively watching from the side!

At the side, Han Li did not shut out the two’s dialog and heard it clearly. From the words he heard, the doubts in his heart were cleared.

Unexpectedly, these two were originally friends. Furthermore, their relationship was rather good.

This was rather troublesome! These two were certain to coordinate together against enemies far better than common temporary alliances. Hearing their words, it seemed they had cooperated on more than one occasion!

Han Li couldn’t help but feel greatly depressed!

‘It seems I can only use the Lightning Child. But first, it’s important that I dispose of one of them. Then I will be able to handle the remaining one much more easily! However, this is too strange! Originally, each sect’s disciples were randomly transported. How could they happen be transported to the same area and happen to meet? This is truly incredible!’ Han Li hatefully thought. He felt greatly indignant toward their luck.

Han Li did not know that the Heavenly Imperial Fortress disciple had also joyfully thought this in his heart.

When this person saw the fully bearded man walk toward Han Li, his mind couldn’t help but think that he was able to meet his good friend due to the great work of the “Harmonic Spiritual Talisman”.

‘High-grade Harmonic Spiritual Talisman, this item is truly useful. So long as we enter the forbidden area during the same moment and use the talisman at the same time, our Spiritual Qi will temporarily bind together, and the restriction formation will transport us to the same area. Although I heard the odds of success is fifty percent, the price of the talisman was exceptionally more expensive than ordinary elementary high-grade talismans. But in the end, we were able to wait in that location and successfully ambush several disciples who passed through. It was a great harvest!’

‘Besides, I, Yan, am not foolish! Spending such a large price to brave the strange dangers of the forbidden area, was it not in order to openly kill and plunder the many individuals who were covetously gazing at those spiritual medicines? There will be great harvests without any repercussions. This one is convinced that so long as us two join hands and don’t come across those fierce experts, our objective will be easily and effortlessly accomplished. Then, when it is near the end, we will pull back and find a place to hide. We’ll stay there until it’s time and safely leave! This is truly a flawless plan. Only I could have thought of it!’ The Heavenly Imperial Fortress disciple thought of his future prospects after he left and could not help but think beautiful narcissistic thoughts. His mind naturally did not think of the great battle that was about to occur.

At this moment the fully bearded man took out a green leather pouch and sent Han Li an evil grin as he approached. It seemed he wanted to dispose of him.

However, it was unknown if it was because of his good friend’s warning, but he used a talisman halfway,. He became covered in a green-colored light barrier that increased his defense.

Seeing these circumstances, Han Li wrinkled his brow. He had a bit of a headache!

He was originally going to act fearful of the Spirit Beast Mountain disciple’s actions and prepare to make use of this person’s negligence, getting rid of this person first. But now that his opponent released a defensive magic technique, this was no longer something he could do in a short amount of time.

Naturally, if he used “Heaven’s Lightning Child”, this person wouldn’t be able to do anything even if he had other methods. However, this was a one time use consumable. If it wasn’t a crucial moment of life or death, Han Li would not use it!

Since using it was out of the question, Han Li naturally planned to attack the the Heavenly Imperial Fortress disciple instead.

He saw that the person had both hands behind his back with his head raised to the sky. He was currently pondering about something, not taking note of anything happening at all. Han Li was exalted; he knew there was an opportunity to exploit!

Without taking the time to think, he used the “Earth Prison Technique” talisman in his hand, throwing it toward the fully bearded man.

As a result, the talisman turned into a stream of yellow light in midair, fiercely shooting toward his opponent. It actually covered the barrier of the fully bearded man’s defensive magic technique. It took the shape of a larger yellow barrier and firmly trapped him within, not allowing him to move an inch forward.

Chapter 184: Might of the Golden Light Brick

When the fully bearded man saw Han Li with his hand still on the talisman, he was not worried. The wood attribute defensive barrier he wore had frightening defensive power that could fundamentally ignore common attacks.

Furthermore, on the basis that his opponent was a novice who cultivated to the eleventh layer, he didn’t believe that he could possess a talisman of great strength. At most, it would be an elementary mid-grade talisman.

Because of this, he continued to walk forward without taking notice, opening his pouch as if he were about to bring something out.

But when he was suddenly rooted in place by the yellow light barrier which he recognized as the “Earth Prison Technique”, the fully bearded man’s expression finally changed, realizing that things had taken a turn for the worse.

At this time, a strange dark green snake with a pair of purple wings leapt out out from his pouch. As soon as it appeared, the snake immediately made a few odd “gua gua” cries and began to viciously attack the yellow barrier, causing the barrier to tremble continuously; its strength was not small.

When the fully bearded man saw this, his spirits were slightly lifted. He took out another pouch to release another spirit beast, hoping to combine their efforts to break through the earth prison. He was confident that he would be able to escape in a short period of time!

When he escaped, he would definitely pull out his opponent’s ribs one by one to quench the hatred in his heart.

Han Li didn’t even pay attention to his surrounding enemies; in a swift movement, he rushed towards the man from the Heavenly Imperial Fortress. His movements were quick, and throughout the whole way he seemed to be darting in and out of view, even leaving behind a series of afterimages, making him seem almost phantom-like.

At the same time, Han Li gently patted the storage pouch near his waist. The original “Gold Beetle Swarm Blades” suddenly switched with another similarly small magic tool that he clutched tightly in his hand.

At this time, the man from the Heavenly Imperial Fortress finally awoke from his beautiful dream, instantly seeing the strange scene unfolding in front of him. His expression changed dramatically. He hurriedly backed up and flipped his palm, causing a talisman to appear.

Meanwhile, Han Li was still at least thirty meters away from him. The man relaxed, thinking that there was more than enough time to cast the talisman.

However, before he was able to use his spiritual power to activate the talisman, he was stunned to see that the charging Han Li suddenly smiled mysteriously at him. In turn, one of Han Li’s hands gently waved at him, a movement similar to a greeting between two familiar friends. At the same time, he also felt a slight itch on his neck, as if he had been bitten by a mosquito.

The man from the Heavenly Imperial Fortress stared blankly, yet to realize the other side’s intention. In a moment of turmoil, his eyes dimmed as he lost consciousness.

“Brother Yan!”

Standing off to the side, the fully bearded man from Spirit Beast Mountain involuntarily cried out with wide eyes, having seen the whole thing clearly.

He personally saw that Han Li was able to kill his close friend with a simple wave of his hand from about three meters away. His friend’s head rolled on the ground with a “gu lu lu” sound, separated from its body. However, the now headless body continued to back up a few steps until it fell over on the ground, blood spurting from its neck about a few feet high with “hu hu” sounds.

The fully bearded man suddenly felt his hands and feet turn ice cold with a cold sweat down his back.

The methods the opponent used to kill his friend were too demonic! He had seen clearly that his friend was killed without contact, and the opponent for sure hadn’t used any kind of magic technique.

“Boy, as soon as I get out I will hack you to pieces!” Although he felt beads of cold sweat exuding from his forehead and was filled with grief for his friend, the fully bearded man maintained a menacing attitude to strengthen his courage, bracing himself and standing firm.

In actuality, however, he had decided in his heart that as soon as he escaped from the Earth Prison Technique, he would immediately run far away, biding his time. Revenge was a dish best served cold, after all!

The boy in front of him was too strange. Not only did he have the high grade Earth Prison Technique talisman, but he also could kill people with invisible weapons, making him truly difficult to deal with! Getting revenge for his friend is indeed important, but first he must preserve his own life!

It turned out that the seemingly ferocious fully bearded man was actually a person as cowardly as a mouse that bullied the weak yet feared the strong! Most people would be surprised by this!

Of course, Han Li had no way of knowing his opponent’s thoughts; all he saw was that the opponent had released another pangolin-like beast that, along with that strange snake, had begun to fiercely attack the yellow barrier. The fully bearded man had also taken out a pair of iron-rod-like magic tools to aid the two beasts in smashing the barrier, causing it to flicker with light incessantly.

The Earth Prison Technique could not be maintained for much longer!

As soon as Han Li realized this, he took out his “Golden Light Brick” treasure talisman with one hand, bringing it in front of his eyes and staring at it intently in order to activate it. If he were to use any other normal magic tool, he simply could not feel at ease! His opponent, after all, was a thirteenth layer expert; if he was unable to kill him with one blow, there would be big trouble when his opponent escaped! Until now, he still remembered the exhausting battle with Senior Martial Brother Lu – and at that time Senior Martial Brother Lu had only been at the twelfth layer!

Despite this, he had not expected that he could actually use the transparent thread to finish off a twelfth layer opponent. However, the fully bearded man was already on guard and would not be defeated so easily!

The fully bearded man under the Earth Prison Technique, seeing the weird movements of the talisman in Han Li’s hands, felt his heart tense. He tightened his grip on the pair of black iron cudgels. But the yellow barrier of the Earth Prison Technique was extremely strong! Even if it had changed shape and darkened to the point of being in danger of fracturing, it continued to maintain its integrity! Upon seeing this, the fully bearded man became so angry that he almost vomited blood!

At this time, he suddenly felt a gust of an astonishing amount of spirit power rocketing up from Han Li’s direction. He couldn’t help but slowly turn his body and look in his direction.

He saw Han Li’s hand emitting a strong golden light, and a lustrous, shining golden rectangular object slowly rose up, floating in midair.

“Treasure Talisman.”

The fully bearded man’s expression changed dramatically, and he began to yell in terror. He had realized the nature of the Golden Light Brick.

What he didn’t know, however, was that Han Li’s face at this moment was also deathly pale with alarm. The floating object was furiously draining all of his inner magic power steadily, without any way of stopping it; it seemed as if it would suck him dry.

The quietly complaining Han Li, as he was suffering, began to curse the store that had sold him this item, ‘How is this a treasure talisman? It’s clearly a leech that wants to kill me!’

However, when a third of his magic power had been drained, the treasure talisman finally stopped its wild movements and calmed down. Control over it once again returned to Han Li.

At this time, Han Li did not hesitate and pointed, causing the Golden Light Brick treasure talisman to immediately shoot out. It flew straight towards the fully bearded man, who was still trapped under the Earth Prison Technique. His face became ashen from fright.

The golden brick began to expand, and in the blink of an eye, it became as large as a room. Spiritual Qi revolved around it and radiated golden light in all directions; its pressure was truly astonishing. When it reached the fully bearded man’s forehead, the golden brick was like a small mountain in size, and it came down with a violent clap.

Peng!

“Ah!”

After the loud sound and fully bearded man’s blood-curdling scream, the entire earth shook violently.

Han Li was both surprised and happy; his expression was somewhat strange.

Was it really possible to eliminate a thirteenth layer disciple that easily? Han Li had some doubts.

As soon as he retrieved the treasure talisman, the Golden Light Brick immediately returned to its original form and flew back into Han Li’s hand. An extremely large crater had formed in the place where the golden brick had slammed into the ground, almost thirty meters wide and a meter deep! As for the fully bearded man and his spirit beasts, they had become a pile of mud, indistinguishable from one another.

The fully bearded man really had been killed! Han Li was at a loss. It was as if he couldn’t resist a single strike in the slightest.

Was it that the fully bearded man was too weak or that the Golden Light Brick was simply too strong? Han Li was unable to decide. However, after generating such a loud noise, it was no longer safe to stay in this place!

Han Li quickly became sober. After he destroyed the two corpses, he took the five or six storage pouches and left the area, leaving the Skyline.

Continuing to walk forward would most likely have led to a large forest, which was incidentally also an ideal place to ambush and kill people. Perhaps after entering the forest there would be another fierce battle waiting for him. Thus, before entering, he decided to find a place to rest a little and restore his magic power in order to protect himself.

Chapter 189: Extermination By Lightning

Although Han Li could not understand how Feng Yue’s movements were so fast, suspicions began to arise in his heart.

But now was not the time to get to investigate; he had no choice, but to put away the “Golden Light Brick” treasure talisman. He waved the “Golden Beetle Swarm Blade’s” mother blade in his hand, causing all of the children blades to fly out like a swarm of bees, turning into eight streaks of golden light. They all aggressively shot towards Feng Yue, relying on the chaos the large numbers would create in order to obtain victory.

If the opponent was willing to withdraw the yellow streak to protect himself, it would obviously be better; he would be able to force a stalemate for quite some time, but Han Li was not confident in this idea. Based on the opponent having such a widespread reputation, his true strength definitely would not be limited to this. The previous attack seemed to intend to probe him.

As expected, when Feng Yue saw Han Li’s golden blades flying towards him, he wasn’t panicked in the slightest.

He laughed coldly a few times, and an item that he had just taken out began to emit light; it was a yellow umbrella-shaped magic tool.

Feng Yue didn’t actually cause the umbrella to leave his hand; instead, when he saw the eight streaks of golden light appear in front of him, he leisurely opened the umbrella. A spherical barrier made of yellow light appeared and immediately covered up all of Feng Yue’s body. When the golden blades hit the ball of light, they exploded with strange “pi pi pa pa” sounds, and all of the golden blades easily rebounded.

This was also a high-grade protective magic tool, and judging by its strength it definitely surpassed that of Han Li’s Flying Dark-Iron Shield.

Han Li’s facial color changed dramatically, becoming slightly wane. Feng Yue began to laugh crazily and loudly, and his expression was one of delight.

This was not surprising; ever since he had obtained the “Yellow Parasol”, he had never been harmed by any low-layer cultivators. Seeing Han Li’s frightened appearance, he naturally felt extremely carefree in his heart.

Feng Yue valued this umbrella far more than the knife treasure talisman. Treasure talismans could only be used for a limited amount of time; when their energy was used up, they became useless pieces of paper. On the other hand, the “Yellow Parasol” could be used an unlimited number of times!

Han Li sighed and cut off his spell, pointing with one finger; all of the golden blades were summoned back to him and returned to their original shape upon landing in his hand.

Feng Yue didn’t know what Han Li planned to do, but since he was still being protected and felt carefree, he focused all of his attention on controlling the yellow streak,

Based on protective ability and scope, the “Flying Dark-Iron Shield” possibly was much worse than the “Yellow Parasol”; however, what Feng Yue didn’t know was that in terms of flexibility, this small shield definitely was much better than most normal defensive magic tools.

In the end, it didn’t matter how frantically Feng Yue made the yellow streak move or how wondrously it hovered; they were all completely blocked by the shield outside. It was at this time that he realized if he didn’t utterly destroy this shield, he would have no way of getting to Han Li!

His face revealed an expression of resent, and he was forced to return to his old tactic of using the yellow streak of the knife to slowly wear at the iron shield. Despite the fact that the black light being emitted from the shield had already been decreased by a significant amount, the remaining light was enough to resist for a short period of time.

At this time, Han Li, seeing that there was no way for him to secure victory, clenched his teeth and made a heart-wrenching decision.

He returned the golden blades to his storage pouch and switched it out for a small, azure-black gourd. He raised the gourd high into the air, and seven or eight black spheres flew out from it; these spheres flew towards Feng Yue, light as a feather.

Feng Yue was naturally aware of Han Li’s movements, and thus he stared blankly for a moment. This was because the gourd magic tool was simply too common; lower-layer cultivators all knew about these cheap magic tools, and almost all of them had tried using such items before.

It didn’t matter whether the tool that contained the spheres was a gourd or a bottle or a pot; although the spheres that came shooting out of it were very enticingly called “Primeval Beads”, their strength as compared to top-quality magic tools was simply too small.

But it was also because of this that Feng Yue began to suspect something in his heart.

He didn’t wait for the spheres to come near him; instead, he reached out and placed an “Ice Spear Technique” talisman into his hand. Then, he raised it, and the talisman immediately became a crystal-clear, brilliantly white ice spear, which he resolutely threw to meet the spheres.

With a crisp “peng”, the ice spear flew knocked away three or four of these spheres before shattering. White fragments of ice dispersed in midair, as if they were flowers scattered by heavenly maidens. These fragments of ice became a small rain of hail, beautiful in an unexpected way.

Seeing these circumstances unfold, Feng Yue finally began to relax, and he once again focused his attention onto Han Li himself. This was because at this time, an azure banner had suddenly appeared; on this banner was the image of an azure dragon baring its fangs and brandishing its claws. It appeared incredibly realistic, as if it were about to jump out.

Feng Yue’s experience was very abundant, and with one glance he knew this definitely was a top-notch, high-grade magic tool; he could not afford to underestimate its strength!

Meanwhile, Han Li was controlling this flag, allowing its surface to begin to accumulate azure-colored spiritual light. This light was very dazzling, and its strength was truly not small.

Although Feng Yue was completely confident in his Yellow Parasol, his prudent and cunning personality caused him to unblinkingly stare at this azure flag, afraid that this magic tool would have some kind of odd power and could break through his defenses.

As for those Primeval Beads, he had long realized that those were red herrings meant to disturb his line of sight, and so he ignored them. Based on the pitiful destructive force of the Primeval Beads, even if they were to hover around the Yellow Parasol for an entire day it would be impossible for them to disturb his defenses even slightly.

However, Feng Yue became increasingly distressed and bewildered after seeing Han Li take out one high-grade magic tool after another.

He guessed that Han Li and that woman with many treasures were the same and that he was the disciple of some expert. His desire to kill Han Li became even more urgent.

He feared that if the opponent was able to survive, it would cause him no end of trouble. Even more so, the opponent had witnessed the entire process of him killing people and stealing their belongings. If the elder of the woman with many treasures came looking for him, he would have a lot of trouble on his hands.

Right as Feng Yue was attracted by the Azure Flood Dragon Banner and his killing intent was rising, those Primeval Beads flew in front of him and ran into the barrier created by the Yellow Parasol. After making some silvery noises from attacking the barrier, the foremost few beads were easily repelled out.

When Feng Yue heard that sound, he instinctively lowered his head to take a look.

“Relying on those Primeval Beads to attack me is too arrogant! These aren’t even worth mentioning; even…”

“Yi! Why is this one so small; it’s even colored blue……”

Feng Yue had just sneered when he discovered a Primeval Bead that had revealed a blue bead hiding inside of it after it had been reflected. It was only as large as a pill, much more modest in size than regular Primeval Beads.

Feng Yue startled a little; before he was able to come up with an idea, the blue bead had already hit the ball-shaped barrier.

“White light! A magnificent, blinding white light!”

This was the last color that Feng Yue ever saw in this world. His body slowly turned, and then he never knew anything again.

In the eyes of Han Li, when the blue bead came into contact with the yellow light, it immediately exploded out with silver light in a sphere a few Zhang wide. It noiselessly enveloped the larger half of Feng Yue’s body. After this, the white light disappeared without a trace, revealing Feng Yue’s stupefied expression, as if he were ready to fight another day.

Han Li’s heart sank, but before he could move, a light gust of wind blew. Feng Yue’s body suddenly collapsed like grains of sand and turned into ash that blew away with the wind.

All that remained were the halves of two small legs and the pair of shoes on his feet. They stood all alone on the ground, creating an unspeakably strange scene.

When Han Li saw this, he was not afraid. In fact, he immediately sat on the ground and breathed in deeply, allowing his heart, which had been stuck in his throat, to calm down.

It was only after using his greatest last resort, the “Heavenly Lightning Seed”, paired with a whole string of movements meant to cover it up, that he was able to completely wipe out Feng Yue from the face of the earth.

But Han Li’s expression was not actually one of joy; rather, it displayed both self-deprecation and bitter laughter.

This was not too surprising, given that the Trial by Blood and Fire had only entered the second day; he had already used all of his magic treasures, as well as his ultimate trump card he was saving as a last resort. How could he possibly be happy?

When he thought about the remaining three days, as well as the unknown number of violent people he would meet like Feng Yue, his heart sank again even as he had just begun to relax.

However, if he hadn’t used the Heaven’s Lightning Child, it would have definitely been difficult for him to escape; the Flying Dark-Iron Shield had reached its breaking point. In addition, considering the opponent’s high-grade magic tools as well as the woman with many treasures, he definitely had not suffered a loss; in fact, it would be more accurate to say that he had struck it rich!

Han Li began to think better of his situation, and his countenance was revived; he hurriedly looked to the opposite side. But as soon as his eyes fell upon the site, Han Li’s mouth fell wide open, rendering him speechless for a significant amount of time!

Chapter 190: Black Boots

Because Feng Yue had originally been standing, apart from that pair of boots, there was nothing else on the floor. The storage pouches Han Li had in mind disappeared without a trace.

Han Li stood straight like a carp jumping on water, and then, as if his buttocks were on fire, he hurriedly charged over. After searching for a great long while in the area where Feng Yue disappeared, he couldn’t find the slightest trace of the storage pouch.

“Could it be that the power of the Heavenly Lightning Seed was so powerful? Did it actually turn the storage pouch into ashes along with the person?” After Han Li searched his surroundings with his hands several times, he eventually came to an extremely depressing answer.

Unresigned, Han Li expanded the search area by several times, but the result was the same. However, he was actually able to acquire the rich girl’s small mirror and crystal ball. Furthermore, because the owner had already died, he was able to recover the small blade treasure talisman.

When Han Li saw these three items, he thought that the loss of his Heaven’s Lightning Child, the high-quality magic tools: the silver hook, and the azure rope, as well as the storage pouches that were destroyed by the Heavenly Lightning Seed, he looked up to the sky speechlessly.

However, regardless of what was said after this great battle, he was nonetheless the winner against the much stronger Feng Yue, who had turned to dust.

Not knowing whether to consider it a profit or a loss, Han Li was only able to mock himself.

When he thought of Feng Yue, Han Li unconsciously looked at what was left at him: a pair of halved legs. He could not help but lightly shake his head. He then lifted his hand, releasing two fist-sized fireballs straight toward them. Since this person was already dead, he naturally must thoroughly dispose of the legs to prevent others from discovering this. Who knew what others troubles could arise?

Pengpeng. The flames immediately covered them. In the blink of an eye, aside from those jet-black boots, everything else had turned to ash.

Satisfied, Han Li nodded his head and turned around, thinking to depart.

“Boots? How strange!”

“How could normal boots come out unscathed from my fireballs?”

Just as Han Li took a small step to leave, he immediately saw his mistake and hurried to turn around. He looked toward those seemingly ordinary boots with an odd expression.

With a careful look, Han Li was unable to discover anything irregular. Not only were these boots not destroyed by the fireballs, but they also didn’t have a single trace of being burned. Furthermore, they faintly released slight spiritual ripples.

“Magic tool?”

Han Li asked with great bewilderment.

He hesitated for a moment and walked several steps over, lowering his head and picking up the pair of black boots.

“Light and soft, but they are still very tough! They shouldn’t be cloth or silk boots. They seem to have been made from the hide of an animal!” Han Li concluded after stroking the boots for a while.

Because he was close to them, Han Li was able to feel the boots’ faint Spiritual Qi.

They were certainly magic tools! In addition, they were likely to have been constructed from demonic beast leather.

Seeing these leather boots, Han Li faintly thought of something. He somewhat impatiently took off his cloth shoes and exchanged them for these leather boot magic tools.

They were very comfortable and soft, as if there was nothing there! This was what Han Li first thought when he wore those boots.

He carefully observed the boots after wearing them for a while. So far, nothing extraordinary had occurred.

Wrinkling his brow, Han Li took a small step.

Huchi. Han Li’s body suddenly blurred and appeared over a three meters away, light as a feather.

‘Imperial Flight Technique! No, it’s much quicker than the Imperial Flight Technique!’ Han Li thought, pleasantly surprised.

At this moment, Han Li finally knew the secret behind Feng Yue’s incomparably fast and nimble movements. It was probably because of these boots that he was able to move so strangely and as quick as lightning.

Wearing these boots, Han Li started slowly walking on the ground, gradually familiarizing himself with the boots’ performance. He gradually grew faster and faster, finally making use of Shifting Smoke Steps to speed up.

Before, Han Li’s fastest movements had been able to make his body blur, even causing afterimages to remain. After he put on these boots, Han Li became even faster, causing several identical phantoms to appear simultaneously, all using the same movements and all with the same smile. However, when all of the phantoms simultaneously and gradually converged, Han Li stood there at the center.

Motionless, Han Li stood blankly at his original location as if he were pondering about something, but he then howled with laughter and continued to laugh until tears were flowing out.

After he laughed for a long while, Han Li bent his waist and flashed with an azure light. His entirety turned into an azure wind and actually disappeared into air without a trace.

At this moment, the entire place was extremely quiet. Apart from the occasional rustling of the wind, there were no other sounds.

A burst of rumbling sounds suddenly sounded out. The nearby trees suddenly started to break apart in a strange manner from the center. The cuts were clean and smooth, making the trees resemble the flat of a mirror; however, it was clear that there wasn’t a single person in sight.

The speed at the trees breaking grew quicker and quicker. A short moment later, all that remained of the trees within a hundred meters were tree stumps.

At this moment, Han Li, enveloped in a faint azure light, appeared with a brow filled with sweat. However, he was faintly smiling and was unable to conceal the joy on his face.

Shifting Smoke Steps, leather boot magic tools, along with the Imperial Flight Technique, actually caused Han Li to become so fast that he was able to temporarily break away from the sight of an ordinary person’s naked eye, as if he had become invisible, disappearing without a trace.

According to Han Li’s estimates, even an outstanding cultivator with the aid of the Heaven’s Eye Technique would only be able to see a faint glimpse of him by exerting all their strength. If they didn’t use a defensive magic technique, Han Li would be a great threat.

Currently, so long as Han Li concentrated and a person was within an area of about ten meters away, even if it was a distance of hundred meters, it would take Han Li at most a single breath to reach them.

Naturally, this speed exceeded the limits of the human body; Han Li was only able to maintain the speed for a short amount of time. If he maintained it for too long, his entire body would break down. After all, such high speed movements were extremely stressful on Han Li’s body.

However, it was already fast enough for him to kill the opponent several times. Especially if it were a situation where he used the thread magic tool, his power would increase many times over.

Han Li lowered his head. With a sigh, he caressed the leather boots on his feet for a long while.

He felt that this item was extremely suited for him. Even if someone wanted to use some treasure talisman to exchange for them, he wouldn’t even consider it!

With his confidence increased several times over, Han Li excitedly looked around in every direction.

When he saw the corpse of the yellow-clothed woman, he lightly sighed and used a fireball to blast open a hole. He buried the woman’s body extremely crudely. That was to the limit of what Han Li could do.

After he finished this, Han Li’s figure flashed and disappeared into the forest. He currently wanted to hurry towards the central area.

However, Han Li did not know that after the massacre of the first day that the disciples spent in the forbidden area, only seventy disciples from the various sects remained. Less than half of those who had entered the forbidden area remained. The majority of these were the elite disciples of each sect, and they had all promptly arrived near the central area, preparing and waiting idly for the second day’s great purge.

Those they believed to be weak had all been mercilessly eliminated one by one.

Of course, the rich girl and the Heavenly Imperial Fortress disciple Feng Yue who had been killed by Han Li were among those who had participated in the slaughter. However, they were now dead, naturally disappearing without a trace!

Chapter 193: Division Between Enemy and Friends

“Old Feng’s treasured boots? How did you acquire them? What is your relationship? As far as I know, that guy truly treasures his Cloud Step Boots. He absolutely wouldn’t lend them to others!”

Following these few words, a gaudily dressed person came out from an unknown place and dropped down from a huge flowered tree more than sixty meters away from Han Li. He had a medium stature, eyes of different size, and a black pocked face. He appeared to be about forty years old and had seven to eight different pockets of various sizes.

However, his unbearably ugly face was shocking! His two eyes were rigidly staring at Han Li’s spiritual boots. It seemed he did not dare believe that Han Li was wearing the “Cloud Step Boots”.

“Who is your esteemed self? Why have you attacked me?” Han Li did not reply to his question and instead bluntly asked this question. He truly didn’t wish to be lead by the nose and be suppressed by the other’s presence.

When the ugly man heard this, he was surprised but immediately grew angry, his ugly face turning vicious. He raised his hand, wanting to immediately teach this brat before him a lesson in appreciating the kindness of others. However, he soon thought of something and immediately restrained his wrath with great effort, lowering his hand. He still very fiercely said, “Boy, don’t believe that just because you wear Old Feng’s spiritual boots, I won’t dare to teach you a lesson! When that old fellow Feng Yue gave you those spiritual boots, did he not mention the name of Spirit Beast Mountain’s Zhong Wu? Regardless, I am quite baffled. You are obviously someone from Yellow Maple Valley. How could he give those boots to you? Could it be that you are Old Feng’s illegitimate child? No, you don’t look quite like him!”

As the ugly man said this, he was sizing up Han Li with a peculiar gaze.

This time, it was Han Li’s turn to be angry. He snorted with an unsightly expression and coldly said, “Will your esteemed self refrain from wantonly making casual contact with others? That guy Feng Yue has already long been dead. These boots were peeled off his corpse!”

“Dead? That madman Feng Yue?”

The ugly man’s originally overbearing closeness, after hearing Han Li’s words, jumped three feet into the air and became unceasing bewilderment! Soon after, he couldn’t help but fall back several steps, once again measuring up Han Li.

“You killed him?” The fiendish man let out a deep breath as his eyes spun, asking with a harsh voice. He ceased becoming cruel and vicious.

“That’s right. Do you want to avenge him?” Han Li moved his hands behind his back. Motionless, he silently looked at his opponent.

From within the storage pouch, he secretly took out the thread and quietly wound it around his ring finger.

The reason why Han Li was so calm facing this person and admitted that he had killed Feng Yue was actually mostly to give him established power. He hoped this person would back out without a fight and no longer bother him. He did not wish to immediately engage in a battle where neither would win and waste his much important time for medicine gathering.

Although he heard from this person’s tone that it was as if he had friendly relations with Feng Yue, Han Li believed that the possibility of him truly taking revenge on behalf of Feng Yue wasn’t too large! After all, they were cultivators. The majority of them were those with few and fickle desires. Even more, this person was a villainous man.

Naturally, if the opponent insisted on taking revenge on behalf of Feng Yue, Han Li could only strike first to take the advantage. He would consume much of his physical strength to fully use his movement techniques and catch the opponent off guard, using the thread wound around his finger to quietly wrap around his neck and stealthily finish him off.

However, Han Li fully understood that the odds of success for this sort of surprise attack was not too high! The odds of success were only thirty to forty percent.

Because the distance between him and this ugly man was too far, although Han Li could rush through the sixty meter gap with his movement technique, there was no guarantee of a one-strike kill! In addition, if the opponent felt like using a defensive magic technique, his thread would become useless.

“Revenge? What kind of joke is that? Do I look like someone that bored?” As expected, it was as Han Li had thought. After the ugly man heard Han Li’s words, he chuckled and said those words with disdain.

“Previously I truly had a friendship with that man; However, it wasn’t some deep friendship. Since this person is already dead, There is naturally no longer a friendship!” The ugly man shamelessly said. Although, his words clearly revealed his position, he wasn’t embarrassed in the slightest.

Han Li remained silent. Although he did not relax his guard, he slightly relaxed his heart. It seemed he would need to fight a heavy battle immediately after entering the central area.

“But young brother, you are truly formidable and fierce! You were actually able to deal with that guy Feng Yue, especially with his top-grade magic tools, zeze ! Some of those magic tools are truly hard to come by!”

The ugly man stroked his nose and became far more affectionate toward Han Li, changing the way he addressed him! However, after he asked this, it seemed as if he indistinctly fell back several steps, greatly increasing the distance between them.

Having seen this scene, Han Li couldn’t help but bitterly smile to himself!

According to Han Li’s estimations, if they were to immediately have a falling out and fight, the odds of success just declined, making success unlikely. If this “expert” was as cunning and experienced as Han Li expected, he wouldn’t be easy to deal with!

Furthermore, he guessed that the opponent most likely believed that he obtained all of Feng Yue’s magic treasures. As a result, he faintly showed off the appearance of being afraid of retaliation.

After he became aware of this, Han Li smiled but did not speak. Since he didn’t say whether he obtained the magic tools, he didn’t need to say it, causing this evil man further annoyance and a greater fear of retaliation.

“That masterpiece on the wall in front of the gate, is that your esteemed self’s doing?” Han Li faintly asked, thinking of the scene in front of the gate.

“Nonsense! That was the work of that demon from the Saber Transformation Dock, Han Tianya. I definitely wouldn’t have done such a pointless thing! It was a great pity of such blood and flesh that was wasted. It would have been better if I fed it to my little ones; I heard the flesh of cultivators are a great supplement for them.”

As Han Li listened, he couldn’t help but faintly smile. However, when the ugly man said those words, he took out a large pouch from behind his back and threw out a bloody chunk of flesh, causing Han Li’s smile to become forced. There were even faint signs of his expression breaking.

The evil man peeked at Han Li’s current expression and couldn’t help but secretly reveal his intentions.

In the end, this Yellow Maple Valley disciple was far too young and far too soft!

With just a few of his words, he caused his mind to become restless. It a true battle broke out, this definitely would’ve been a significant mistake.

However, for this person to be able to kill that Feng Yue, he could truly be cause for surprise! But how could he see or think that such a extremely common appearance could truly be such a ferocious character?

It could be said that with this guy’s young age and meager magic power, even if he had several good magic tools, he wouldn’t be able to beat Feng Yue’s Yellow Parasol and his great quantity of top quality magic tools equivalent to the Cloud Step Boots! Still, that guy Feng Yue nonetheless fell underneath this boy’s hand. This matter was truly a bit strange, but he did wear the Cloud Step Boots; this was undeniable.

Could it be he really didn’t kill him but was able to acquire them from some other fortunate occurrence?

Zhong Wu pondered about this, but he was still confused. He was unable to accurately judge Han Li’s true strength. This caused him to take the initiative to test this with his own hands. If he tried to kill him but couldn’t…naturally such a clever man as himself wouldn’t take such a dangerous action!

After the ugly man remained puzzled and gave much deliberation, he took out his cloth pouch and blinked his uneven eyes several times. With a face full of smiles, he said to Han Li, “Oh wait, I still haven’t asked .What is Young Brother’s surname. Do you think you could tell me?”

“Yellow Maple Valley’s Han Li.”

This wasn’t something worth concealing. Han Li calmly replied with an improved complexion.

“So it turned out to be Brother Han! I previously hadn’t heard of Young Brother’s great name. Surely, your distinguished self is one of Yellow Maple Valley’s new and rising stars? How much does Brother Han understand about the central area?” Zhong Wu appeared very cordial as if he were speaking to a friend he hadn’t seen for many years.

“I don’t know much, but Brother Zhong is many years my senior. He surely must know much more than Han Li!” Han Li did not know what the other party was planning, but he grew greatly vigilant.

“Hehe! Brother Han, if you were to trust this one named Zhong, wouldn’t it be better for us to exchange our information on the central area? How about it? This is something that would benefit the both of us.” After Zhong Wu hesitated for a moment, he eventually spoke his true intentions with a soft voice.

After Han Li heard this, he was startled and inwardly contemplated this. Although it was strictly stated in the rules that exchanging his sect’s information without the approval of sect elders was not allowed, in reality, it was an act that disciples did much of! Thus, after a short moment, he wore a smile and said, “Sure. After we exchange resources, we will each greatly benefit.”

“Haha! That’s great. I knew it, Brother Han isn’t some overly careful person. Come! We’ll put our information into jade slips and then exchange them with each other. Zhong Wu’s face full of pockmarks of all sizes was glowing with excitement as he continuously rubbed his hands. It seemed he was greatly expectant of Han Li’s information.

When Han Li saw this, he greatly sneered several times; however, his external appearance was naturally in complete agreement.

To create a copy of information was a very effortless task! After the time it took to make a cup of tea, they finished making their copies and threw the jade slips to each other.

When they each had the jade slips in hand, they both roughly examined the contents. After they confirmed it seemed to be information of the central area, they both looked at each other with a smile containing an ulterior motive.

Within this small amount of time, it was naturally impossible to forge false information! However when the copies were made, some crucial information would be overlooked; this was naturally mutually understood!

After this event, Zhong Wu and Han Li seemed to all of a sudden become much closer! Zhong Wu actually told Han Li a few remarkable stories from the world of cultivators! Seeing these two laugh and talk so closely, it was truly hard to believe that not long ago they had been nearly irreconcilable adversaries. It seemed these two were experts in knowing when to retreat!

Although Han Li wore a beautiful smile and appeared as if he was interested in this chat, he was truly cursing endlessly in his heart.

‘If you want to chat, then chat! Why would you continue to maintain such a long distance!’ So long as he advanced a step, the other party would take two steps back with a hearty smile. Although Han Li had no intention to kill him, the other party’s degree of cautiousness caused Han Li to be dumbfounded.

Chapter 205: Watching the battle

After giving orders to all of the disciples, the young woman turned around and looked at the swamp in front of her, using a faint voice to murmur to herself: “It seems like that object should be inside of this chest! The previous few locations were all a waste; all I got was some trash!”

The young woman’s voice was inaudible; apart from herself, the other disciples could not hear anything at all. They were all extremely excited for the imminent, upcoming big battle.

After the young woman’s orders had been passed down, the male and female disciples from the Masked Moon Sect immediately stood side-by-side with their Dao companions. They actually both reached out a hand very skillfully and held them together.

Suddenly, the two overlapping hands individually emitted a blue and red strange brilliance; then, following down their arms, it spread to these disciples’ entire bodies, causing the six pairs of Masked Moon Sect disciples to be covered with light, red light shrouding the males’ bodies, blue light shooting off of the females, forming a strange blue-red criss-cross shape. Only three disciples remained, one male and two female, having already lost their Dao companions. They could only bring out some magic tools, merely making some basic preparations.

Han Li lay on the mound of dirt. Although he had not heard the young woman murmuring to herself, he had exactly heard the female disciple in front call her “Martial Ancestor”. This instantly caused him to almost bite his tongue and injure it in a moment of surprise!

“Martial Ancestor of the Masked Moon Sect”, what was this notion? Han Li was already no longer a rookie in the cultivation world, and he was very clear about this situation. That was a Core Formation cultivator expert who was of the same level as his sect’s Martial Ancestor Li! That this kind of an expert would actually appear in the forbidden area, which was restricted from cultivators of the Foundation Establishment stage and above, caused Han Li’s head to whirl!

At this time, seeing that all of her sect’s disciples were properly prepared, the young woman began to take action contentedly!

The young woman faintly open her dainty mouth and spat out her magic treasure, the Vermillion Bird Band. When this item came out from her mouth, it immediately whirled through the air as it traveled above the swamp and expanded to the same size as a small building.

Next, the young woman beneath it formed hand incantations for a magic technique and pointed with her finger; a streak of red light shot from her hand to the ring. In an instant, the band’s color rapidly changed from pink to a fiery, blazing red.

On top of the dirt mound, Han Li was stunned by what he saw. This kind of impact and strength…if one said that this wasn’t a magic treasure, one could beat him to death and he wouldn’t believe it.

Since the young woman could control this magic treasure, her identity as a Core Formation cultivator was undoubtable. But how was she able to make her way into the forbidden area, and why was her magic power only at the peak of the Qi Condensation stage? These string of questions flew around in Han Li’s head, but he still had no way of answering them.

The young woman had yet to take the next step when the swamp below began to show signs of movement. With a certain part of the swamp as the center, the nearby silt began to roil; in addition, the roiling area became greater and greater, and the waves higher and higher. It actually slowly formed into a huge protrusion, the sight of which was extremely shocking.

A trace of doubt flitted across the young woman’s face when she saw this; based on her memories, the Black Scale Python had never seemed to be this imposing!

However, seeing that the demonic beast’s appearance was imminent, the young woman did not dare to hesitate. Her two hands formed hand incantations for the Blue Flower magic technique, with her attention connected to the huge Vermillion Bird Band, which began to spin in the air. In a short amount of time, it became blurry because of how fast it was spinning; the hundreds of fireballs inside of it also became a red sea of fire in the time it takes to roll one’s eyes, actually dissolving into one entity.

“Go!”

The young woman spit out as her magic technique suddenly stabilized.

All of a sudden, the round ring’s spinning stopped abruptly, and the encapsulated sea of flames thus suddenly became a thick, large fire cyclone pillar that aggressively shot out downwards, directly spurting towards the huge protrusion from the swamp.

However, before the flame column had neared the swamp, a column of black, inky water as thick as a bowl’s opening shot out of the silt protrusion with a “puchi”, just in time to block the flames shooting towards it.

Suddenly, the explosions filled the air, and a large ball of mist immediately rose up in pieces, causing the surroundings to be steaming with fog in the blink of an eye. Everything became blurry.

“This isn’t the Black Scale Python!”

The young woman’s originally somewhat doubtful expression, upon seeing the column of water that was as dark as ink, immediately changed as she spoke.

As if replying to the young woman’s words, the sound of a wail came from the vast white fog; an extremely strange, piercing scream began to sound and pierce towards the sky. Then, with a “hula”, an extremely hot gust of wind began to blow, causing the surrounding white air to disappear with a roll, revealing the true colors of the demonic beast.

A black, swarthy, snake-shaped demon covered with huge scales appeared before everyone’s eyes.

This seemingly snake-like yet not a snake demonic beast’s bulk was not actually too big, only thirty to forty meters long; however, its entire body from head to toe was shrouded by a layer of faint black fog, appearing extremely demonic. In addition, its external appearance from head to tail was not much different from that of a regular black python. Of course, its black and shiny hug scales were an exception.

“Inky Flood Dragon!”

The young woman, upon clearly seeing the demonic beast’s appearance, couldn’t help but cry out; her face revealed an apprehensive yet excited expression.

However, the ten or so disciples standing behind her were somewhat puzzled. Wasn’t this the “Black Scaly Python”? Since when did it became some “Inky Flood Dragon”?

The young woman couldn’t afford to explain clearly to all the disciples because the demonic beast floating numerous meters above the ground had already found the main culprit in disturbing its rest. The two small, green eyes on the side of its head flashed malevolently; it opened its mouth, and another black column of water leaped towards the people from the Masked Moon Sect.

“Beast! You're looking to die!”

The young woman knew very well the strength of the Inky Flood Dragon; although this demonic beast seemed as if it was young, she did not dare to be careless at all! She hurriedly controlled the Vermillion Bird Band, instantly releasing a red ring of light that suddenly flashed and blocked in front of the young woman. Then, a string of fireballs came flying out from within the ring, causing that black water to be stopped halfway to its destination.

“Receive, Speed, Restrain, Arrest, Lock!”

The young woman’s two hands formed a half-half contained a full-moon as she awe-inspiringly spit out these five words from her mouth.

When these five words had just left her mouth, the Vermillion Bird Band began to jitter rapidly in midair; then, it began to emit a low ring, and disappeared into thin air. This caused the spiritually wise Inky Flood Dragon to blink its small eyes, staring blankly because of it.

But the next instant, the ring actually directly appeared on the demonic beast’s forehead while humming. It took advantage of the demonic beast’s slowness to react and instantly sank down, then rapidly became much smaller. In the blink of an eye, the Vermillion Bird Band actually abruptly wrapped around the Inky Flood Dragon’s midsection, and then a fiery light rose up rapidly on the ring. Instantly, half of the demonic beast’s body was enveloped in the fierce flames.

“Move quickly! I can’t contain this Inky Flood Dragon for too long.”

Although the Vermillion Bird Band had securely wrapped the demonic beast, the young woman didn’t have any relaxing expression; instead, she sent out commands behind her with anxiety.

Although the Masked Moon Sect disciples behind her did not know how the Black Scaly Python had suddenly become the Inky Flood Dragon that their Martial Ancestor informed them about, this did not prevent them from releasing the offensive that they had prepared a long time ago.

“Attack!”

Under the orders of a relatively elderly, white-clothed female, ten columns of red and blue intersecting light were released from these male and female disciple’s bodies, emitting an appalling “chi chi” sound that tore through the air. They unmistakably attacked the immobile demonic beast.

A series of loud “hong hong” sounds spread out; when these columns had just reached near the demonic beast’s body, they were forcibly blocked by the faint black fog that shrouded its body. Fierce bursting sounds rang out.

“Continue to attack, the Inky Flood Dragon’s protective fog can’t hold on much longer!” The young woman commanded hastily, her eyes sharp. At the same time, she continued to push the red flaming technique on the Vermillion Bird Band, causing the flames surrounding the demonic beast to become even more vigorous.

Under the string of commands from the young woman, the Masked Moon Sect disciples incessantly shot out individual columns of red and blue light, hitting the demonic beast’s body. Although they had yet to break through that layer of black fog, they had already caused that demonic beast to howl and go crazy; it bared its teeth and viciously shook the two halves of its body that were able to move, furiously trying to break free from the ring’s grasp. However, its struggle was futile; under the young woman’s all-out efforts to restrict it, the round ring was fixed in midair, not moving even a little, thoroughly locking down its body.

Watching from the side, Han Li was struck with fright; he had never seen the spectacle of a group of cultivators this large battling a common enemy. Even more, the appearance of the magic treasure and fact that the opponent was a demonic beast that wasn’t weak was a big eye-opener for him.

However, Han Li also decided that whether the demonic beast beat its enemies or the Masked Moon Sect people killed the demonic beast, he would quietly sneak away after the big battle. This was not the time to casually expose his own tracks!

“Wu……”

Just as Han Li was entertaining all sorts of ideas in his head, the Inky Flood Dragon suddenly let out a long cry, its sound numerous times louder than before; at the same time, its scream was filled with pain.

Han Li was started and immediately fixed his gaze there.

He saw that the black fog on the demonic beast had already completely dissipated, and a bowl-opening-wide bloody hole had appeared on the area of its body covered by the huge scales. Evidently, it had been hurt by the red and blue columns of light. The agony also caused the demonic beast’s struggling to become even more crazy!

'It seems that the people from the Masked Moon Sect are of a higher skill level!' Han Li couldn’t help but think after seeing this.

“Not good! Everyone, be careful! I can’t contain this Inky Flood Dragon any longer!”

Han Li was stunned when he heard the young woman. It was difficult to tell who the winner would be!

Chapter 208: Joyous Meeting

Han Li felt that he was having an incredibly marvelous, erotic dream; the person with him in the dream had a burning passion, but he could never clearly see the face of the peerless beauty

But even if the erotic dream were better, there would always be a time when he would wake up. After an unknown amount of time had passed, Han Li finally awoke from his glamorous dream.

But as soon as he opened his eyes, what he saw was a gorgeous, peerless face and a pair of snow-like cold pupils. This beautiful face was both unfamiliar yet familiar at the same time, causing Han Li’s heart to thump once.

“You woke up!” The young woman said indifferently with a voice no trace of emotion. This caused a slight chill to rise from Han Li’s back when he heard it.

Speaking of a chill, Han Li discovered that his entire naked body was tightly embracing a similarly naked beautiful woman. The woman’s face was first crimson, but immediately her sleek eyebrows rose vertically, and her jade-like face frosted over. She coldly spat out:

“Have you had enough! Take your dog paws off me and let me go!”

Started, Han Li instinctively retrieved both of his hands and released the woman.

This great beauty, seeing that Han Li had let go, hurriedly used one hand to push herself off the ground. Her eye-catching, curved body immediately stood up from Han Li’s chest.

But just as the extremely beautiful young woman’s slender waist had straightened, she yelled out, her flowery face losing its color with pain. Her body shook once, and then she fell again into Han Li’s chest, causing Han Li to again experience the feeling of soft jade covering his torso.

Han Li did not consider himself to be a base person, but he definitely did not consider himself to be a person with noble character.

So when this beautiful woman had thrown herself into his arms, he regained his focus and immediately rode his hands up, pressing the woman up against his body. The, he gently kissed the woman’s tender, alluring lips, causing the words that the woman had wanted to berate Han Li with to be forcibly shocked away. Underneath Han Li’s hot kisses, her slender eyebrows slowly smoothed out, and she began to fall into a trance.

What followed was a case of “when conditions are right, success will naturally follow”!

Han Li and the young woman wordlessly enjoyed the taste of ecstasy between a man and a woman once again. This, compared to the experience they had when the two of them were in a state of semi-consciousness, caused them to become even more intoxicated and made them even more crazy and forgetful!

Today, the beautiful woman’s two eyes were tightly pressed up against Han Li’s chest, her two cheeks flushed red, her chest rising and falling indefinitely. Evidently, she had yet to awaken from the greatest stimulus. Han Li embraced this beautiful woman with one hand, and the other hand was incessantly fondling the woman’s round and well-developed area with a desire to continue.

After an unknown amount of time, the gorgeous woman’s breathing finally stabilized, and her expression had finally returned to normal. She slowly opened her eyes.

This time she didn’t say a single sentence to Han Li, immediately pushing aside Han Li’s mischief-causing hand from her body. She stood up with a bleak expression and walked towards a nearby storage pouch. Han Li was slightly startled, but after a moment of hesitation, he did not obstruct this woman.

The young woman retrieved a set of snow-white garments from the storage pouch and gently put them on. Not too long afterwards, she finished getting dressed, causing her entire temperament to change in an instant; she began to appear graceful and poised. At this time, she turned her head around to glance at Han Li, then stared blankly for a moment!

This was because Han Li had long since stood, neatly clothed, not too far behind her. He was currently gazing at her with an admiring and tender gaze, causing this woman’s state of mind to stir. A trace of a strange feeling crept into her heart.

“You should be very clear about what kind of person I am! The things that happened between us were only mistakes! Just pretend it was all a dream!” the young woman said faintly, gently curling her sleek hair.

“I know!” Han Li answered peacefully after a moment of silence, rubbing his nose.

“If a third person finds out what happened today, I will kill you!” the young woman suddenly stated in a cold tone.

“I will not breathe a word. If this matter travels to the outside world, you can just kill me!” Han Li warmly responded with a faint smile.

“Hmph! As long as you know!” Seeing that Han Li agreed instantly, the woman did not actually feel happy in her heart; in fact, she began to feel somewhat vexed, and her tone became even more vile.

After saying this, the woman and Han Li remained silent in a stalemate for some time; neither of them uttered another sentence.

Although the woman was a Core Formation cultivator, she had always spent her time cultivating as a child; as for the affairs between males and females, she was not much different from normal young women. Thus, although she had instinctively forced Han Li to not transmit this matter to the outside world, her thoughts were still in turmoil, unsure of how to face this matter.

Han Li was not much better than the woman; he had never expected that his first intimate relationship with a woman would actually be with a female Core Formation cultivator. In addition, it was with this kind of a peerless talent and beautiful person, completely different from the sweet-tempered, pretty daughter from a humble family that he had imagined. This caused him to laugh bitterly. Would this one-night affair be a blessing or a curse to him?

But regardless of what it would be, Han Li had already seen that the woman did not harbor the malevolent idea of killing him to silence him, causing him to let out a sigh of relief. Many favorable impressions spawned towards this great beauty with whom he had already experienced the affairs of a husband and wife. But these were only favorable impressions; if the other person still wanted to become hostile and make a move, Han Li decided that he would not resign himself to death!

“What exactly was that sphere? How could it cause you and me to……” Han Li was the first to open his mouth, but after saying half of the sentence, he did not continue; however, he trusted that the other person would be able to understand his meaning.

“That was the Inky Flood Dragon’s prostate capsule; I didn’t expect that this beast actually was a very rarely seen male flood dragon, and I actually carelessly forgot this matter! This capsule contains an aphrodisiacal fog; when it contacts any female, it will immediately erupt.”

“So it was like that!”

Hearing this, Han Li was finally enlightened! The riddle in his heart was finally resolved.

“Then your current appearance, why is it different from before…..”

“I practice a sect-unique cultivation technique, the Female Essence Incarnation Technique. This magic technique, although somewhat strange, can allow a person to remain perpetually young. Every ten years, this magic technique will cycle through once. My magic strength would have gone through the cycle, and I thus naturally would have restored my young appearance. But after what happened between us, this technique was temporarily broken and I slightly aged!” the young woman explained casually after a moment of silence.

“Then you won’t have any troubles, right?” Han Li didn’t know why he couldn’t help but ask this question.

“It’s not a problem. My magic technique is already at great success stage; even if my virginity has been broken, I will only lose five to six years of magic power; this to me does not count for much!” said the woman coldly, glancing at Han Li with a complicated expression.

Hearing this, Han Li became silent. He knew that the other person’s heart still contained a significant amount of resentment towards losing her virginity. He could only remain silent and face it!

This woman truly felt that she had been extremely wronged!

She had just then secretly sized up the other person a few times and had confirmed once again that this Yellow Maple Valley disciple was truly completely average, whether in terms of appearance or natural talent. And she had actually done things that should only be done between a husband and wife with this person. How could this not cause her, who had always been proud and arrogant, to feel incredibly dejected!

But she was also somewhat reluctant of the idea of killing this person to relieve the hatred in her heart. After all, the other person was the male who had taken away her virginity, and she inevitably had a few strange feelings towards this person. This caused her to feel both anger and hatred!

“What time is it now? It shouldn’t have passed the time limit of five days, right?” Han Li couldn’t help but ask after suddenly recalling something.

Upon hearing this, the woman, whose state of mind was already unstable, felt an abrupt fright spring up in her heart, but immediately afterwards, she calmed down and said calmly:

“It shouldn’t have been that long. The sedative contained in the Inky Flood Dragon’s aphrodisiacal smoke should be very low in concentration! At most, we were unconscious for five to six hours.”

“But if we want to leave, we also must make our preparations now; this dangerous area is not so easy to exit from,” added the woman, knitting her eyebrows.

“However, before all of that, you have no opinions on me taking this treasure chest, right?!” inquired the young woman as she glanced coldly at Han Li, her almond lips opening slightly.

Hearing this, Han Li bitterly laughed; although at the moment he could not sense the depth of that woman’s magic power, it was definitely above the Foundation Establishment stage. How could he dare to fight with her over the treasure chest!

The woman, seeing that Han Li did not utter a word, coldly smiled and leaped towards the white jade pavilion. In the end, she very smoothly retrieved the golden chest into her storage pouch, then flew back to Han Li’s side.

“Those spiritual medicines……!” Seeing that the woman had not harvested those spiritual medicines, Han Li stammered, somewhat baffled.

“I have no need of them; if you like them, you can harvest them all!” The woman glanced at Han Li and said without geniality after hearing this.

Hearing these words, Han Li became very happy in his heart. He had just been worrying that, after exiting the forbidden area, he would not have enough spiritual medicines to turn in to his sect and would seem suspicious to others! Thus, he unhesitatingly immediately flew over, and in the time it took to roll one’s eyes he retrieved tens of spiritual medicines.

The woman stood in the same spot and coldly watched Han Li’s movements without making a sound. Only after Han Li harvested the medicines and return, did she slowly and solemnly say, “To break free from this place requires cooperation between the two of us; we cannot successfully leave this place if one of us is missing…”

Chapter 210: The Gamble

Han Li suddenly thought of the other young woman that he had encountered inside the forbidden area and couldn’t help but glance in the direction of Spirit Beast Mountain. In the end, he discovered that Han Yunzhi was cutely sitting cross-legged on the ground, her expression very even. There did not seem to be anything unexpected, causing Han Li to let out a sigh of relief.

Near the closed tunnel entrance, those from the Masked Moon Sect appeared increasingly unsightly from worry.

As for the people from the other sects, although they outwardly appeared to be anxious for the Masked Moon Sect disciples, flower of happiness had contrarily bloomed in their hearts. After all, the Masked Moon Sect was State of Yue’s strongest sect and had long attracted the jealousy of others. These few were naturally happy to see an opportunity to weaken its power.

Perhaps because their wishes had gone awry, the opposite of their desires occurred; when the passageway was only a quarter hour away from closing, a white shadow flashed within the passageway, and a group of ten or so Masked Moon Sect disciples walked out in an orderly fashion. Their leader was the extremely alluring beauty Nangong.

Seeing them walk out, the Senior Eccentric Qiong’s reaction was acceptable, only letting out a long sigh. That Celestial Ni Chang couldn’t help but pounce at her, tugging on the arm of the beautiful Celestial Nangong. She began to ask her questions with extreme concern, her face revealing an expression of anxiety.

The other sects felt puzzled upon seeing this.

This was no surprise. Although Nangong Wan had met with these Core Formation cultivators several times, she had worn a veil and never revealed her true appearance. Thus, these people did not actually know that the beautiful, flowery young woman before them was actually the “Celestial Nangong” that they had met with numerous times.

Seeing this woman had safely returned, Han Li was also very pleased. After all, she was the first person he had joined bodies with. Even if he clearly knew that there was no way to continue their relationship, in his heart he still couldn’t help but worry about her.

However, the smiles on Martial Ancestor Li and the Daoist Priest’s face had become somewhat forced. This was not unexpected; ignoring how many spiritual medicines the Masked Moon Sect had harvested, even the number of people that had walked out of forbidden area alive had surpassed the combined numbers of the people from their two sects. How could this not cause the two of them to be extremely depressed!

“All of the disciples should have emerged by now. The ones who didn’t appear...” muttered the leader of the Spirit Beast Mountain, clearing his throat.

But before he had finished his sentence, a person came scrambling out of the tunnel that was just about to close. It was actually that old, crafty Xiang Zhili from Yellow Maple Valley; only, the Giant Sword Sect and the young Daoist Priest originally harvesting the spiritual medicines with him had disappeared without a trace.

The old man had just crawled out of the passageway when thunderous vibrations came from the direction of the forbidden area; next, an azure light flashed, and the passageway fragmented, finally disappearing completely.

At this time, even if there were still people inside the forbidden area who had yet to come out, it would only be a dead end for them. This was because any disciple who had not exited in time in the past never appeared again even at the next opening of the forbidden area. They had all disappeared for an unclear reason, and this was also the reason why other people were not willing to waste time.

However, the fact that this old, crafty Yellow Maple Valley tenth layer cultivator could actually escape at the very end was truly beyond expectation. They couldn’t help but size up Xiang Zhili.

“Brother Li, I didn’t expect that your esteemed valley actually had so many talents! Not only eleventh layer cultivators could walk out of the forbidden area, even tenth-layer strength disciples can preserve their lives and exit. Your esteemed sect truly uses the correct method of teaching your disciples, I am truly in admiration!” Seeing that only two people from his sect had left the forbidden area, and that the barefooted male whom he had high hopes for had not come out while two low-level disciples from the Yellow Maple Valley had come out and preserved their own small lives, the cultivator from the Giant Sword Sect couldn’t help but feel his anger rise. He said these two sentences mockingly.

When Martial Ancestor Li heard this, his face fell. He also reckoned that Han Li and Xiang Zhili had both stayed in hiding and did not reveal themselves, wanting to seize any opportunity available. He could not help but bitterly glare at the old, crafty man, but he still had no choice but to protect the two of them with his words:

“The cultivation technique of these juniors is too superficial. Being able to preserve their own lives can also be considered to be their own good fortune; as for what method they used, the others and I, as their senior generation, have no need to add on any blame!”

“Hmph!”

The Giant Sword Sect expert, seeing Martial Ancestor Li put on such an act, found it extremely objectionable and wanted to say something else. However, Senior Eccentric Qiong opened his mouth, somewhat impatiently.

“What is there for you two to argue about? Since the person could survive, this is the skill of the junior generation; do you want them to stubbornly charge forwards even if they clearly know it is impossible! However, little fellow Li! Quickly examine the results of the bet. The earlier we know, the earlier our hearts will be at ease; do you want the elderly me to wait here for even longer?”

This old man was clearly taking advantage of his age, but Martial Ancestor Li and the man from the Giant Sword Sect actually really did not dare to make this person unhappy. They could only glance at each other before laughing the matter off. Otherwise, if this old freak started holding a grudge against them, they would have some really bad luck!

Thus, under Senior Eccentric Qiong’s urging, Fu Yunzi of the Clear Void Sect and Martial Ancestor Li could only pinch their noses and move closer to him. Then, each of the disciples from the three sects that had come out of the forbidden area individually displayed the harvest that they had in order to determine the winner and loser of the bet!

The Clear Void Sect’s Daoist Priests who had walked out from the forbidden area were only four in number. However, when the middle-aged Daoist Priest that had been the first to walk out of the forbidden area brought out his spiritual medicines, the faces of all the people present changed slightly.

“Fully mature three hundred year-old Blood Blue Pearls, two three hundred-year-old Sky Spirit Fruits, three four hundred-year-old Chalcedony Mushrooms……”

The Daoist Priest brought out eleven or twelve spiritual medicines in a row, individually placing them on the ground. The quantity was extremely high, greatly astonishing the surrounding people. Only Fu Yunzi, who had made the bet, was lightly smiling with content, as if he was very satisfied by the stunned looks of the others.

Not only that, the spiritual medicines that the elders from Yellow Maple Valley and the male Masked Moon Sect disciples had placed earlier were far less, each person merely placing a few herbs.

Next, the harvest of the second Daoist Priest was finally not as excessive, but there were still seven or eight spiritual medicines, significantly greater than harvests under normal circumstances! This caused Martial Ancestor to begin to feel unsettled, and Senior Eccentric Qiong’s look of laughter was also retrieved; he became serious for the first time.

Hearing of the matter concerning the bet, the experts from the other four sects naturally became interested and individually came forward to take a look. When they saw this scene, they also quietly considered it amazing!

However, the spiritual medicines of the Chen Clan brother and sister pair after them finally allowed Martial Ancestor Li to be somewhat delighted, since their combined harvest neared twenty herbs, already roughly the same as those two Daoist Priests. The next Clear Void Sect disciple’s harvest was finally normal, only four herbs.

As for the Masked Moon Sect disciples, they maintained an average quantity; three people in a row had five or under herbs, causing the Daoist Priest and Martial Ancestor Li to quietly sigh in relief.

However, the next youth from Yellow Maple Valley to place his spiritual medicines delayed for a few moments; with great shame he only pulled out three spiritual medicines. This caused Martial Ancestor Li to become so angry that his nose almost became crooked. He almost opened his mouth to berate him. This was because he did not have any belief that Han Li or the crafty old man could contribute much!

According to sequence, it should have been Han Li’s turn to go forwards, but who knew that crafty Xiang, with a stride, would grab the place in front of Han Li, respectfully pulling out two Purple Monkey Flowers. This caused Martial Ancestor Li to feel great surprise, and his expression instantly became somewhat more pleasant; however, it was merely somewhat more! Although he had one or two more spiritual medicines than the Clear Void Sect in front of him, as long as the other side’s last individual could bring out a normal amount of spiritual medicines, he would definitely lose. He had absolutely no hope that Han Li’s harvest would be too large, reckoning that Han Li at most would be like the crafty old man. Throwing two or three spiritual medicines would already be not too bad, and it could be considered the due diligence of these lower-level disciples.

Thinking to this point, Martial Ancestor Li couldn’t help but glance at Fu Yunzi, only to see the other person’s restless appearance; he was also currently glancing at him. The two of them slightly started, then immediately averted their gazes, continuing to closely follow the gambling game.

The last Daoist Priest to step forward was a white-haired elderly man. When he walked to the front, he calmly brought out one herb after another; his slow dilly-dallying manner caused all of the people to continuously roll their eyes.

However, when he had pulled out five spiritual medicines in a row and was still reaching into his storage pouch, Martial Ancestor Li’s expression instantly sank, while Fu Yunzi began to beam with joy. As for the Masked Moon Sect disciples, those two people were unable to endure anymore and walked over, expressing their interest.

Greatly beyond any expectations, this last white-haired Daoist Priest actually pulled out seven spiritual medicines in a row, causing all of the onlookers to feel greatly surprised.

When Martial Ancestor Li saw this, his expression had already become incredibly ashen, while the Daoist Priest excitedly turned his attention to the other Masked Moon Sect disciples, reckoning that his victory over the Yellow Maple Valley was already secure.

At this time, Han Li stepped forward. Other people only indifferently glanced at him before returning their gazes to the Masked Moon Sect, completely ignoring him.

Martial Ancestor Li also saw this scene, but he similarly did not glance at Han Li at all, reckoning that he had already lost his opportunity to make a comeback. This eleventh layer disciple’s appearance would only be to make a fool of himself; thus, he naturally would not give Han Li any face.

Han Li did not pay attention to the movements of other people, and even more didn’t have the idea of saving some ripe spiritual medicines and bringing out less.

This was because each sect’s ranks contained two other stewards, who had one or two smelling spiritual beasts by their sides. These kinds of squirrel-like strange beasts could smell out any hidden hundred-year-old or above spiritual medicines from a distance of thirty feet. Even if they were inside a storage pouch, they could not escape notice.

Thus, every disciple that exited the forbidden area, after voluntarily turning in all of their spiritual medicines, also had to be smelled by these small beasts once over before being allowed to leave. This was to prevent against disciples with malicious plans to smuggle a secret stash of spiritual medicines!

Arriving at the location, Han Li held a storage pouch in his hand that he had prepared a long time ago. Then, he rudely flipped his hand, dropping it on the table. After a burst of white light, a huge pile of roughly twenty or so multicolored spiritual medicines formed a huge pile on the ground.